<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><id>https://github.com/weg38asyy/GameRss.git</id><title>My Game Rss</title><updated>2023-04-22T13:13:40.405404+00:00</updated><author><name>Koala</name><email>weg38asyy@gmail.com</email></author><link href="https://github.com/weg38asyy" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Personal learning of English use</subtitle><entry><id>https://www.gamespot.com/articles/star-wars-jedi-survivor-xbox-digital-edition-preorders-discounted/1100-6513474/</id><title>Star Wars Jedi: Survivor Xbox Digital Edition Preorders Discounted</title><updated>2023-04-22T13:13:40.405643+00:00</updated><content type="html">Star Wars Jedi: Survivor will be released on April 28, and if you're still looking for a copy--Xbox digital edition preorders are discounted by $10 over at Newegg. Use the promo code SWSVV to get Star Wars Jedi: Survivor standard edition for $60 ($70) or the deluxe edition for $80 (90$). &lt;br&gt;   &lt;br&gt;   &lt;br&gt; This is a good deal for Star Wars Jedi: Survivor preorders and the lowest actual discount we've seen. A comparative offer is Best Buy including a $10 gift card with standard and deluxe edition preorders. Newegg's discount is limited to Xbox, while Best Buy offers the gift card deal for all platforms, including PlayStation and PC. &lt;br&gt; All Star Wars Jedi: Survivor preorders, regardless of which retailer you purchase the game from, come with the Jedi Survival Cosmetic Pack containing Obi-Wan Kenobi-inspired cosmetics, including the Hermit Cosmetic for Cal, the Combustion Blaster skin, and the Hermit Lightsaber skin. &lt;br&gt; The Star Wars Jedi: Survivor deluxe edition includes the preorder bonus and also two more cosmetic packs: New Hero Cosmetic Pack and Galactic Hero Cosmetic Pack. Combined, the packs include two outfits for Cal, two skins for BD-1, a DL-44 Blaster Set, and a Rebel Hero Lightsaber. &lt;br&gt; For more information, you can check out our Star Wars Jedi: Survivor preorder guide. &lt;br&gt; Star Wars Jedi: Survivor is the sequel to Star Wars Jedi: Fallen Order. Check out our Star Wars Jedi: Survivor preview for a glimpse of what you can expect from Cal Kestis' next journey. &lt;br&gt; Star Wars Jedi: Survivor releases on April 28 for PS5, Xbox Series X|S, and PC.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;詳細句子文法解析：&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. "Star Wars Jedi: Survivor will be released on April 28, and if you're still looking for a copy--Xbox digital edition preorders are discounted by $10 over at Newegg." &lt;br&gt;這是一個條件句，其中if引導了條件子句，表示當某件事情發生時，另外一件事情也會隨之發生。使用此種文法可以表達前後因果與條件與結果之間的關係。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. "Use the promo code SWSVV to get Star Wars Jedi: Survivor standard edition for $60 ($70) or the deluxe edition for $80 (90$)."&lt;br&gt;在這個句子中，使用了動詞不定式結構來表達目的，也就是為了什麼而做什麼。動詞不定式結構可以作為目的語、主語、表語等等，用意清晰明確，常用於簡單明了的句子中。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. "This is a good deal for Star Wars Jedi: Survivor preorders and the lowest actual discount we've seen."&lt;br&gt;這個句子中，使用了形容詞的最高級表達了極端讚揚的含義。最高級通常用於超過兩個人或事物之間的比較，是形容詞的比較級和原級之外的一種角度。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. "A comparative offer is Best Buy including a $10 gift card with standard and deluxe edition preorders."&lt;br&gt;在這個句型中，使用了兩個正義的相似對比。比較級形容詞會形成一種銜接與相互關聯的複數橋樑，這樣就能較好地比較相似點和差異之間的關係。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. "Newegg's discount is limited to Xbox, while Best Buy offers the gift card deal for all platforms, including PlayStation and PC."&lt;br&gt;這句話使用了兩個時間連接詞，表示在同一時間或添加一個新的概念，在日期或起點之前或之後發生兩個行動或事件。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;6. "All Star Wars Jedi: Survivor preorders, regardless of which retailer you purchase the game from, come with the Jedi Survival Cosmetic Pack containing Obi-Wan Kenobi-inspired cosmetics, including the Hermit Cosmetic for Cal, the Combustion Blaster skin, and the Hermit Lightsaber skin."&lt;br&gt;本句使用了許多名詞並將它們放在同一結構中，形成一個長階排序列。這種方式可以讓句子清晰易讀，從而更好地表達訊息。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;7. "The Star Wars Jedi: Survivor deluxe edition includes the preorder bonus and also two more cosmetic packs: New Hero Cosmetic Pack and Galactic Hero Cosmetic Pack."&lt;br&gt;在這個句子中，使用了一個包括的動詞形式，指示對象、項目或概念的完整集合依照它所指示的完整性加以敘述，該句式特別適用於數學、科學和企業硏究等領域，可以給人一個直覺的概成功能和公式。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;8. "Combined, the packs include two outfits for Cal, two skins for BD-1, a DL-44 Blaster Set, and a Rebel Hero Lightsaber."&lt;br&gt;在這個句子中，使用了分詞結構，可以進一步說明句子的主要動作，這種結構通常用來表達原因、條件、時間和方式。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;9. "For more information, you can check out our Star Wars Jedi: Survivor preorder guide."&lt;br&gt;在這個句子中，使用了 第二人稱可區別，這是一種常見的寫作技巧，特別是在如何文本中。使用這種寫作技巧可以讓讀者感覺他們正在參與對話或操作，從而更好地理解文本。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;10. "Star Wars Jedi: Survivor is the sequel to Star Wars Jedi: Fallen Order."&lt;br&gt;本句使用了一個關係副詞結構，以描述主要子句和相對子句之間的關係，關係副詞通常可以指示處所、人、時間、原因、方式，還可以用來類型化或比較。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;單字：&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. preorders - 預訂（注文）&lt;br&gt;- 記憶方式：將preorders拆解成prefix "pre"與字根"order"，pre前綴中的"pre-"可以解釋為"前"或"先"，或者指事情發生或完成之前需要什麼前置決策。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;日文單字：注文（ちゅうもん）&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. deluxe - 豪華的（豪華な）&lt;br&gt;- 記憶方式：這個單詞可以拆解成"deluxe"，"delu-"在拉丁語中是"豪華的"，例如deluxe hotel。 加上字尾"x"，就組成了這個熟悉的詞彙。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;日文單字：豪華な（ごうかな）&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. promo - 促銷（プロモ）&lt;br&gt;- 記憶方式：這個單詞沒有很深刻的記憶方式，只需要熟記其含義即可，例如："promo code"表示"促銷代碼"。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;日文單字：プロモ&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. cosmetic - 化妝品；美容（化粧品；美容）&lt;br&gt;- 記憶方式：這個單詞可以拆解成"cosm-"和"etic"，"cosm-"意味著 "宇宙"， -etic意味著"相關的"或"演化的"。因此，cosmetic便是指與宇宙演化相關的東西。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;日文單字：化粧品（けしょうひん）&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. rebellion - 反叛；起義（反逆；謀反）&lt;br&gt;- 記憶方式：該單詞源自名詞"rebel"，可以拆分為"re-"和"bel"，"re-"前綴通常表示"再次"或"重複"，而"bel"部分的字根可以解釋為"反抗"或"起義"。因此，rebellion是 "再次反抗"或"重複起義"。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;日文單字：反逆（はんぎゃく）&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;6. glimpse - 一瞥；看一眼（一見）&lt;br&gt;- 記憶方式：glimpse可以拆解成"glim"和"pse"，"glim-"的字根意味著"一瞥"，"pse-"的字根則表示"精神"或"心理"，因此，glimpse可以被視為指在一個瞬間捕捉到的精神或心理功能。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;日文單字：一瞬（いっしゅん）&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;7. hermit - 隱士（世捨て人）&lt;br&gt;- 記憶方式：hermit是一個示範性的單詞，其與hermitage有聯繫。 Hermitage是指一個隱士的住所，在一個僻靜的地方，可能是一個山洞，一個瞭望塔等，有時可能杜蘭特起到避難所的作用。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;日文單字：世捨て人（よもだれ）&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;8. blaster - 槍械；炸藥；打擊（ブラスター）&lt;br&gt;- 記憶方式：blaster的字根可以解釋為"爆破"或"發射"，因此，可以與槍械、炸彈等緊密聯繫。英文解釋blasted（徹底毀滅）完全彰顯出這種連接。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;日文單字：爆撃（ばくげき）&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;9. gift card - 禮品卡（ギフトカード）&lt;br&gt;- 記憶方式：這個短語非常容易記憶，因為它是先進不需太多描述的理念。 禮品卡的概念常常被植入消費者名字的概念之中，因此也經常與OxygenCard, Visa等名信片母公司聯想到一起。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;日文單字：ギフトカード&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;10. platform - 平台（プラットフォーム）&lt;br&gt;- 記憶方式：此概念料不用太多的描述，因為在數個方面（如計算機、媒體、旅遊、工程等）， platform的概念已非常成熟。這個詞可以通過其他典型概念關聯起來，如音樂平台、饗宴平台等等。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;日文單字：プラットフォーム&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;片語：&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. discounted by - 折扣(price reduced by)；降價(reduce the price)&lt;br&gt;- 相似片語：marked down、price cut&lt;br&gt;- 反義片語：raised up、price up、price increased&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. regardless of - 不论；无论（～に関係なく、～にかかわらず）&lt;br&gt;- 相似片語：in spite of、despite&lt;br&gt;- 反義片語：as a result of、due to&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. come with - 附属；随附（付属する）&lt;br&gt;- 相似片語：include、enclosed&lt;br&gt;- 反義片語：exclude、take away&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. combined with - 与...结合；与...组合（〜と組み合わせた、〜に加えて）&lt;br&gt;- 相似片語：together with、along with&lt;br&gt;- 反義片語：apart from、independent of&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. check out - 看看；查看（チェックする）&lt;br&gt;- 相似片語：look into、examine&lt;br&gt;- 反義片語：ignore、neglect&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;6. regardless of which - 不论哪一个；无论哪一个（どちらでも、どの...でも）&lt;br&gt;- 相似片語：no matter which、whichever&lt;br&gt;- 反義語: certain specified (指定した、特定の)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;7. limited to - 限于；受限于（〜に限定された、〜に制限された）&lt;br&gt;- 相似片語：restricted to、confined to&lt;br&gt;- 反義片語：unlimited to、open to&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;8. including - 包括；含括（〜を含めて）&lt;br&gt;- 相似片語：comprising、containing&lt;br&gt;- 反義片語：excluding、leaving out&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;9. regardless of where - 不管在哪裡（どこにいても、どこにあっても） &lt;br&gt;- 相似片語：no matter where、wherever&lt;br&gt;- 反義片語：in a specific place、in particular location&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;10. in the lowest - 最低（最低）&lt;br&gt;- 相似片語：the bottom, least&lt;br&gt;- 反義片語：the highest, uppermost, top</content><link href="https://www.gamespot.com/articles/star-wars-jedi-survivor-xbox-digital-edition-preorders-discounted/1100-6513474/" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>