<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><id>https://github.com/weg38asyy/GameRss.git</id><title>My Game Rss</title><updated>2023-04-23T13:12:18.843365+00:00</updated><author><name>Koala</name><email>weg38asyy@gmail.com</email></author><link href="https://github.com/weg38asyy" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Personal learning of English use</subtitle><entry><id>https://www.gamespot.com/articles/crochet-creator-crafts-functional-ddr-pad/1100-6513475/</id><title>Crochet Creator Crafts Functional DDR Pad</title><updated>2023-04-23T13:12:18.843601+00:00</updated><content type="html">You can now dance dance away with your fingers using some tech wizardry plus crochet. TikTok creator kims_threads (Via Polygon) posted a tutorial explained how they made a functional DDR pad by crocheting yarn, weaving conductive thread in-between the crocheted pattern, and plugging the creation into the open-source software project Arduino. They then shows footage of them playing DDR with their fingers. &lt;br&gt; As Polygon points out, you could enlarge the project in theory by crocheting granny squares, making a cozy and customizable full-size DDR mat. Such a mat would need some extra work or a base mat to place under it so that it wouldn't slip around while you are trying to dance. &lt;br&gt; Kims_threads has yet to upload a pattern for the creation, though they might, as they sell several other patterns on her Etsy shop. However, they used a tutorial from Popular Science as a baseline for their own creation. With some trial, error, and ingenuity, you could make your very own crochet DDR pad. &lt;br&gt; This is just one of Kims_threads video game/tech-themed projects, which include a knit Animal Crossing beanie and a AR-enabled, crochet Tamagochi tapestry. &lt;br&gt; Fun fact: crochet, unlike knitting, cannot be done by machines (yet). I'll believe the robot overlords are coming for us when they can crochet a DDR pad of their very own. &lt;br&gt; Video credit: kims_threads via Tiktok&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;詳細句子文法解析：&lt;br&gt;1. You can now dance dance away with your fingers using some tech wizardry plus crochet.&lt;br&gt;這是一個由"with/using + 名詞"構成的片語，可以表示所使用的工具或方式。此外，英文中經常使用倒裝句，使句子更加生動。本句中的"dance away"則表示以很大的熱情或心情來跳舞。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. TikTok creator kims_threads (Via Polygon) posted a tutorial, explained how they made a functional DDR pad by crocheting yarn, weaving conductive thread in-between the crocheted pattern, and plugging the creation into the open-source software project Arduino.&lt;br&gt;本句經由"by + Ving"表達了一個因果關係，並強調製作DDR板墊所使用的方法和步驟。此外，“in-between”的使用則可以用來表示物體之間的距離和關係。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. They then show footage of them playing DDR with their fingers.&lt;br&gt;"then"在此句子中用來表示「時間上的先後關係」。此外，利用名詞來句子主語，所使用的動詞也要隨之變化。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. As Polygon points out, you could enlarge the project in theory by crocheting granny squares, making a cozy and customizable full-size DDR mat.&lt;br&gt;此句為一個方式狀語從句。 "in theory"表示「理論上」，強調創造此物體的可能性。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. Such a mat would need some extra work or a base mat to place under it so that it wouldn't slip around while you are trying to dance.&lt;br&gt;本句中使用了"would"表達假設的情況，表示「如果……將會……」。此外，"so that"常常與to不定詞搭配使用，表達目的的含義。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;6. Kims_threads has yet to upload a pattern for the creation, though they might, as they sell several other patterns on her Etsy shop. &lt;br&gt;此句為一個“as”引導的時間狀語從句，主要表示動作發生的同時。本句也表示一個狀態，使用"have yet to"表達某件正在進行的事情。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;7. ...they used a tutorial from Popular Science as a baseline for their own creation.&lt;br&gt;標點符號的使用，可以使一個句子在語義上更加清晰。這裡的"..."表達了"（在可接受的範圍內）省略了一些信息"的意思。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;8. With some trial, error, and ingenuity, you could make your very own crochet DDR pad.&lt;br&gt;此句子利用了"With"的用法表達一個工具，後面則是表達了簡單的條件句，帶給讀者一個跨越差距，從"我不知道如何做到"，到"我也能創造這個產品"的感覺。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;9. Fun fact: crochet, unlike knitting, cannot be done by machines (yet).&lt;br&gt;本句作為提示或者引言，开头写有“Fun Fact”三个单词，表示此处是一个有趣的科普小知识。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;10. I'll believe the robot overlords are coming for us when they can crochet a DDR pad of their very own.&lt;br&gt;本句是一个表达条件的假设，一般借助于when, unless等引导词来表达，意思是“条件成立才能做到某事”。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;單字及提供（拆解後詞彙聯想）：&lt;br&gt;1. wizardry（n.) 魔術&lt;br&gt; wizard（n.) 巫師&lt;br&gt; weasel（n.) 黃鼠狼&lt;br&gt;2. conductive（adj.) 有導電性的&lt;br&gt; conduct（n.) 行為；舉止；導電&lt;br&gt;3. customize(v.) 定制&lt;br&gt; custom（n.) 風俗習慣；定制貨&lt;br&gt; costume（n.) 服裝&lt;br&gt;4. ingenuity(n.) 機智；創造力&lt;br&gt; genius（n.) 天才&lt;br&gt; genuine（adj.) 純真的&lt;br&gt;5. crochet（n./v.) 鉤編&lt;br&gt; crocodile（n.) 鱷魚&lt;br&gt; cricket（n.) 蟋蟀&lt;br&gt;6. enlarge(v.) 擴大&lt;br&gt; large(adj.) 巨大的&lt;br&gt; largely(adv.) 大部分地 &lt;br&gt;7. tutorial(n.) 教程&lt;br&gt; tutor（n.) 家庭教師&lt;br&gt;  tortoise（n.) 烏龜&lt;br&gt;8. footage(n.) 片段、影片&lt;br&gt; foot（n.) 腳、腳步&lt;br&gt; food（n.) 食物&lt;br&gt;9. cozy(adj.) 舒適的&lt;br&gt; cosy (英國英語) &lt;br&gt; cozy up cuddle/cosy down sleep  (phrasal verb) 癱坐著溫馨地相擁/舒適下降睡覺&lt;br&gt;10. functional(adj.) 功能性的&lt;br&gt; function(v.) 運作、運轉&lt;br&gt; finale(n.) 終曲、結局&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;片語（相似及反義片語）：&lt;br&gt;1. dance away - 相似片語：搖滾離去、收拾好離開；反義片語：無欲无求、毫無動力 &lt;br&gt;2. by + Ving - 相似片語：by chance（偶然地）, by design（故意）、by + N（by bike）（搭乘...）&lt;br&gt;3. would + Vr. - 相似片語：could + Vr.(能夠)、should +Vr. (應該)、may + Vr.（可能）&lt;br&gt;4. sell + N - 相似片語：sale + N、Sell out （售空）、sell to N（售給...）&lt;br&gt;5. so that - 相似片語：without + N (沒有...)、with + N (有...)&lt;br&gt;6. have yet to + V (尚未...) - 相似片語：be about to (就要...)、have already (已經...)&lt;br&gt;7. as...as... (和...一樣...) - 相似片語：not as...as... (不如...)&lt;br&gt;8. With + N - 相似片語：At +N(在...方面)，without+ N(忽略...), except +N (除了...)&lt;br&gt;9. unlike (不像) - 相似片語：just like（像...一樣), poor likeness (不像，還原度差)&lt;br&gt;10. when + S + V (當...) - 相似片語：if + S + V（如果...）, while + S + V (當...的時候)</content><link href="https://www.gamespot.com/articles/crochet-creator-crafts-functional-ddr-pad/1100-6513475/" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>