<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><id>https://github.com/weg38asyy/GameRss.git</id><title>My Game Rss</title><updated>2023-04-27T13:14:13.801718+00:00</updated><author><name>Koala</name><email>weg38asyy@gmail.com</email></author><link href="https://github.com/weg38asyy" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Personal learning of English use</subtitle><entry><id>https://www.gamespot.com/articles/star-wars-jedi-survivor-already-has-its-breakout-star/1100-6513613/</id><title>Star Wars Jedi: Survivor Already Has Its Breakout Star</title><updated>2023-04-27T13:14:13.801967+00:00</updated><content type="html">Even though Respawn's Star Wars Jedi: Survivor is still a few days away, the game already has a breakout star. And it's someone you'd never guess. &lt;br&gt; It was recently revealed that throughout your adventures in Jedi: Survivor, Cal runs into a frog-like alien named Turgle. They walk on two feet and look like a man if you stare at them long enough. It didn't take long for the Star Wars community to discover this hidden gem, and Lucy James took to Twitter to note how much of a star Turgle is. &lt;br&gt; You need a javascript enabled browser to watch videos. &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;        Want us to remember this setting for all your devices?&lt;br&gt;       &lt;br&gt; Sign up or Sign in now!&lt;br&gt;       &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;        By clicking 'enter', you agree to GameSpot's&lt;br&gt;                        Terms of Use and&lt;br&gt;        Privacy Policy &lt;br&gt; enter &lt;br&gt; Now Playing: Star Wars Jedi: Survivor Review - Fear Itself &lt;br&gt; In just the short time they've been introduced, Turgle has already received their own Wookieepedia page where you can look up everything you'll need to know about the new face of Star Wars. It would be nice to see a novel-length book further fleshing out they're story further down the line because someone as elegant as they definitely deserve it. &lt;br&gt; If you look up "Turgle" on Twitter, you'll see countless tweets of fans praising them and jokes about how they deserve to be the lead. A large reason fans may be obsessed with them is probably due to their powerful presence and the urge to protect them from anything that may harm them. Even other outlets, such as Prima Games, have taken the opportunity to give Turgle their own review to explain the impact they've had throughout the galaxy. &lt;br&gt; It's also worth noting that this isn't the first time Star Wars has introduced a cute alien that fans have fallen in love with. When season 1 of The Mandalorian first came out, much of the Star Wars fan base reacted similarly to seeing Baby Yoda, aka Grogu, for the first time. &lt;br&gt; Be sure to check out our Star Wars Jedi: Survivor review, where Jordan Ramée wrote: "Survivor builds on Fallen Order in several meaningful ways, tightening up the combat mechanics, expanding the variety of lightsaber styles, alleviating the frustration of platforming and puzzles, and digging into less-mainstream Star Wars lore to tell a fantastic story about a Jedi trying to defeat a tyrannical evil at all costs and coming to the realization that you can't just fight for good--you have to fight for good in the right way."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;詳細句子文法解析:&lt;br&gt;1. Even though 在這句話中表示雖然某件事情是真的，會用be動詞 "is" 承先啟後，後面多接跟著一個"but"的句子。這個片語用於轉換立場，更明確地表達於某種假設條件下結果如何。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. It's someone you'd never guess. 這句話是過去簡化式, 表示過去在一段時間或多次發生的個人或物品布達馬通常事物狀況. 此句中的'you'd'代表'you would', 也就是你本來不會想到的東西。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. where you can look up everything you'll need to know about the new face of Star Wars.此處you will need根據上下文解讀，具體含義為:所有新的Star Wars風貌(games，等）的知識和掌握可在他們的網頁上找到。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. It would be nice to see a novel-length book further fleshing out they're story.此處it would be nice to...，反映了發出此 statements 提到有關 Turgle 的更多相關信息是 令人欣喜的好主意。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. because someone as elegant as they definitely deserve it.此段落為定語從句，修飾緊跟在"someone"後面的名詞子句，以提供進一步的信息。"as...as"是打比方的常用用法，作為定語從句的使用頻率相對較高。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;6. that fans have fallen in love with.這是一個定語從句, which 闡述 這些星球大战粉丝喜欢的原因。fall in love 常用的慣用語，意為"喜歡上"。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;7. to seeing Baby Yoda, aka Grogu, for the first time.這句話使用縮寫"aka"，表示"亦稱"(in the way)。縮寫aka類似於中文解說文字的用法，以註釋時代指稱。"for the first time" 為時間副詞, 意為第一次.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;8. fighting for good in the right way."在這个句型中，巧妙地運用了分詞常常被用於猜測賓語在句子中的作用。'Fighting'是分詞，用作後面的宾语‘good’的定语短语，這個句型有時包括「for + 行動動詞 + 消息化賓語」的完整用法，通常用于表达某些想要通过某种方式提高人姓的行動。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;9. Be sure to check out our Star Wars Jedi: Survivor review.這句話用了一个不定式结构，To check out means ‘to have a look', 在该句型中,该习语充当了完整的结果句.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;10. where Jordan Ramée wrote.在这个句中用了定语从句whrtere+主谓谓语，修饰前面的已确定星球大战的描述.‘where’在这里指代主语“Jordan Ramée”的位置。 &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;單字:&lt;br&gt;1. adventures 冒險(n.) / icaltition 好的(n.) &lt;br&gt;2. reveal 透露(v.) /akiraka ni suruに 形成形式 基本形&lt;br&gt;3. throughout 自始自終 (ad.) / zentai 身體(n.)to te chintai 全部人&lt;br&gt;4. gem寶石(n.) /houseki 寶石(n.)&lt;br&gt;5. powerful强大的(adj.) /Tsuyoi 強い(adj.)&lt;br&gt;6. elegant高雅的(adj.) / Yuga-na 優雅な(adj..)&lt;br&gt;7. obsession著迷(n.) / kanchigai偏見(n.)&lt;br&gt;8. impact影響(n.) / kage影(n.)&lt;br&gt;9. defeat擊敗(v.) /haiboku惡消平(n.)&lt;br&gt;10.costscom全部所需付款(n.) /giyoukyu緊急添加(n.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;單字記憶方式:&lt;br&gt;1. adventures--('Ad'飆高音'vengers')--從 'Avengers' 劇集想起幾位英雄比賽誰能勝出， 勝者將是新一期冒險之旅的冠軍&lt;br&gt;2. reveal--('ray'與female ='L'形')--開啟全光線， 她的全身光芒點亮，最後形成"L" type讓本来的秘密暴露了&lt;br&gt;3. throughout--('through'穿過牆壁+'out'外面強調)=始終--他一路從內向外經年來一直走穿著這道牆：從“through”內的腦袋，“out”到強調的「外面」&lt;br&gt;4. gem--('綠寶石'=turquoise)--有一英俊騎士王子與巨龍進了劇場，他 揭露 他世代受到毒蜥蜴的夢幻項鏈"turquoise"是 救了整個星球的 '寶石'&lt;br&gt;5. powerful--('床舖fort'+ 'full充滿的'='powerful')--睡在充滿 投射八路多面 保護物的床 fort ，會有內心强大的 'powerful'習性 &lt;br&gt;6. elegant--('音樂box'+ 'gant褔利'='elegant)--音樂盒开启蓋子，聽听他伴随著珠宝小提琴声和丰饶的音效跳舞的慷慨动人的提琴手，让他的演奏氣質(HI)显得尤为 'Elegant'&lt;br&gt;7. obsession--('蘋果'='pon)&amp;('台中'='Obsession 絲巴達')-- 以前他總是 ispon,現在已是台中(社會名流)的激情 'Obsession'的男人&lt;br&gt;8. impact--('immediately'='impact'激烈的動作) immediately 暗示着瞬间的冲击力,毀滅性的 'impact'效應  &lt;br&gt;9. defeat--('大家勝利'=v &amp;..'defeat'=Ha! Bad luck')--整个碼頭都為 ‘v’喊贏了贏家,除了一個非常嚴格的裁判 laugh 了一下 “Ha”--- 'defeat' &lt;br&gt;10. costs--('模憶解放'='costs')-- 擺脫控制和 'costs'（price），開始释放内在的自我。</content><link href="https://www.gamespot.com/articles/star-wars-jedi-survivor-already-has-its-breakout-star/1100-6513613/" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>