<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><id>https://github.com/weg38asyy/GameRss.git</id><title>My Game Rss</title><updated>2023-04-09T13:10:39.575349+00:00</updated><author><name>Koala</name><email>weg38asyy@gmail.com</email></author><link href="https://github.com/weg38asyy" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Personal learning of English use</subtitle><entry><id>https://www.gamespot.com/articles/zelda-breath-of-the-wild-adds-online-co-op-with-new-mod/1100-6513088/</id><title>Zelda: Breath Of The Wild Adds Online Co-Op With New Mod</title><updated>2023-04-09T13:10:39.575485+00:00</updated><content type="html">You can now play The Legend of Zelda: Breath of The Wild online with your friends thanks to modders hired by content creator PointCrow. &lt;br&gt; This mod has been nearly two years in the making. Back in November of 2021, PointCrow posted on Twitter that they wanted someone to create this mod and offered a "$10,000 bounty" to whoever created one. &lt;br&gt; I'M PUTTING A $10,000 BOUNTY ON THE CREATION OF A BREATH OF THE WILD MULTIPLAYER MODterms &amp; conditions read here: https://t.co/oOfIbZQQTa #breathofthewild #botw #zelda pic.twitter.com/e287bFE740 &lt;br&gt; On April 4, 2023, the mod was officially released. The mod allows you to play through the entire game with your friends. But you can also play PVP to see who's the better player. To download the mod, you'll need to join PointCrows Discord server and click on -Mod-Downloads, leading you to a Google Doc explaining how to install it. As always, you should be mindful of what you download online. &lt;br&gt; It didn't take long for fans to run wild with the mod. One TikTok video shows 18 players running around in a single server. &lt;br&gt; PointCrow subsequently announced that their YouTube channel was struck by copyright infringement claims by Nintendo a few days after the mod was released. "Incredibly disappointed that [Nintendo] has decided to block my videos on Breath of the Wild," the tweet reads. "It's the love for the community and the innovation that we bring to it that has kept it alive &amp; brought new people to love the Zelda series. I hope you reverse your decision soon." &lt;br&gt; Incredibly disappointed that @NintendoAmerica has decided to block my videos on Breath of the Wild. It’s the love for the community and the innovation that we bring to it that has kept it alive &amp; brought new people to love the Zelda series. I hope you reverse your decision soon. pic.twitter.com/CtvjpmBrs3 &lt;br&gt; For more Zelda news, be sure to check our coverage on The Legend Of Zelda: Tears Of The Kingdom preorders to help you secure exclusive items.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;詳細句子文法解析：&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. "You can now play The Legend of Zelda: Breath of The Wild online with your friends thanks to modders hired by content creator PointCrow." &lt;br&gt;- 這個句子是由 "You can now play [...] with your friends" 構成，表示現在你可以和朋友一起玩 Zelda 的 Breath of the Wild，也因為 modders 的參與才可能實現這個功能。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. "Back in November of 2021, PointCrow posted on Twitter that they wanted someone to create this mod and offered a "$10,000 bounty" to whoever created one."&lt;br&gt;- "Back in November of 2021" 是表示時間點，使用的是過去式，指的是過去的事情。&lt;br&gt;- "that they wanted someone to create this mod" 中的 "that" 是一個關代詞，用來引導一個子句，這個子句用來說明他們想要製作一個 mod。&lt;br&gt;- "and offered a "$10,000 bounty" to whoever created one" 是另外一個子句，用來說明他們提供懸賞金額給哪個程式設計師。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. "On April 4, 2023, the mod was officially released."&lt;br&gt;- "On April 4, 2023" 是表示時間點，在這個句子裡使用了 on 來表示是在那一天。&lt;br&gt;- "the mod was officially released" 是一個被動句，指的是這個 mod 被釋出。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. "But you can also play PVP to see who's the better player."&lt;br&gt;- "But" 是一個轉折詞，用來轉折前後兩個句子，表示相對的意思。&lt;br&gt;- "to see who's the better player" 是一個動詞不定式短語，用來表示這個 PVP 模式的目的，也就是用來比較誰比較厲害。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. "It didn't take long for fans to run wild with the mod."&lt;br&gt;- "It didn't take long" 是用過去時態表示已經發生過的事情。&lt;br&gt;- "for fans to run wild with the mod" 是指這個 mod 很快就被玩家使用並且很受歡迎。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;單字：&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. multiplayer (n.) - 多人遊戲&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;日文：マルチプレイヤー (maruchipureiyā)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. modders (n.) - 模組製作者&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;日文：モッダー (moddā)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. bounty (n.) - 懸賞金&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;日文：賞金 (shōkin)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. server (n.) - 伺服器&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;日文：サーバー (sābā)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. PVP (n.) - 玩家對玩家模式&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;日文：PVP （ピーブイピー）(pī bui pī)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;6. copyright infringement (n.) - 侵犯版權&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;日文：著作権侵害 (chosakuken shinai)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;7. innovation (n.) - 創新&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;日文：革新 (kakushin)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;8. coverage (n.) - 報導&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;日文：報道 (hōdō)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;9. exclusive (adj.) - 獨家的&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;日文：独占的 (dokuzen-teki)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;10. install (v.) - 安裝&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;日文：インストール (insutōru)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;片語：&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. run wild - 恣意妄為; 任意發揮&lt;br&gt;- 相似片語：run riot，run amok&lt;br&gt;- 反義片語：behave well，behave decently&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. as always - 照慣例&lt;br&gt;- 相似片語：as usual, as customary&lt;br&gt;- 反義片語：anomalously, untypically&lt;br&gt;</content><link href="https://www.gamespot.com/articles/zelda-breath-of-the-wild-adds-online-co-op-with-new-mod/1100-6513088/" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>