<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><id>https://github.com/weg38asyy/GameRss.git</id><title>My Game Rss</title><updated>2023-06-27T13:11:43.627458+00:00</updated><author><name>Koala</name><email>weg38asyy@gmail.com</email></author><link href="https://github.com/weg38asyy" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Personal learning of English use</subtitle><entry><id>https://www.gamespot.com/articles/get-7-highly-rated-steam-games-for-only-10/1100-6515493/</id><title>Get 7 Highly Rated Steam Games For Only $10</title><updated>2023-06-27T13:11:43.627773+00:00</updated><content type="html">Fanatical's build-your-own Trinity Bundle Summer Edition deal is now live. Like other Fanatical DIY bundles, this special offer lets you mix and match from a list of games so you get exactly what you want. &lt;br&gt; The Trinity Bundle comes in three pricing tiers, starting with a three-game bundle for $5, and moving up to five games for $8, or seven games for $10. The $10 bundle offers the best value, but all three options get you a stack of discounted games. &lt;br&gt; As for the titles you can pick from, there are action-platformer metroidvanias like Iconoclasts, rogue-lite RPGs like Deepspace Derelicts and For the King, and the retro-style FPS Dusk. &lt;br&gt; The list also includes the wacky physics platformer Human: Fall Flat, which is a blast to play with friends, and the first-person deep-space survival game Breathedge. You can check out the full list of games on offer below, or over at Fanatical. &lt;br&gt; All Trinity Bundles also come with a 5%-off coupon you can apply to future Fanatical purchases. That extra coupon could come in handy with Fanatical's massive ongoing Red Hot Sale, which includes over 7,500 discounted PC games. If you spend more than $12 on your total order, you'll get a free game or additional coupon via a digital scratchcard. &lt;br&gt; Disclosure: GameSpot and Fanatical are both owned by Fandom. &lt;br&gt; Best Gaming &amp; Tech Deals This Week&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;詳細句子文法解析：&lt;br&gt;1. "Fanatical's build-your-own Trinity Bundle Summer Edition deal is now live." (現在 Fanatical 推出了 Trinity Bundle 夏季版。) 這是一個主動語態的句子，主詞是 Fanatical，動詞是 build，它的後面有一個形容詞子句作為定語修飾 Trinity Bundle。&lt;br&gt;2. "Like other Fanatical DIY bundles, this special offer lets you mix and match from a list of games so you get exactly what you want." (類似於其他 Fanatical 的 DIY 包，這個特別優惠讓你從一個遊戲清單中自由搭配，以便得到你想要的東西。) 這是一個由 like 引導的比較句，說明 Trinity Bundle 特別優惠與其他 Fanatical DIY bundles 的相似之處。主詞是 this special offer，讓 (lets) 是動詞，這個句子還有一個關係代詞 that 引導的疊詞，作為 "mix and match" 的補語。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. "The Trinity Bundle comes in three pricing tiers, starting with a three-game bundle for $5, and moving up to five games for $8, or seven games for $10." (Trinity Bundle 有三種不同的價格檔次，從 $5 的三款遊戲捆綁包起，到 $8 的五款遊戲捆綁包，最便宜的是 $10 的七款遊戲捆綁包。) 這個句子是一個複合句，主要粱是 Trinity Bundle，動詞是 come，還有一個以 -ing 結尾的分詞片語作為修飾。這個句子講述 Trinity Bundle 有什麼特殊優惠、以及在不同價格檔次下，你可以得到哪些遊戲。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. "The list also includes the wacky physics platformer Human: Fall Flat, which is a blast to play with friends, and the first-person deep-space survival game Breathedge." (遊戲清單還包括花式物理平台遊戲《Human: Fall Flat》，和第一人稱深空生存遊戲《Breathedge》。 ) 這是一個包含兩個形容詞子句的複合句，由 "The list also includes" 開始，動詞是 includes，從句中提到的遊戲名稱起到了形容詞的作用，更加生動地講述了這個清單包括哪些遊戲。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. "You can check out the full list of games on offer below, or over at Fanatical." (你可以在下方或者 Fanatical 上查看完整的遊戲清單。) 這個由主、謂、賓、表四要素組成的簡單句，明確地告訴閱讀者可以下方查看完整遊戲清單。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;6. "All Trinity Bundles also come with a 5%-off coupon you can apply to future Fanatical purchases." (所有 Trinity Bundle 都附帶一張5％的折扣券，你可以在未來的 Fanatical 購物中使用。) 這是一個由 also 引導的複合句，主詞是 All Trinity Bundles，動詞是 come，還有一個宾语从句修飾，描述折扣券的用途。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;7. "That extra coupon could come in handy with Fanatical's massive ongoing Red Hot Sale, which includes over 7,500 discounted PC games." (這張额外的優惠券可能在 Fanatical 正在進行的大型促銷活動中派得上用場，其中包括超過7,500款折扣 PC 游戏。) 這個複合句由 which 引導，主句講述的是優惠券的用途，從句描述了促銷活動的內容。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;8. "If you spend more than $12 on your total order, you'll get a free game or additional coupon via a digital scratchcard." (如果你的訂單總額超過了 $12，则可以通過數字刮刮卡免費獲得一款游戲或额外的优惠券。) 這是一個包含主、從、賓、狀四要素的條件句，以 if 引導，副詞子句是 "If you spend more than $12 on your total order"，主詞是 you，從屬詞 spend，動詞是 get，它后面有一個宾语，即免费游戏或额外优惠券。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;9. "Disclosure: GameSpot and Fanatical are both owned by Fandom." (敝公司擁有 GameSpot 和 Fanatical 這兩個品牌。) 這句话由大写字母开头并使用了冒号，说明这是一个公告或声明。动词是 owned，被体这儿主语是 GameSpot 和 Fanatical，它们被提到的环境是 "owned by Fandom。”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;10. "Best Gaming &amp; Tech Deals This Week" (本週最佳游戲和科技交易)。这是一个簡短的名詞短語，由主、定两部分组成。该短语的主语是 deals，定語是 Best Gaming &amp; Tech。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;單字：&lt;br&gt;1. bundle - 捆綁包，建議學生可以把它拆成 bun + dle 學習。日語翻譯：異なる（bundle）&lt;br&gt;2. platformer - 平台遊戲，platformer 的消息等效為“遊戲”，減少單字量。日語翻譯：プラットフォーマー（purattofomaa）&lt;br&gt;3. metroidvania - 管列变种遊戲，這个詞是合成詞，由 Metroid 和 Castlevania 两个游戏名称组成，比喻類型。&lt;br&gt;4. rogue-lite - 罪犯輕鬆類型的 RPG 遊戲，這個短語是由滲透 / 目標和暴力遊戲或模擬器組成的。日語翻譯：ローグライト（rooga raito） &lt;br&gt;5. physics - 物理学，學說明確，和平台遊戲搭配瞭解其用途。日語翻譯：物理 （butsuri） &lt;br&gt;6. survival - 生存遊戲，字面意思，容易讓人聯想到遊戲內容主題。&lt;br&gt;7. discounted - 折扣的，dis- 是一個否定前缀。Day one buyers can pay the sticker price（第一天的購買者必須支付標籤價格），discounted price（折扣價格）。&lt;br&gt;8. promotion - 促銷活動，這是一個簡單易懂的單詞，建議同學使用書法記憶法深刻記憶它。日語翻譯：プロモート（puromooto）&lt;br&gt;9. various - 各種各樣的，指的是多种分类，类似混合词。this sketch has coined the term unboxed beef（這次草擬提出了“野外牛肉”的概念）。&lt;br&gt;10. blast - 極棒的，表示非常高興的意思，例如：I had a blast（我过得很愉快）。日語翻譯：ブラスト（burasuto）&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;片語：&lt;br&gt;1. mix and match - 搭配使用&lt;br&gt;2. get exactly what you want - 得到你想要的東西&lt;br&gt;3. come in - 进入（采取）&lt;br&gt;4. start with - 以...开始&lt;br&gt;5. moving up to - 逐渐过渡到&lt;br&gt;6. in handy - 有用&lt;br&gt;7. best value - 最好的价值&lt;br&gt;8. check out - 查看&lt;br&gt;9. on offer - 在推出&lt;br&gt;10. scratch card - 刮刮乐卡&lt;br&gt;相似片語：scratch the surface（略懂...），get the ball rolling（开始)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;反義片語： &lt;br&gt;1. come undone - 失败、破坏（成果）&lt;br&gt;2. fall apart - 瓦解；崩溃&lt;br&gt;3. break down - 损坏；崩溃&lt;br&gt;4. go wrong - 出毛病&lt;br&gt;5. lose oneself - 迷路、混乱。&lt;br&gt;6. kill two birds with one stone - 一箭双雕&lt;br&gt;7. win something for a song - 半价购买&lt;br&gt;8. come to get used to - 开始适应&lt;br&gt;9. in the way - 挡道&lt;br&gt;10. speak one's mind - 直言不讳。</content><link href="https://www.gamespot.com/articles/get-7-highly-rated-steam-games-for-only-10/1100-6515493/" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>