<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><id>https://github.com/weg38asyy/GameRss.git</id><title>My Game Rss</title><updated>2023-03-27T17:50:00.518337+00:00</updated><author><name>Koala</name><email>weg38asyy@gmail.com</email></author><link href="https://github.com/weg38asyy" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Personal learning of English use</subtitle><entry><id>https://www.gamespot.com/articles/former-forza-horizon-studio-head-starts-new-studio-lighthouse-games/1100-6512726/</id><title>Former Forza Horizon Studio Head Starts New Studio Lighthouse Games</title><updated>2023-03-27T17:50:00.518636+00:00</updated><content type="html">Former founder and studio head of Forza Horizon developer Playground Games, Gavin Raeburn, has started a new AAA studio called Lighthouse Games. The studio is based in Leamington Spa and currently working on an unannounced IP. Lighthouse Games is composed of other former Playground Games veterans such as director Nick Wheelwright and creative director Jon Davis-Hunt. “I’m delighted that 30 former colleagues and other industry heavyweights have chosen to join me at Lighthouse. With Horizon, Playground and I created one of the most successful Xbox franchises of all time," Raeburn explained in a statement. He continued: "We delivered significant commercial success year after year, to massive critical acclaim following the success from my time at Codemasters leading Dirt, Grid, and F1. That DNA is now at Lighthouse, and with it, we intend to build something truly special using all our experience to create a new genre-defining franchise.” As the team is currently working on its first game, it is also looking to hire for open positions including lead-level designer and senior online engineer. There have been many new studios being formed lately by veterans from big studios including former Need for Speed developers at Fuse Games and former Apex Legends developers at Wildlight Entertainment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;詳細句子文法解析：&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. "Former founder and studio head of Forza Horizon developer Playground Games, Gavin Raeburn, has started a new AAA studio called Lighthouse Games." (past participle phrase)&lt;br&gt; → 用作主詞的過去分詞組，這裡是形容 Gavin Raeburn 的過去經歷以及他成立了新公司的事實。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. "The studio is based in Leamington Spa and currently working on an unannounced IP." (present progressive tense)&lt;br&gt; →目前進行式時態，指一個正在進行中的動作，這裡表示 Lighthouse Games 目前正在進行創作但尚未公佈詳細情報。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. "Lighthouse Games is composed of other former Playground Games veterans such as director Nick Wheelwright and creative director Jon Davis-Hunt." (passive voice)&lt;br&gt; → 被動語態，這裡表示 Lighthouse Games 的成員由We are currently members of Lighthouse Games were composed of other former Playground Games veterans。Playground Games的前成員組成。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. "There have been many new studios being formed lately by veterans from big studios including former Need for Speed developers at Fuse Games and former Apex Legends developers at Wildlight Entertainment." (present perfect continuous tense)&lt;br&gt;→現在完成進行式時態，表示一個現在還在進行的動作開始於一段時間前，這裡是指近期有許多由之前大型遊戲公司的資深成員所成立的新工作室。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;單字：&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. founder (n.) - 創辦人，創立者；成立者&lt;br&gt;2. veteran (n.) - 資深成員，老手；退伍軍人&lt;br&gt;3. franchise (n.) - 特許經營權；連鎖店；特別授權&lt;br&gt;4. acclaim (n./v.) - 喝彩，讚賞，稱讚&lt;br&gt;5. DNA (n.) -  (生命) 遺傳物質；基因組&lt;br&gt;6. intend (v.) - 打算，計畫；意圖；企圖&lt;br&gt;7. genre (n.) - 風格，流派；類型；型式&lt;br&gt;8. unannounced (adj.) - 未公布的，未宣布的&lt;br&gt;9. commence (v.) - 開始，開辦；著手&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;中文容易記住方法：&lt;br&gt;1. founder(創辦人) - 把 founder 分解為 found(發現) 以及 er(-er則為人)，既代表是「發掘和創建某事的人」。&lt;br&gt;2. veteran(資深成員) - 聯想到退伍軍人，意思是有許多經驗和技能。&lt;br&gt;3. franchise(特許經營權) - 發音比較接近法國的「法蘭西斯」，且其中有單字的法文「chise」，可聯想到「與資方有關的權利」。&lt;br&gt;4. acclaim(讚賞，稱讚) - 中文翻譯為「喝采聲」，由此聯想到聽到錄音時的觀眾叫喊聲，表示熱烈的讚揚和喜歡。&lt;br&gt;5. DNA(遺傳物質；基因組) - 聯想到電影或書中的偵探小說有「DNA檢驗」這個詞，是透過身體的遺傳物質找出嫌疑人的線索，因此可以聯想到這個單字所代表的意思。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;諧音方法:&lt;br&gt;6. intend (v.) - 我們考慮 "in-tendency"  (升起的傾向，即準備行動的傾向)。 "In-tend" 發音與 "intend" 類似。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;相似片語:&lt;br&gt;Thesaurus: aim, plan, design, contemplate, have in view, have in mind, propose, purpose。&lt;br&gt;反義片語：&lt;br&gt;無相反字義。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;日文對應單字：&lt;br&gt;1. founder - 創業者（創業者 ）&lt;br&gt;2. veteran - 老練なメンバー（老練的團隊成員）&lt;br&gt;3. franchise - フランチャイズ（特許經營，授權經營權）&lt;br&gt;4. acclaim - 賞賛（表揚，高度評価）&lt;br&gt;5. DNA - DNA（DNA ）&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;其他：&lt;br&gt;1. Lighthouse Games 是由 Forza Horizon 開發商 Playground Games 的前員工組成。&lt;br&gt;2. Lighthouse Games 正在進行創作但尚未公佈詳細情報，旨在創建一個煥然一新的遊戲大作。&lt;br&gt;3. 許多之前開發者從大型的遊戲公司出走開創新的工作室也開始變得非常普及。&lt;br&gt;4. Lighthouse Games 現正招聘領導級設計師和資深現場工程師等高級職位。</content><link href="https://www.gamespot.com/articles/former-forza-horizon-studio-head-starts-new-studio-lighthouse-games/1100-6512726/" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>