<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><id>https://github.com/weg38asyy/GameRss.git</id><title>My Game Rss</title><updated>2023-03-22T17:28:34.207846+00:00</updated><author><name>Koala</name><email>weg38asyy@gmail.com</email></author><link href="https://github.com/weg38asyy" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Personal learning of English use</subtitle><entry><id>https://www.gamespot.com/articles/new-hobbit-illustrated-edition-includes-50-drawings-and-maps-from-tolkien-himself/1100-6512596/</id><title>New Hobbit Illustrated Edition Includes 50+ Drawings And Maps From Tolkien Himself</title><updated>2023-03-22T17:28:34.208310+00:00</updated><content>A new illustrated edition of J.R.R. Tolkien's The Hobbit has been announced, and it is packed with enough new material to convince fans to buy yet another copy of the classic fantasy book. As revealed by IGN, HarperCollins has announced a new edition of the book that comes with more than 50 sketches, drawings, paintings, and maps from Tolkien himself. It releases on September 19, and you can order a copy through Amazon. The book includes a forward by the late Christopher Tolkien, as well as further notes from Tolkien scholars Wayne G. Hammond and Christina Scull. Head to IGN to see some photos from the book ahead of its release in September.   The release of the new illustrated edition of The Hobbit follows similar illustrated versions of The Lord of the Rings and The Silmarillion, which are currently available to buy at book stores. The Hobbit was published in September 1937. It tells the story of the unassuming hobbit Bilbo Baggins who embarks upon a grand adventure and obtains the One Ring. The book was made into a trilogy of films from Peter Jackson, which together earned billions at the box office. Tolkien followed up The Hobbit with the heavier and more intensely dramatic The Lord of the Rings book series, which Jackson also adapted for a trilogy of Oscar-winning films. In other Lord of the Rings news, Cirian Hinds has joined the cast of The Rings of Power Season 2, while New Line is planning more Lord of the Rings films. There are also five more Lord of the Rings video games set for release in the next two years. 


詳細句子文法解析：

1. "A new illustrated edition of J.R.R. Tolkien's The Hobbit has been announced"。
   句型：主詞+動詞+過去分詞+句子補語。
   解析：Announce為及物動詞，它的受詞是"A new illustrated edition of J.R.R. Tolkien's The Hobbit"，過去分詞"announced"表示完成時態，"has been"是現在完成式的被動態，意指在過去一段時間內，宣布了一個新的插畫版欣賞，由此可知本句落點在強調書籍新版本的推出。

2. "HarperCollins has announced a new edition of the book that comes with more than 50 sketches, drawings, paintings, and maps from Tolkien himself."
   句型：主詞+動詞+宾语从句。
   解析：句子主落在書籍的內容，而announce（宣布）為及物動詞，在此主詞"HarperCollins"，其宾语从句"that comes with more than 50 sketches, drawings, paintings, and maps from Tolkien himself"表示這次新版欣賞內容的內容。

3. "The book includes a forward by the late Christopher Tolkien, as well as further notes from Tolkien scholars Wayne G. Hammond and Christina Scull."
   句型：主詞+動詞+从句。
   解析：句子主詞仍是"The book"，動詞為"includes"，含有"As well as"的从句表示新版本里書中，更內容增加了一個富有意義的前言和更多的筆記。

4. "The release of the new illustrated edition of The Hobbit follows similar illustrated versions of The Lord of the Rings and The Silmarillion."
   句型：主詞+動詞+品質的從句。
   解析：此句強調的是喬治．R．R．托爾金的不同版本的相似性，及要充分利用此版本的內容，故使用了"follows" (類似於) 以及"As well as"作為类型從句的引入。

5. "In other Lord of the Rings news, Cirian Hinds has joined the cast of The Rings of Power Season 2, while New Line is planning more Lord of the Rings films."
   句型：分詞+分號+分詞。
   解析：此句強調不屬於主軸、次要的相關內容談起，使用分詞構成附加的關於同一主題的內容。

單字：
illustrated   [ˈɪləstreɪtɪd]   adj. 有插圖的
edition   [ɪˈdɪʃn]             n. 版本

片語：
Come with   搭配，附帶

其它：
1. illustrated 可以聯想成"Illust"，比如「插圖、圖版、美圖」都能叫做"Illust Beauty "。
2. edition為「版」，聯想可參考“掐表歸正Ⅷ”。日文版：版(van)
3. similar illustrated versions of... 可以聯想相小的版本，是「minoriously illustrated」，其反义詞是「heavily illustrated」. 日文：小さく載った、 weightlessly illustrated &amp; たっぷり載った、heavily illustrated
4. come with意為「伴隨、附帶」，密码联想「铠甫美」，也就是伴随美好的配戴。日文片语「付き合う（つきあう）」表示伴随相关的涵义。</content><link href="https://www.gamespot.com/articles/new-hobbit-illustrated-edition-includes-50-drawings-and-maps-from-tolkien-himself/1100-6512596/" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>