<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><id>https://github.com/weg38asyy/GameRss.git</id><title>My Game Rss</title><updated>2023-04-12T13:10:55.781733+00:00</updated><author><name>Koala</name><email>weg38asyy@gmail.com</email></author><link href="https://github.com/weg38asyy" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Personal learning of English use</subtitle><entry><id>https://www.gamespot.com/articles/dead-island-2-preorders-bonuses-and-collectors-edition-still-available/1100-6506859/</id><title>Dead Island 2 Preorders - Bonuses And Collector's Edition Still Available</title><updated>2023-04-12T13:10:55.782008+00:00</updated><content type="html">After more than a decade of waiting, Dead Island fans are so close to getting their hands on the sequel. Dead Island 2 releases on April 21 for PS5, PS4, Xbox Series X|S, Xbox, and PC. If you're looking forward to slaying hundreds of zombies,  multiple editions of Dead Island 2 are available to preorder.  At this time,  the priciest edition--the Hell-A edition--is still available to preorder  for $100. And regardless of which edition or platform you pick, you'll score some preorder bonuses by ordering early. &lt;br&gt;   &lt;br&gt; All Dead Island 2 preorders come with the Memories of Banoi Pack, which includes the Banoi War Club, Memories of Banoi Baseball Bat, a Balanced Weapon Perk, and Personal Space Skill Card.  &lt;br&gt; If you want a physical edition, your best bet is to  preorder Dead Island 2 from Best Buy.  The retailer is giving away an exclusive steelbook case, shown above, with all preorders. &lt;br&gt;   &lt;br&gt; The standard edition of Dead Island 2 is also called the "Day One Edition" for physical copies (at least at launch), but they’re essentially the same thing. You’ll get the base game along with any eligible preorder bonuses. &lt;br&gt; It's worth noting that there are three different disc versions: PS5, PS4, and Xbox. Like many other game releases, the Xbox version comes with both the Series X and Xbox One editions. PlayStation is a bit more complicated. The PS4 disc also comes with the PS5 version, while the PS5 disc only works on PS5. Regardless of which platform you choose, the standard edition of Dead Island 2 costs $70. &lt;br&gt;   &lt;br&gt; As an alternative to the Day 1 edition, there's the Pulp edition. Weirdly enough, this edition also costs $70. The only difference here is that you also get the Pulp Weapons Pack (on top of the regular preorder bonuses). &lt;br&gt; The Pulp edition comes with the base game, any eligible preorder bonuses, and the Pulp Weapons Pack--which is filled with digital goodies. This version is only available in physical formats. &lt;br&gt; Step up to the digital-only Deluxe edition and you’ll get the Golden Weapons Pack and Character Pack 1 &amp; 2. These offer some in-game goodies to help jumpstart your zombie-slaying career. &lt;br&gt; The Dead Island 2 Gold Edition clocks in at $90, but you’re getting a lot of content for the price. Here’s a closer look at everything it offers: &lt;br&gt; The Hell-A Edition is essentially the collector’s edition of Dead Island 2. It includes everything found in the Gold Edition, along with a steelbook case and collectible items. These collectibles include: &lt;br&gt; Yes, that means you'll get two steelbook cases if you preorder this edition from Best Buy &lt;br&gt;  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;句子文法解析：&lt;br&gt;1. "If you're looking forward to slaying hundreds of zombies, multiple editions of Dead Island 2 are available to preorder." &lt;br&gt;此句為條件句，使用 present continuous (are available)，強調現在正在發生的事情，並使用 future tense (will be) 預測未來可能發生的情況。&lt;br&gt;2. "The standard edition of Dead Island 2 is also called the 'Day One Edition' for physical copies (at least at launch), but they’re essentially the same thing." 此句中，使用 also called 強調標準版和首發版等價。&lt;br&gt;3. "Like many other game releases, the Xbox version comes with both the Series X and Xbox One editions." 此處使用配對(conjunction)技巧，將兩個單詞 Series X 和 Xbox One 連起來用同樣落款範本，使其看起來像是同一個東西。&lt;br&gt;4. "Step up to the digital-only Deluxe edition and you’ll get the Golden Weapons Pack and Character Pack 1 &amp; 2."此句中，使用了縮寫來表達版本型號。Deluxe edition 縮寫為 "DLX"，Character 縮寫為 "Char"。&lt;br&gt;5. "The Dead Island 2 Gold Edition clocks in at $90, but you’re getting a lot of content for the price."此句中的 "clocks in at" 強調了價格的固定和明確，並使用 "getting" 表示價值，意為買到的內容值得這個價格。&lt;br&gt;6. "Yes, that means you'll get two steelbook cases if you preorder this edition from Best Buy."此句中，使用 "that means" 來強調前文所述之兩個鋼匣子的內涵。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;單字：&lt;br&gt;preorder - 預購 (初學者可能會誤以為是"預估")&lt;br&gt;eligible - 有資格的&lt;br&gt;zombie - 殭屍 (中文”亡者”也可作為聯想)&lt;br&gt;edition - 版本&lt;br&gt;slay - 屠殺&lt;br&gt;physical - 實體的&lt;br&gt;content - 內容&lt;br&gt;steelbook - 鐵皮盒 (直譯成 "鋼皮書"可減少記憶負擔)&lt;br&gt;collectible - 收藏品&lt;br&gt;bonus - 獎勵，紅利&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;日文對應單字：&lt;br&gt;preorder - 予約 (よやく/yoyaku)&lt;br&gt;eligible - 資格のある (しかくのある/shikaku no aru)&lt;br&gt;zombie - ゾンビ (ぞんび/zonbi)&lt;br&gt;edition - 版 (ばん/ban)&lt;br&gt;slay - 虐殺する (ぎゃくさつする/gyakusatsu suru)&lt;br&gt;physical - 物理的な (ぶつりてきな/butsuriteki na)&lt;br&gt;content - 内容 (ないよう/naiyou)&lt;br&gt;steelbook - スチールブック (すちーるぶっく/suchiirubukku)&lt;br&gt;collectible - 収集品 (しゅうしゅうひん/shuushuu-hin)&lt;br&gt;bonus - ボーナス (ぼーなす/boonasu)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;片語：&lt;br&gt;preorder bonuses - 預購獎勵&lt;br&gt;Day One edition - 首日版&lt;br&gt;memory pack - 記憶力練習包&lt;br&gt;Golden Weapons Pack - 黃金武器包&lt;br&gt;Personal Space Skill Card - 個人空間技能卡&lt;br&gt;Balanced Weapon Perk - 平衡武器特典&lt;br&gt;Pulp Weapons Pack - 派克武器裝備包&lt;br&gt;jumpstart - 啟動&lt;br&gt;exclusive steelbook case - 獨有的鐵皮盒&lt;br&gt;Dead Island 2 releases - 死島2即將發行&lt;br&gt;preorders are available - 可以預購&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;相似片語：&lt;br&gt;regular bonuses - 常規獎勵；regular editions - 常規版本&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;反義片語：&lt;br&gt;physical vs digital - 實體版與數字版；standard vs collector’s edition - 標準版與珍藏版</content><link href="https://www.gamespot.com/articles/dead-island-2-preorders-bonuses-and-collectors-edition-still-available/1100-6506859/" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>