<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><id>https://github.com/weg38asyy/GameRss.git</id><title>My Game Rss</title><updated>2023-03-23T16:50:06.355498+00:00</updated><author><name>Koala</name><email>weg38asyy@gmail.com</email></author><link href="https://github.com/weg38asyy" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Personal learning of English use</subtitle><entry><id>https://www.gamespot.com/articles/super-mario-manga-suggests-that-1-up-mushrooms-are-grown-from-bodies-of-dead-marios/1100-6512646/</id><title>Super Mario Manga Suggests That 1-Up Mushrooms Are Grown From Bodies Of Dead Marios</title><updated>2023-03-23T16:50:06.355796+00:00</updated><content type="html">A 1-Up mushroom is an essential part of any Mario game, a literal pick-me-up in a fungal form that guarantees you an extra chance to complete a level. Green mushrooms that add a touch of resurrection to a Mario Bros. run, these power-ups are iconic and might harbor a dark secret that could rock Nintendo's mega-popular franchise to its very core. As noted by the Twitter account Super Mario Broth, a page from the Super Mario 64 manga all the way back in 1996 suggested that Mario was trapped in a grim cycle of eco-friendly life and death. Every Mario who died in the Mushroom Kingdom would eventually become one with the dirt, their bodies feeding the soil and producing 1-Up mushrooms that the next Mario could consume. This probably explains why a single 1-Up in Super Mario 64 was almost impossible to collect. A 1996 Super Mario 64 manga suggests that 1-Up Mushrooms grow from the bodies of dead Marios, perpetuating the cycle of life and death. pic.twitter.com/KjGsnig3hB Before an existential crisis about the state of Mario takes root, it's worth noting that this is just an interesting idea from the manga authors. "Please note that these mangas are filled with jokes and eccentric theories such as this," Super Mario Broth added. "This should be taken more as an interesting thought experiment than anything that would actually be endorsed by Nintendo!" As he heads to the big screen in his first animated feature film, April is shaping up to be a big month for Mario. Set for a Wednesday release on April 5, Super Mario Bros. is expected to pull in between $85 million-$90 million at the US box office over the Easter weekend. The film stars the voices of Chris Pratt as Mario, Charlie Day as his brother Luigi, Anya Taylor-Joy as Princess Peach, Seth Rogen as Donkey Kong, and Jack Black as Bowser.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;詳細句子文法解析：&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. A 1-Up mushroom is an essential part of any Mario game, a literal pick-me-up in a fungal form that guarantees you an extra chance to complete a level.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- "a literal pick-me-up"：詞性為名詞片語，用來形容「1-Up mushroom」，強調這顆蘑菇可以幫助玩家重新獲得生命。&lt;br&gt;- "in a fungal form"：詞性為介系詞片語，用來修飾「pick-me-up」，表示這顆蘑菇是形成蘑菇狀的。&lt;br&gt;- "guarantees you an extra chance to complete a level"：動詞片語，表示「1-Up mushroom」的功能，即可以在Mario的遊戲中給予一次額外的生命機會。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Green mushrooms that add a touch of resurrection to a Mario Bros. run, these power-ups are iconic and might harbor a dark secret that could rock Nintendo's mega-popular franchise to its very core.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- "that add a touch of resurrection to a Mario Bros. run"：定語子句，修飾「green mushrooms」，表示綠色蘑菇可以為Mario在遊戲中帶來一絲點活力。&lt;br&gt;- "these power-ups are iconic"：狀語子句，表示這些附帶能力的物品非常著名。&lt;br&gt;- "might harbor a dark secret that could rock Nintendo's mega-popular franchise to its very core"：主要句子，意為「可能會隱藏一個令Nintendo的非常著名品牌遭受打擊的深淵秘密」。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. As noted by the Twitter account Super Mario Broth, a page from the Super Mario 64 manga all the way back in 1996 suggested that Mario was trapped in a grim cycle of eco-friendly life and death.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- "As noted by the Twitter account Super Mario Broth"：分詞片語，用來引出文章的一些背景資料。&lt;br&gt;- "a page from the Super Mario 64 manga all the way back in 1996 suggested that Mario was trapped in a grim cycle of eco-friendly life and death"：主要句子，表示「1996年的Super Mario 64漫畫中的某一頁曾經建議馬力歐被困在一個黑暗的生與死的環境中」。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;單字：&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. resurrection：名詞，復活、復甦。（日文：蘇生、復活）&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;記憶方法：聯想「re-（重新）」以及「-surrection（起死回生）」。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. iconic：形容詞，代表性的、象徵性的。（日文：代表的）&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;記憶方法：聯想「ic-（像）」以及「-onic（音音樂）」，代表符號或形象。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. eco-friendly：形容詞，環保的。（日文：エコフレンドリー）&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;記憶方法：聯想「eco-（環保）」以及「-friendly（友好的）」，表示對環境友好的。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;片語：&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. pick-me-up：名詞片語，提振精神的事物，像是一個飲料、糖果或是其他的能量補充品。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;相似片語：stimulant、boost&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;反義片語：downer、depressor&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. life and death：名詞片語，生死、生命和死亡。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;相似片語：death and life、mortality&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;其它：&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. 此篇文章介紹了Mario遊戲中其中一種角色的起源，帶有一點幽默而且有趣。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. 課程主師可以引導學生閱讀雙語版本遊戲的劇情，以便提高他們的英文閱讀能力和了解有趣的文化知識。</content><link href="https://www.gamespot.com/articles/super-mario-manga-suggests-that-1-up-mushrooms-are-grown-from-bodies-of-dead-marios/1100-6512646/" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>