<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><id>https://github.com/weg38asyy/GameRss.git</id><title>My Game Rss</title><updated>2023-07-03T13:11:09.854016+00:00</updated><author><name>Koala</name><email>weg38asyy@gmail.com</email></author><link href="https://github.com/weg38asyy" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Personal learning of English use</subtitle><entry><id>https://www.gamespot.com/articles/disney-speedstorm-launches-in-full-later-this-year/1100-6515630/</id><title>Disney Speedstorm Launches In Full Later This Year</title><updated>2023-07-03T13:11:09.854269+00:00</updated><content type="html">Gameloft has announced that Disney Speedstorm is leaving early access and will be fully released later this year on September 28. &lt;br&gt; The game has been in early access since it was released in April, and new content has been added, which includes characters, race tracks, and more. &lt;br&gt; You need a javascript enabled browser to watch videos. &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;        Want us to remember this setting for all your devices?&lt;br&gt;       &lt;br&gt; Sign up or Sign in now!&lt;br&gt;       &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;        By clicking 'enter', you agree to GameSpot's&lt;br&gt;                        Terms of Use and&lt;br&gt;        Privacy Policy &lt;br&gt; enter &lt;br&gt; Now Playing: Disney Speedstorm - Launch Trailer &lt;br&gt; Disney Speedstorm is a kart racer where you play as popular Disney characters and race each other to the finish line. Similar to Mario Kart, each race track includes a variety of power-ups you can use to help give you the upper hand. From now until September 30, you can purchase the Founder's Pack for $30, that's on sale right now for 20% off for the next 10 days, which gives you exclusive content such as in-game currency, Mickey Mouse and Donald Duck as racers, and more. And when the game fully launches, it'll be free-to-play on the Xbox One, Xbox Series X|S, PlayStation 4, PlayStation 5, Nintendo Switch, and PC. &lt;br&gt; In our Disney Speedstorm preview, Steve Watts wrote, "While the first few hours of Disney Speedstorm are a raucous joyride, the leveled gating mechanics and confusing web of menus are a blinking 'check engine' light. It doesn't immediately spoil the fun, but it's definitely cause for alarm."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;詳細句子文法解析：&lt;br&gt;1. Gameloft has announced that Disney Speedstorm is leaving early access and will be fully released later this year on September 28.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;這個句子是一個簡單的陳述句，用於描述Gameloft宣布了Disney Speedstorm正在離開早期測試階段，並將在今年9月28日正式發行。"is leaving" 和 "will be fully released" 是將來進行式，用於描述將來發生的動作。重點是將來進行式的應用。&lt;br&gt;   &lt;br&gt;2. The game has been in early access since it was released in April, and new content has been added, which includes characters, race tracks, and more.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;這個句子中，"has been" 和 "has been added" 是現在完成進行式，用於描述從過去某個時間開始並持續到現在的動作，強調過去開始的時間點和繼續進行的時間長度。重點是現在完成進行式的用法。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. You need a javascript enabled browser to watch videos.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;這個句子是一個陳述句，用於表示觀看視頻需要一個啟用了javascript的瀏覽器。重點是使⽤動詞 "need" 表示需要某⽣以及形容詞 "enabled" 修飾名詞 "browser"。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. Want us to remember this setting for all your devices?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;這個句子是⼀個問題句，用於詢問是否希望記住此設置，以⽤於所✎有的設備。重點是 "want" + 名⩔ + 不定式結構的⽤法。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. Sign up or Sign in now!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;這個句子是⼀個命令句，表示現在要註冊或登錄⽤戶帳號。重點是對話中常⽤的命令句型。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;6. By clicking 'enter', you agree to GameSpot's Terms of Use and Privacy Policy.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;這個句子是⼀個陳述句，表示通過點擊"enter"按鈕，你同意遵守GameSpot的使用條款和隱私政策。重點是使⽤介詞短語 "by + V-ing" 表示通過某種⾏為發⽣的動作。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;7. Disney Speedstorm is a kart racer where you play as popular Disney characters and race each other to the finish line.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;這個句子是⼀個陳述句，描述了Disney Speedstorm是⼀款卡通賽車遊戲，玩家扮演受歡迎的迪斯尼角⾊，互相競賽直到抵達終點。重點是介紹這款遊戲的性質和目標。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;8. Similar to Mario Kart, each race track includes a variety of power-ups you can use to help give you the upper hand.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;這個句子是⼀個陳述句，表示與馬⾥奧賽車遊戲類似，每個賽道都包含各種道具，你可以使⽤它們來獲得優勢。重點是⽤ "similar to" 表達相似之處，以及動詞短語 "can use" 表⽰能夠使⽤的能⼒。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;9. From now until September 30, you can purchase the Founder's Pack for $30, that's on sale right now for 20% off for the next 10 days, which gives you exclusive content such as in-game currency, Mickey Mouse and Donald Duck as racers, and more.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;這個句子描述了一個時間段內的購物活動。重點是表述限定時間內的特價優惠以及介紹購買Founder's Pack所能獲得的獨家內容。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;10. And when the game fully launches, it'll be free-to-play on the Xbox One, Xbox Series X|S, PlayStation 4, PlayStation 5, Nintendo Switch, and PC.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;這個句子描述了遊戲正式發行後的價格。重點是表達遊戲正式發行後的價格政策。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;單字：&lt;br&gt;1. leaving (離開) - J: 出発する (shuppatsu suru)&lt;br&gt;2. early access (早期測試) - J: 早期アクセス (souki akusesu)&lt;br&gt;3. released (發行) - J: リリースされました (rirīsu sa remashita)&lt;br&gt;4. content (內容) - J: コンテンツ (kontentsu)&lt;br&gt;5. characters (角色) - J: キャラクター (kyarakutā)&lt;br&gt;6. race tracks (賽車賽道) - J: レーストラック (rēsu torakku)&lt;br&gt;7. javascript (JavaScript) - J: JavaScript (jābāsuchipuritto)&lt;br&gt;8. enabled (啟用) - J: 有効にされました (yūkō ni sa remashita)&lt;br&gt;9. watch (觀看) - J: 見る (miru)&lt;br&gt;10. devices (設備) - J: デバイス (debaizu)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;片語：&lt;br&gt;1. Early access - 早期測試&lt;br&gt;   相似片語: Exclusive access - 獨家測試&lt;br&gt;   反義片語: Public access - 公開測試&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Fully released - 完全發行&lt;br&gt;   相似片語: Partially released - 部分發行&lt;br&gt;   反義片語: Unreleased - 未發行的&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. Free-to-play - 免費遊玩&lt;br&gt;   相似片語: Pay-to-play - 付費遊玩&lt;br&gt;   反義片語: Subscription-based - 訂閱制</content><link href="https://www.gamespot.com/articles/disney-speedstorm-launches-in-full-later-this-year/1100-6515630/" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>