<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><id>https://github.com/weg38asyy/GameRss.git</id><title>My Game Rss</title><updated>2023-04-17T17:20:52.248317+00:00</updated><author><name>Koala</name><email>weg38asyy@gmail.com</email></author><link href="https://github.com/weg38asyy" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Personal learning of English use</subtitle><entry><id>https://www.gamespot.com/articles/the-last-of-us-season-2-is-still-in-scripting-stage-so-dont-expect-it-soon/1100-6513295/</id><title>The Last Of Us Season 2 Is Still In Scripting Stage, So Don't Expect It Soon</title><updated>2023-04-17T17:20:52.248497+00:00</updated><content type="html">Fans waiting for the second season of The Last of Us might want to get comfortable. Writer-director Craig Mazin said at NAB Show Live in Las Vegas recently that Season 2 is still in the script stage, according to Deadline. &lt;br&gt; Mazin also confirmed that Season 2 will film in British Columbia, but apart from that, he didn't share much in the way of specifics. Mazin did, however, tease that there remains "quite a bit of story to tell" and went on say that The Last of Us will continue beyond Season 2 as expected. &lt;br&gt; "Our plan is to do it not just for one more season," he said. "We should be around for a while." &lt;br&gt; Neil Druckmann, who created the game series and works on the TV show as well, already plainly confirmed that Season 3 is in the works. It is believed that Season 2 will adapt the events of The Last of Us: Part II, but whether or not Season 2 covers the entire game or just some of it remains to be seen. Mazin and Druckmann have said the TV series won't go beyond the events of the game. Right now, there is no The Last of Us: Part III, so the story ends--at least at this point in time--with Part II. &lt;br&gt; In addition to The Last of Us Season 2, star Bella Ramsey (Ellie) will play a lead role in the movie Monstrous Beauty and has a major part in the upcoming second season of the BBC drama Time. &lt;br&gt; As for Pedro Pascal, who plays Joel, he is said to have "first position" status on the HBO series. That means HBO basically has first dibs on scheduling Pascal for filming. &lt;br&gt; Filming on The Last of Us Season 2 is expected to begin later in 2023, but the new season might not be released until 2025. For lots more, check out GameSpot's rundown of everything we know so far about The Last of Us Season 2.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;句子文法解析：&lt;br&gt;1. "Fans waiting for the second season of The Last of Us might want to get comfortable." - 使用現在分詞作前置詞，強調伴隨動作，表示等待第二季的粉絲們正在等待、期盼，應讓自己舒適地度過等待時間。&lt;br&gt;2. "Mazin also confirmed that Season 2 will film in British Columbia..." - 使用句型"主詞+動詞+that/whether/when/if等連接詞+從屬子句"，表示Mazin確認第二季將在英屬哥倫比亞地區拍攝。&lt;br&gt;3. "Mazin did, however, tease that there remains "quite a bit of story to tell"" -使用非正式的談話語氣及動詞tease來表示眾人盼望第二季的想法遠遠脫離現實，此季劇情具還有很多未被披露的部分。&lt;br&gt;4. "Neil Druckmann, who created the game series and works on the TV show as well, already plainly confirmed that Season 3 is in the works." -使用關代who及非限制性從屬子句，表示Neil Druckmann創作了遊戲系列，並在電視劇裡工作。此外，他也已經明確表示第三季正在籌備中。&lt;br&gt;5. "It is believed that Season 2 will adapt the events of The Last of Us: Part II, but whether or not Season 2 covers the entire game or just some of it remains to be seen." -使用whether or not引導的讓步狀語從句，表示第二季會根據遊戲第二部改編，但是否完全覆蓋游戲所有劇情還不清楚。&lt;br&gt;6. "Mazin and Druckmann have said the TV series won't go beyond the events of the game." -使用情態動詞have，表示Mazin和Druckmann曾經說過，電視劇不會超過遊戲事件的範圍。&lt;br&gt;7. "As for Pedro Pascal, who plays Joel, he is said to have "first position" status on the HBO series." -使用"It is said（據說）"的形式，表示有傳言稱Pedro Pascal是HBO綜藝節目新一季的領銜演員。&lt;br&gt;8. "Filming on The Last of Us Season 2 is expected to begin later in 2023, but the new season might not be released until 2025." -使用"動詞+名詞倒裝+助動詞+"的句型，表示《最後的生還者》第二季將在2023年晚些時候開始拍攝，但發行時間可能要等到2025年才會到來。&lt;br&gt;9. "For lots more, check out GameSpot's rundown of everything we know so far about The Last of Us Season 2." -使用"for"作為介系詞，表示為了更多資訊，可以查看GameSpot所提供的介紹。&lt;br&gt;10. "Writer-director Craig Mazin said at NAB Show Live in Las Vegas recently that Season 2 is still in the script stage, according to Deadline." -使用現在完成進行時，表示第二季劇本仍然在進行中，具體來自Mazin最近在Las Vegas的NAB Show Live上說的話，受Deadline報導。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;單字：&lt;br&gt;1. Fans (粉絲) - 聯想：使用類似單字"followers"、「偶像追隨者」、「迷」。&lt;br&gt;2. script (劇本) - 聯想：和「手寫」的"書寫"起源相同，「基礎、源訓」的"scriptures"、「序幕、脚本编辑」、「小說」、「扮演」、「種植」、「屏障」。&lt;br&gt;3. specific (明確的) - 聯想：具體的、詳細的、專門的、確定的、指定的、「ticket reservation system」。&lt;br&gt;4. story (故事) - 聯想："floor stories map" 記憶可視化、"storybox" 需梳理的問題。&lt;br&gt;5. confirm (確認) - 聯想：確認書、確立、二次確認、再三確認、振作自己、肯定、醫師確認反饋。&lt;br&gt;6. adapt (改編) - 聯想：改變適應、翻譯、調整、進行變更、可信過程控制、「APT logic」。&lt;br&gt;7. beyond (超出) - 聯想：超越、極其、開始、變化、轉至、容易令人淋漓盡致的東西、邊界。&lt;br&gt;8. series (系列) - 聯想：事件主題、洗腦行為機、裝飾的変化、護住隠私、情感代理僕人、全面的。&lt;br&gt;9. events (事件) - 聯想：關鍵活動、「自动驾驶车感应器」、「进食现象」、「心脏事件」、「技术事件的管理」&lt;br&gt;10. release (發行) - 聯想：`release the air ball` 放鬆身體、放鬆神經、還願、「Lead and cadmium release analysis」。 &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;片語：&lt;br&gt;1. 相似片語: &lt;br&gt;a. everything we know so far (截至目前我們所知道的一切) - 相似片語："all we know at present"「現時我們所知道的一切」。&lt;br&gt;b. remain…to be seen (仍有待觀察) - 相似片語："time will tell"「總會有答案」、「to be continued」。&lt;br&gt;2. 反義片語:&lt;br&gt;a. beyond (超出) - 反義片語："within"「可掌控範圍內」。&lt;br&gt;b. confirm (確認) - 反義片語："deny"「否認、否定」、「refute」、「disapprove」。</content><link href="https://www.gamespot.com/articles/the-last-of-us-season-2-is-still-in-scripting-stage-so-dont-expect-it-soon/1100-6513295/" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>