<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><id>https://github.com/weg38asyy/GameRss.git</id><title>My Game Rss</title><updated>2023-04-19T13:11:52.005097+00:00</updated><author><name>Koala</name><email>weg38asyy@gmail.com</email></author><link href="https://github.com/weg38asyy" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Personal learning of English use</subtitle><entry><id>https://www.gamespot.com/articles/cod-warzone-2-0-and-dmz-best-weapon-loadouts-and-attachment-tuning/1100-6509352/</id><title>CoD: Warzone 2 And DMZ Best Weapon Loadouts And Attachment Tuning</title><updated>2023-04-19T13:11:52.005218+00:00</updated><content type="html">Season 3 of Call of Duty: Warzone 2 added the Massive Resurgence mode for Al Mazrah, made a major overhaul to DMZ, and more. The seasonal patch notes also included major weapon tuning, so you'll want to make some adjustments to your loadouts. Here we recommend some of the best loadouts and tuning to use in Season 3. &lt;br&gt; Warzone 2's Gunsmith utilizes Modern Warfare 2's tuning feature, which adds the ability to fine tune attachments to improve certain weapon stats, such as recoil control, bullet velocity, aim-down-sight speed, and more. This is done by adjusting two sliders toward one stat benefit or the other. &lt;br&gt; It's important to note that not every attachment needs to be tuned just for the sake of tuning, as every adjustment has a pro and con tradeoff, but tuning attachments like muzzles and barrels can be beneficial. For our recommended loadouts, we do include a few attachments worth fine-tuning for each build. &lt;br&gt;   &lt;br&gt;   &lt;br&gt; The M4 has returned as a top-tier assault rifle choice for medium- to long-range gunfights. This is a fairly easy-to-use weapon, and the recommended attachments will help boost ammo count, ADS speed, and bullet velocity to make the M4 even better to use. This is a solid build for any mode, but this is perfect for those long-range fights in DMZ or battle royale on Al Mazrah. &lt;br&gt; For further tuning, you can tune the muzzle with the left slider favoring recoil smoothness at +0.78, while the bottom slider is tuned towards bullet velocity at +0.80. &lt;br&gt; The barrel can be tuned with the left slider adjusted towards recoil steadiness at +0.20, and the bottom slider at +0.26 towards damage range. &lt;br&gt; For the optic, tune the left slider towards aim down sight speed at -1.05, while adjusting the bottom slider to -1.65 towards far. (Some players chose to max out the slider towards close instead of far, but it's going to be personal preference whether you want a really close and larger optic instead.) &lt;br&gt; Finally, tune to rear grip with the left slider favoring recoil steadiness at +0.50, while the bottom slider is tuned towards aiming idle stability at +0.18. &lt;br&gt;   &lt;br&gt; Despite the Season 3 nerf, the ISO Hemlock is still one of Warzone 2's most powerful assault rifle options, but you'll want to switch up some attachments this season. The recommended attachments will help boost bullet velocity and damage range. &lt;br&gt; For further tuning, you can tune the muzzle with the left slider favoring recoil smoothness at +0.80, while the bottom slider is tuned towards bullet velocity at +0.60. &lt;br&gt; The barrel can be tuned with the left slider adjusted towards recoil steadiness at +0.18, and the bottom slider at +0.25 towards damage range. &lt;br&gt; For the optic, tune the left slider towards aim down sight speed at -2.16, while adjusting the bottom slider to -1.65 towards far. (Some players chose to max out the slider towards close instead of far, but it's going to be personal preference whether you want a really close and larger optic instead.) &lt;br&gt; The rear grip can be fine tuned by adjusting the left slider to +0.50 towards recoil steadiness, while tuning the bottom slider to +0.15 towards aiming idle stability. &lt;br&gt;   &lt;br&gt; The Sakin MG38 light machine gun is the top option for light machine guns to use in Warzone 2, especially as a long-range powerhouse for Al Mazrah or for mowing down AI in DMZ. The recommended attachments will help with mobility and control. &lt;br&gt; For further tuning, you can tune the ZLR Talon 5 muzzle with the left slider favoring recoil smoothness at +0.54, while the bottom slider is tuned towards bullet velocity at +0.58. &lt;br&gt; The barrel can be tuned with the left slider adjusted towards recoil steadiness at +0.28, and the bottom slider at +0.25 towards damage range. &lt;br&gt; For the optic, tune the left slider towards aim down sight speed at -1.56, while adjusting the bottom slider to -1.65 towards far. (Some players chose to max out the slider towards close instead of far, but it's going to be personal preference whether you want a really close and larger optic instead.) &lt;br&gt; For the rear grip, the Bruen G305 Grip Wrap can be adjusted with the left slider favoring recoil steadiness at +0.52, and the bottom slider at +0.28 of aiming idle stability. &lt;br&gt;   &lt;br&gt; The Vel 46 is now one of the best close-range options in Warzone 2, especially after the added headshot damage buff for the Season 3 update. The recommended attachments will help you make the most out of the weapons mobility, while also helping with recoil control. This can be great for any close combat situations, but it's definitely a solid build for Resurgence on Ashika Island. &lt;br&gt; For further tuning, you can tune the muzzle with the left slider favoring the aim down sight speed at -0.45, while tuning the bottom slider to +0.29 towards gun kick control. &lt;br&gt; The laser can be adjusted with the left slider tuned at -0.34 towards sprint to fire speed, and the bottom slider tuned at -35.70 towards aim down sight speed. &lt;br&gt; For the stock, you can tune the left slider to -2.80 towards aim down sight speed, and the right slider to -1.58 for better aim walking speed. &lt;br&gt; Finally, the rear grip can be adjusted with the left slider tuned at -0.40 towards aim down sight speed, while the bottom slider can be tuned to -0.37 toward sprint to fire speed. &lt;br&gt;   &lt;br&gt; Season 3 gave the Bas-P submachine gun some pretty significant buffs, so this is a great choice for sniper support or mid-range combat. The recommended attachments will help manage recoil and boost the ammo count. &lt;br&gt; For further tuning, you can tune the muzzle with the left slider favoring the aim down sight speed at -0.42, while tuning the bottom slider to +0.25 towards gun kick control. &lt;br&gt; The barrel can be fine tuned by adjusting the left slider to +0.19 towards recoil steadiness, and the bottom slider tuned to +0.25 to damage range. &lt;br&gt; For the optic, tune the left slider towards aim down sight speed at -2.25, while adjusting the bottom slider to -2.25 towards far. (Some players chose to max out the slider towards close instead of far, but it's going to be personal preference whether you want a really close and larger optic instead.) &lt;br&gt; The rear grip can be adjusted by tuning the left slider to +0.80 recoil steadiness, while the bottom slider to +0.20 towards aiming idle stability. &lt;br&gt;   &lt;br&gt; One of the overall best sniper rifles in Warzone 2 is the MCPR-300, and the Season 3 buff with added explosive ammo makes this an even more powerful sniper capable of knocking players with one-shot headshots. &lt;br&gt; For further tuning, you can tune the muzzle with the left slider favoring aim down sight speed at -1.04, while the bottom slider is adjusted to +0.78 towards bullet velocity. &lt;br&gt; Adjust the barrel by moving the left slider to +0.35 towards recoil steadiness, and then move the bottom slider to +0.34 towards damage range. &lt;br&gt; Tune the laser to adjust the left slider to -0.38 towards sprint to fire speed, and move the bottom slider to -41.00 towards aim-down-sight speed. &lt;br&gt; For the optic, tune the left slider towards aim down sight speed at -2.16, while adjusting the bottom slider to -0.75 towards far. &lt;br&gt; For the explosive ammo, tune the left slider to +0.52 damage range, while moving the bottom slider to +5.94 towards bullet velocity. &lt;br&gt;   &lt;br&gt; Season 3's new FJX Imperium is the rebranded version of the original Modern Warfare 2's Intervention sniper rifle, and this is also a powerful choice for sniping in battle royale or DMZ. Like the MCPR-300, this is a bolt-action sniper capable of one-hit snipes with the explosive ammo equipped. &lt;br&gt; For further tuning, you can tune the muzzle with the left slider favoring aim down sight speed at -0.45, while the bottom slider is adjusted to +0.80 towards bullet velocity. &lt;br&gt; Adjust the barrel by moving the left slider to -0.15 towards aim walking speed and then move the bottom slider to +0.22 towards damage range. &lt;br&gt; Adjust the VLK laser to tune the left slider to -0.18 sprint to fire speed, while moving the bottom slider to -36.18 towards aim down sight speed. &lt;br&gt; For the rear grip, adjust the left slider to -0.60 aim down sight speed, while tuning the bottom slider to +0.26 towards aiming idle stability. &lt;br&gt; Finally, tune the ammo with the left slider at +0.52 towards damage range, and the bottom slider to +4.32 towards bullet velocity. &lt;br&gt; If you still need to unlock Season 2 weapons, here is a guide to unlock the Tempus Torrent marksman rifle and a guide for unlocking the crossbow. &lt;br&gt; DMZ added new features in Season 3, including workbenches and a bartering system. Here's everything you need to know about DMZ workbenches for customizing Contraband weapons. Make sure to check out our best recipes list for DMZ's bartering.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;詳細句子文法解析： &lt;br&gt;1. "Season 3 gave the Bas-P submachine gun some pretty significant buffs, so this is a great choice for sniper support or mid-range combat." &lt;br&gt; 解析：本句主要為講解Bas-P冲锋枪火器的強化，使其成為狙擊支援或適合中程戰鬥的武器選擇。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. "For further tuning, you can tune the muzzle with the left slider favoring the aim down sight speed at -1.04, while the bottom slider is adjusted to +0.78 towards bullet velocity." &lt;br&gt;解析：本句內容為進一步調整Bas-P的附件，視情況根據需要加入一些更適合的裝置以升級武器性能，並且詳細介紹了如何調整附件的相關數值。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. "If you still need to unlock Season 2 weapons, here is a guide to unlock the Tempus Torrent marksman rifle and a guide for unlocking the crossbow." &lt;br&gt;解析：本句意在提供一些解鎖季節武器的資訊，並以Tempus Torrent狙擊步槍和弩槍作為例子進行介紹。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. "DMZ added new features in Season 3, including workbenches and a bartering system." &lt;br&gt;解析：本句介紹了Season 3 DMZ區域的新特徵，包括工作台和交易系统的新增。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. "Here's everything you need to know about DMZ workbenches for customizing Contraband weapons." &lt;br&gt;解析：本句完整介紹了玩家在DMZ工作臺中品改走私武器的相關知識。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;6. "It's important to note that not every attachment needs to be tuned just for the sake of tuning, as every adjustment has a pro and con tradeoff, but tuning attachments like muzzles and barrels can be beneficial." &lt;br&gt;解析：本句重點是強調槍械附件不需要為了Tuning而全都做大量更改，必須實事求是的作點適當的調整，而進一步的介紹這個進程的利弊得失。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;7. "For the rear grip, adjust the left slider to -0.60 aim down sight speed, while tuning the bottom slider to +0.26 towards aiming idle stability." &lt;br&gt;解析：本句提到了後握可以進一步的調整，調整左滑塊可讓准心移動的速度減少，調整底部的滑塊可增加瞄準時的穩定性，如此可使射擊更加準確。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;8. "The barrel can be tuned with the left slider adjusted towards recoil steadiness at +0.18, and the bottom slider at +0.25 towards damage range." &lt;br&gt;解析：本句講解了槍管裝置，藉由略微的跨越調整可增加射程，而調整偏于垂直方向上的左滑塊，則可使槍口垂直度下降。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;9. "The Vel 46 is now one of the best close-range options in Warzone 2, especially after the added headshot damage buff for the Season 3 update." &lt;br&gt;解析：本句描寫Vel 46作為戰地2最佳短距離武器之一，尤其在Season 3升級後增加頭擊傷害的情況下。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;10. "The recommended attachments will help manage recoil and boost the ammo count." &lt;br&gt;解析：本句提到珍貴的配件可以幫助管理回彈，並增強彈藥存量，進而提升作戰能力。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;單字及容易記住的方法：&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. Resurgence - 再起&lt;br&gt;   【拆解後詞彙聯想】 「Re」意為重新，如 re-start 再次開始、relive 重新體驗；「sur」意味著上方，再加上「gence」得出「上方再起」。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. overhaul - 檢修&lt;br&gt;   【英文諧音】為了將舊的，轉成新的再讓他運行，好像上映-銷。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. ammo - 彈藥&lt;br&gt;   【拆解後詞彙聯想】「am」表示愛，「mo」表示移動，看似二者沒啥關係，但由於拼音像 ammo，聯想愛移就是彈藥吧。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. tuning - 調整、調音&lt;br&gt;   【拆解後詞彙聯想】「tune」通常是指調整音樂上的音調、節奏等元素。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. recoil - 後座力&lt;br&gt;   【拆解後詞彙聯想】「re-」意為反向、反轉；【英文諧音】把槍往外逆,再進來，便會產生後座力。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;6. velocity - 速度&lt;br&gt;   【拆解後詞彙聯想】「veloci-」是英文單字 velociraptor(恐龍迅猛龍) 的詞源，由 Latin「velox,」意思是快速，得出影射「速度」之單字。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;7. overhaul - 緩沖器&lt;br&gt;   【英文諧音】如果你冷知識扎堆還是想吳翔的話，發音可以變得跟 “換借券”的「軟禿奇」一樣。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;8. powerhouse - 強大戰力&lt;br&gt;   【英文諧音】應該可以聯想到「莫力克」（powerful）。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;9. mobility - 機動性&lt;br&gt;   【拆解後詞彙聯想】「mobile」+「-ity 」x2 連帶了美食拼盤上的可麗餅（Pancake mobility）。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;10. buff - 強化、提升&lt;br&gt;    【拆解後詞彙聯想】與 world of warcraft中的buff概念想通，buff表示強化、增益</content><link href="https://www.gamespot.com/articles/cod-warzone-2-0-and-dmz-best-weapon-loadouts-and-attachment-tuning/1100-6509352/" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>