<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><id>https://github.com/weg38asyy/GameRss.git</id><title>My Game Rss</title><updated>2023-03-27T17:21:51.710043+00:00</updated><author><name>Koala</name><email>weg38asyy@gmail.com</email></author><link href="https://github.com/weg38asyy" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Personal learning of English use</subtitle><entry><id>https://www.gamespot.com/articles/mcu-and-creed-iii-star-jonathan-majors-arrested-for-alleged-assault-reps-say-hes-innocent/1100-6512725/</id><title>MCU And Creed III Star Jonathan Majors Arrested For Alleged Assault, Reps Say He's Innocent</title><updated>2023-03-27T17:21:51.710334+00:00</updated><content type="html">On March 25, actor Jonathan Majors was arrested in New York for strangulation, assault, and harassment charges. Police say they were responding to a 911 call regarding a domestic dispute between Majors and a 30-year-old woman, according to the AP. A New York Police Department spokesperson put out a statement that the woman "sustained minor injuries to her head and neck and was removed to an area hospital in stable condition." Majors' lawyer, Priya Chaudhry, told Deadline that the Ant-Man and The Wasp: Quantumania actor "is completely innocent and is provably the victim." Chaudhry also argued that there is video evidence and witness testimony that will clear Majors of any wrongdoing, although that has yet to be made public. "All the evidence proves that Mr. Majors is entirely innocent and did not assault her whatsoever," the lawyer added. "Unfortunately, this incident came about because this woman was having an emotional crisis, for which she was taken to a hospital yesterday. The NYPD is required to make an arrest in these situations, and this is the only reason Mr. Majors was arrested. We expect these charges to be dropped soon." Along with his role as Kang the Conqueror in the MCU, Majors also stars in the blockbuster Creed III alongside Michael B. Jordan. Majors could also be seen in a US Army campaign with TV commercials, but those have been suspended, per the AP. "While Mr. Majors is innocent until proven guilty, prudence dictates that we pull our ads until the investigation into these allegations is complete," The Army Enterprise Marketing Office said in a statement. Currently, Majors is set to appear in court May 8.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;詳細句子文法解析：&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. "actor Jonathan Majors was arrested in New York for strangulation, assault, and harassment charges." - 過去式被動結構，表示主語（Jonathan Majors）是動作的承受者，強調事件已經發生。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. "Police say they were responding to a 911 call regarding a domestic dispute between Majors and a 30-year-old woman, according to the AP." - 過去式進行式，表示過去某時正在進行的動作。根據警方和新聞報導說法，明確指出報案和爭吵事件的時間和來龍去脈。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. "Majors' lawyer, Priya Chaudhry, told Deadline that the Ant-Man and The Wasp: Quantumania actor 'is completely innocent and is provably the victim.'" - 過去式陳述句，表示發生過的事件，並且講述 Priya Chaudhry 私人律師對于 Jonathen Majors 無罪的觀點。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. "Chaudhry also argued that there is video evidence and witness testimony that will clear Majors of any wrongdoing, although that has yet to be made public." - 過去式複合式，表示在一個時間段內發生的多個動作。Priya Chaudhry 認為，會有錄像證據和證人證言證明 Jonathan Majors 是無辜的，儘管相關資訊尚未對外公開。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. "Currently, Majors is set to appear in court May 8." - 現在進行時，暗示動作是發生在當下或未來。Jonathan Majors 預計在5月8日出庭受審。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;單字：&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. Arrested - 逮捕、拘留；日文單字：逮捕 (たいほ)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Strangulation - 扼流、勒喉；日文單字：絞め殺される (しめころされる)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. Harassment - 騷擾、煩惱；日文單字：ハラスメント (はらすめんと)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. Innocent - 無辜的；日文單字：無実の (むじつの)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. Testimony - 講述、證詞；日文單字：供述 (きょうじゅつ)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;6. Charges - 控訴、指控；日文單字：チャージ (ちゃーじ)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;7. Victim - 受害者；日文單字：被害者 (ひがいしゃ)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;8. Prudence - 審慎、謹慎；日文單字：慮重 (りょちゅう)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;9. Suspected - 懷疑的、嫌疑犯；日文單字：病原体（びょうげんたい）&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;10. Enterprise - 企業、公司；日文單字：エンタープライズ (えんたーぷらいず)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;片語：&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. Domestic dispute - 家庭糾紛；相似片語：family conflict/argument；反義片語：Harmonious family life - 和諧的家庭生活&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Innocent until proven guilty - 无罪推定；相似片語：guilty until proven innocent - 有罪推定；反義片語：Guilty conscience - 內疚&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. Completely innocent - 完全清白；相似片語：completely guilty - 完全有罪；反義片語：with evidence of guilt - 有罪的證據&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. Domestic violence - 家庭暴力；相似片語：Spouse abuse - 配偶虐待；反義片語：Healthy relationship - 健康關係&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;其他：&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. 字彙記憶記憶方式建議：透過聯想方法，例如 "arrested" 把它聯想成 "ass rest"，表示被人用屁股緊緊按住，遭受拘留。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. 片語記憶方式建議：將相關的片語彙在較短的文章中確認其出現次數和上下文，使學生在閱讀和寫作時容易使用並掌握其用法。</content><link href="https://www.gamespot.com/articles/mcu-and-creed-iii-star-jonathan-majors-arrested-for-alleged-assault-reps-say-hes-innocent/1100-6512725/" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>