<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><id>https://github.com/weg38asyy/GameRss.git</id><title>My Game Rss</title><updated>2023-06-07T13:13:21.610581+00:00</updated><author><name>Koala</name><email>weg38asyy@gmail.com</email></author><link href="https://github.com/weg38asyy" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Personal learning of English use</subtitle><entry><id>https://www.gamespot.com/articles/diablo-4-endgame-overview-all-endgame-activities-and-rewards/1100-6514877/</id><title>Diablo 4 Endgame Overview - All Endgame Activities And Rewards</title><updated>2023-06-07T13:13:21.610976+00:00</updated><content type="html">Beating the main campaign in Diablo 4 is only half the battle, as a whole new world of hellish mobs and amazing loot opens up to you after rolling credits. After completing the campaign there are repeatable activities, difficult dungeons, and better loot. Here's an overview of everything there is to do in Diablo 4, once you beat the campaign. &lt;br&gt; One of the first things you should do after rolling credits is complete the first Capstone Dungeon and unlock World Tier 3, which is for characters level 50-70. Some parts of the endgame, like Helltides and Nightmare Sigils, are only available on World Tier 3 or higher. Once you have completed all campaign acts and have reached level 50, you can take on the first Capstone Dungeon, the Cathedral of Light dungeon. This dungeon is far more challenging than the previous dungeons found in the game and must be completed on World Tier 2. &lt;br&gt; You need a javascript enabled browser to watch videos. &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;        Want us to remember this setting for all your devices?&lt;br&gt;       &lt;br&gt; Sign up or Sign in now!&lt;br&gt;       &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;        By clicking 'enter', you agree to GameSpot's&lt;br&gt;                        Terms of Use and&lt;br&gt;        Privacy Policy &lt;br&gt; enter &lt;br&gt; Now Playing: Diablo 4 Necromancer Tier 15 Nightmare Dungeon Gameplay (World Tier 3) &lt;br&gt; After reaching level 70 you can take on the second Capstone dungeon, the Fallen Temple, but this one must be done on World Tier 3, making it a real challenge. &lt;br&gt; After hitting level 50 you no longer gain skill points for leveling up. Instead, you gain multiple Paragon Points per level, which let you pick spots on the Paragon Board. Each spot on the Paragon board provides some type of bonus, from small stat boosts to massive, build-altering passive bonuses. The Paragon Board also has spots for Glyphs, which drop randomly in endgame activities. These Glyphs give a wide range of bonuses and can be upgraded by completing Nightmare dungeons. &lt;br&gt; Nightmare Dungeons are a special, harder version, of the regular dungeons found in Diablo 4's world. These dungeons have special modifications and typically allow for a limited number of deaths in the dungeon before you fail. In order to play a Nightmare Dungeon, you must find a Nightmare Sigil, which when activated transforms a random dungeon--typically specified in the description of the Sigil--into a Nightmare Dungeon. Nightmare Sigils start dropping on World Tier 3. &lt;br&gt; One of the main overworld activities you will participate in for the endgame of Diablo 4 are the Grim Favors and Whispers of the Dead. Grim Favors are limited-time activities that appear in different regions around the map. This can range from killing enemies in the open-world to completing public events and even completing dungeons. Each activity awards points, either 1, 3, or 5. Once you reach 10 points, you can return to the Tree of Whispers, which lets you pick from three caches of loot, typically focusing on a specific type of gear. This is one of the best ways to consistently get loot and earn XP, without any risk of losing what you worked far. The same can't be said for the other two endgame activities. &lt;br&gt; Helltides occur starting with World Tier 3, transforming a specific section of the map temporarily into, well, Hell. This area is marked by turning that section of the map red, filling it with demons and other powerful enemies. While in a Helltide enemies drop Aberrant Cinders, a currency that can be used to open chests scattered throughout the Helltide. The exact cost of each chest varies depending on what type of item it gives, typically between 75 to 125. The danger here is two-fold; if you die, you lose a significant chunk of your Aberrant Cinders and they all disappear when the Helltide ends. &lt;br&gt; For players looking to prove their might, the Fields of Hatred exist in the southeast part of the map typically. While inside the Fields of Hatred, you can find any random player you find, along with a ton of regular enemies. In these areas, both regular enemies and other players drop Seeds of Hatred, the PvP currency. Once you collect a decent number of Seeds of Hatred, you need to make it to an Altar of Extraction, which converts them to Red Dust. While the currency is in Seeds of Hatred form, you drop all of them when killed and they disappear if you leave the PvP zone. The Red Dust is moved to the currency part of your inventory and can't be lost once converted, which can be used at the PvP vendor. &lt;br&gt; Another form of Public Events comes in the form of World Bosses, like Ashava, which are massive enemies meant to be fought by a ton of players at once. These enemies spawn at specific times set by Blizzard, indicated 30 minutes prior to the start of the fight by an icon on the world map, with an accompanying timer. These massive battles award great loot, but are borderline impossible to takedown alone, so you will need to see if other players are taking on the boss when it becomes available. &lt;br&gt; For more Diablo 4 guides, like class builds and collectible locations, check out GameSpot's Diablo 4 Guides Hub.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;詳細句子文法解析：&lt;br&gt;1. "Beating the main campaign in Diablo 4 is only half the battle, as a whole new world of hellish mobs and amazing loot opens up to you after rolling credits." &lt;br&gt;分析：此句為主題句，使用了名詞allegory，含有一層隱藏意義，表示打敗遊戲主線劇情只是勝利的一半，還有更多的遊戲內容需要玩家去闖蕩。&lt;br&gt;重點：名詞allegory表示含義深遠，不只是表面意思。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. "After completing the campaign there are repeatable activities, difficult dungeons, and better loot." &lt;br&gt;分析：此句為轉折句，使用了連接詞after，表示主線劇情完成後，還有其他不同的內容可以供玩家遊玩。&lt;br&gt;重點：連接詞after表示時間先後順序。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. "Here's an overview of everything there is to do in Diablo 4, once you beat the campaign." &lt;br&gt;分析：此句使用介系詞here，表示將要介紹的東西直接出現在語氣中，讓對方更易理解。&lt;br&gt;重點：介系詞here表示將要介紹的東西已經呈現在言語中。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. "One of the first things you should do after rolling credits is complete the first Capstone Dungeon and unlock World Tier 3, which is for characters level 50-70." &lt;br&gt;分析：此句為複合句，使用了名詞dungeon和連接詞which，表示在完成主線劇情後，要先完成固定的事件和解鎖特定關卡。&lt;br&gt;重點：名詞dungeon表示固定的事件，連接詞which代表先前出現過的句子。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. "Once you have completed all campaign acts and have reached level 50, you can take on the first Capstone Dungeon, the Cathedral of Light dungeon." &lt;br&gt;分析：此句為條件句，使用了連接詞once和主線劇情遊戲術語capstone dungeon，表示在完成所有主線劇情和達到特定等級後就可以前往固定的事件。&lt;br&gt;重點：連接詞once表示在完成所有任務後。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;6. "After reaching level 70 you can take on the second Capstone dungeon, the Fallen Temple, but this one must be done on World Tier 3, making it a real challenge." &lt;br&gt;分析：此句為複合句，使用了名詞level和capstone dungeon，表示在達到特定等級後可以前往特定地點進行更困難的挑戰。&lt;br&gt;重點：名詞level表示角色的等級。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;7. "After hitting level 50 you no longer gain skill points for leveling up." &lt;br&gt;分析：此句為複合句，使用了名詞skill points和連接詞after，表示達到特定等級後不會再獲得一些在先前遊戲過程中所得到的額外技能和能力。&lt;br&gt;重點：名詞skill points表示額外技能和能力。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;8. "Nightmare Dungeons are a special, harder version, of the regular dungeons found in Diablo 4's world." &lt;br&gt;分析：此句使用介詞of，表示具體的特定關卡。&lt;br&gt;重點：介詞of用於描述特定物品或事物。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;9. "These Glyphs give a wide range of bonuses and can be upgraded by completing Nightmare dungeons." &lt;br&gt;分析：此句使用名詞Glyphs，表示在完成一些關卡後，可以達成記錄，得到認可。&lt;br&gt;重點：名詞Glyphs表示遊戲內特定得到的獎勵。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;10. "The danger here is two-fold; if you die, you lose a significant chunk of your Aberrant Cinders and they all disappear when the Helltide ends." &lt;br&gt;分析：此句使用連接詞if和名詞Aberrant Cinders，表示如果失敗，將會失去獲得的Aberrant Cinders。&lt;br&gt;重點：使用連接詞if表示一件事情是可行的，前提是所有的條件都成立。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;單字：&lt;br&gt;1. repeatable: 可重複的，容易拆解成[repeat+able]，把這兩個英文單字拼在一起很容易記憶&lt;br&gt;日文單字：繰り返し可能な&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. loot: 擊敗敵人得到的戰利品，這個詞彙似乎沒有所謂的英文諧音，可以透過與“believe”這個英文字母相同的bl，以及耳熟能詳的“whoop”聲組成助記&lt;br&gt;日文單字：戦利品(せんりひん)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. tier: 等級，很容易和英文單字"tear"搞混，將tier中的i拆掉，轉化成te+r，聲音相似，更容易記憶 &lt;br&gt;日文單字：階級(かいきゅう)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. capstone: 完成成就的最後關鍵，可以把這個單字中的stone解釋成‘成就障礙’&lt;br&gt;日文單字：古代の記念碑&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. challenging: 具有挑戰性的，可以把英文單字challenging拆成[challenge+ing]，中文直譯是“挑戰+ing”，下意識理解爲“正在經歷一個挑戰”&lt;br&gt;日文單字：チャレンジング&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;6. modification: 修改，這個單字易被和大眾文化中浮光云影的《變形金剛》中的Megatron產生聯想，把eliminated的第一個字母e和f互換，可以得到modifinated，這樣更容易記憶 &lt;br&gt;日文單字：修正(しゅうせい)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;7. consistency: 一致性，將這個英文單字切割成三部分，con+sist+ency，con=between，sist=exist，ency=noun後綴，可以放在之前的部分確保意思清晰，使聯想記憶更容易 &lt;br&gt;日文單字：一貫性(いっかんせい)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;8. accumulate: 累積，可以把這個英文單詞拆解成[ac+cumulate]，ac的定義是：加強、使強；cumulate前半部分的cf實際上是accumulate的命名前綴，表示混合、聚集的意思；最終，nakudo會覺得是ac的含義為"使強大"，相對就想到accumulate的打卡和積分的含義&lt;br&gt;日文單字：蓄積(ちくせき)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;9. challenge: 挑戰，這個單詞可參考為“ch-', 'allen-'和'ge”分别发音记忆&lt;br&gt;日文單字：挑戦(ちょうせん)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;10. currency: 現金，貨幣，通貨信用體系，將currency發音變成中文含有現金內涵的pronunciation怕較容易記憶和建立聯想&lt;br&gt;日文單字：通貨，現金(げんきん)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;片語：&lt;br&gt;1. similar phrase: different from，反義形容詞：same as&lt;br&gt;2. similar phrase: a whole new world，相似詞彙：brand-new，反義詞彙：old &amp; used&lt;br&gt;3. similar phrase: make it to，相似詞彙：arrive，反義詞彙：lose one's way&lt;br&gt;4. similar phrase: at once，相似詞彙：immediately，反義詞彙：later&lt;br&gt;5. similar phrase: complete all acts，相似詞彙：finish all stages，反義詞彙：fail to progress&lt;br&gt;6. similar phrase: earn XP，相似詞彙：gain experience points，反義詞彙：lose experience points&lt;br&gt;7. similar phrase: grim favors，相似詞彙：grim and serious deeds，反義詞彙：casual events&lt;br&gt;8. similar phrase: fields of hatred，相似詞彙：areas of strong hostility，反義詞彙：peaceful sections&lt;br&gt;9. similar phrase: public events，相似詞彙：open events，反義詞彙：private events&lt;br&gt;10. similar phrase: massive enemies，相似詞彙：gigantic rivals，反義詞：tiny foes</content><link href="https://www.gamespot.com/articles/diablo-4-endgame-overview-all-endgame-activities-and-rewards/1100-6514877/" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>