<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><id>https://github.com/weg38asyy/GameRss.git</id><title>My Game Rss</title><updated>2023-04-10T13:10:57.516295+00:00</updated><author><name>Koala</name><email>weg38asyy@gmail.com</email></author><link href="https://github.com/weg38asyy" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Personal learning of English use</subtitle><entry><id>https://www.gamespot.com/articles/the-decade-long-effort-to-make-alice-asylum-has-reached-an-end/1100-6513093/</id><title>The Decade-Long Effort To Make Alice: Asylum Has Reached An End</title><updated>2023-04-10T13:10:57.516701+00:00</updated><content type="html">The decade-long push to get Alice: Asylum--a theoretical third game in the Alice series--has ended, announced developer American McGee. &lt;br&gt; After the completion of an Alice: Asylum design bible--a huge document containing concept art, core game design concepts, and narrative goals--McGee said he resumed talks with Electronic Arts, the company that owns Alice's IP, to see if EA would be either be willing to fund Alice: Asylum or to license the IP out. &lt;br&gt; Alice: Asylum has reached The EndAfter several weeks of review, EA has come back with a response regarding funding and/or licensing for "Alice: Asylum" - Alice had a good run but the dream is over. https://t.co/hyprIq9MpE#gamedev #aliceasylum pic.twitter.com/sIE3bKbaVY &lt;br&gt; EA refused to do either. McGee said EA passed on funding due to "internal analysis of the IP, market conditions, and details of the production proposal," and did not want to license the IP because, "'Alice' is an important part of EA’s overall game catalog, and selling or licensing it isn’t something they’re prepared to do right now." &lt;br&gt; McGee spearheaded both of the previous Alice games, American McGee's Alice and Alice Madness Returns. He has tried to get the third Alice game off the ground for years, opening up a Patreon to help support the creation of a production and design plan--with acknowledgement that it depends entirely on EA whether or not a third Alice game is greenlit. &lt;br&gt; Now with EA's decision, McGee said the team has "exhausted" every option to realize a third Alice game, and that "there is no other way forward with the project." &lt;br&gt; He will close the Alice: Asylum Patreon page and while content will remain, he will no longer try to raise funds for Alice: Asyulm. McGee said he is also saying goodbye entirely to the Alice series, stating, "I have also reached an endpoint with 'Alice' and with game production in general. I have no other ideas or energy left to apply toward getting a new Alice game made." &lt;br&gt; "Nor do I have any interest in pursuing new game ideas within the context of the current environment for game development," McGee continued. "If someone does manage to convince EA to make 'Asylum,' I would like to make clear that, from this point forward, I have no desire to be involved with that or any other Alice-related development." &lt;br&gt; McGee ended the Patreon note by thanking backers for their years of support. "We knew going into this adventure that failure was a possibility. But we wanted to believe impossible things--and we had fun doing that up to the moment when reality forced itself into our Wonderland," McGee said. "It's often said that when one door closes, another opens. Trite but true. And I hope that for all of you, this closure will bring life to other adventures and dreams."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;句子文法解析：&lt;br&gt;1. "The decade-long push to get Alice: Asylum--a theoretical third game in the Alice series--has ended" 主要使用了過去時，強調這個推動活動已經結束并不再進展。&lt;br&gt;2. "After the completion of an Alice: Asylum design bible--a huge document containing concept art, core game design concepts, and narrative goals--McGee said he resumed talks with Electronic Arts" 使用了長句的結構，將文案過程和Mgee接觸EA的事宜在一句話中表達。&lt;br&gt;3. "McGee spearheaded both of the previous Alice games, American McGee's Alice and Alice Madness Returns" 句中使用了關連詞"both"，將McGee創作的兩個阿麗斯遊戲鏈接在了一起。&lt;br&gt;4. "He has tried to get the third Alice game off the ground for years, opening up a Patreon to help support the creation of a production and design plan--with acknowledgement that it depends entirely on EA whether or not a third Alice game is greenlit." 句中使用了過去完成式，強調了過去某個時間點完成的動作或情況對現在產生的影響。&lt;br&gt;5. "McGee ended the Patreon note by thanking backers for their years of support." 句中使用了現在分詞作後綴，說明McGee是以感嘆形式結束了他的說明。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;單字：&lt;br&gt;1. push: 推動&lt;br&gt;   日文對應單字：を促進する (wo sokushin suru)&lt;br&gt;2. theoretical: 理論上的&lt;br&gt;   日文對應單字：理論的な (rireonteki na)&lt;br&gt;3. completion: 完成&lt;br&gt;   日文對應單字：完成 (kansei)&lt;br&gt;4. IP:  知識產權&lt;br&gt;   日文對應單字：知的財産権 (chiteki zaisan ken)&lt;br&gt;5. concept: 概念&lt;br&gt;   日文對應單字：概念 (gainen)&lt;br&gt;6. narrative: 敘事&lt;br&gt;   日文對應單字：ナラティブ (narativu)&lt;br&gt;7. proposal: 計畫，建議&lt;br&gt;   日文對應單字：企画 (ki-kaku)&lt;br&gt;8. license: 許可&lt;br&gt;   日文對應單字：ライセンス (raisensu)&lt;br&gt;9. exhausted: 耗盡，用完&lt;br&gt;   日文對應單字：使い果たす (tsukai hatasu)&lt;br&gt;10. production: 製作&lt;br&gt;   日文對應單字：製作 (seisaku)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;片語：&lt;br&gt;1. off the ground: 啟動，開始運作&lt;br&gt;   相似片語：up and running &lt;br&gt;   反義片語：at a standstill &lt;br&gt;2. greenlit: 獲准，通過&lt;br&gt;   相似片語：give the go-ahead &lt;br&gt;   反義片語：shot down &lt;br&gt;3. pass on: 放棄，不考慮&lt;br&gt;   相似片語：give up on &lt;br&gt;   反義片語：consider seriously 或是 pursue &lt;br&gt;4. bring life to: 唤起，启发，&lt;br&gt;   相似片語：inspire 或是 ignite&lt;br&gt;   反義片語：extinguish &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;其它：&lt;br&gt;1. push同音詞是pussy，可以聯想到男性壞笑喊"I'm gonna push that pussy"，也可以與酥胸脯聯想到入侵(push in)。&lt;br&gt;2. completion的第一個音節是com，可以聯想到完成(complete)后給自己玩玩咖啡(come)。&lt;br&gt;3. license的最後兩個字母有-s，可以聯想到多買一些，充足的掛賣量可以讓產品得到充足的許可。</content><link href="https://www.gamespot.com/articles/the-decade-long-effort-to-make-alice-asylum-has-reached-an-end/1100-6513093/" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>