<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><id>https://github.com/weg38asyy/GameRss.git</id><title>My Game Rss</title><updated>2023-06-11T13:11:39.012327+00:00</updated><author><name>Koala</name><email>weg38asyy@gmail.com</email></author><link href="https://github.com/weg38asyy" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Personal learning of English use</subtitle><entry><id>https://www.gamespot.com/articles/diablo-4-best-classes-ranked-which-class-is-best-for-new-players/1100-6514708/</id><title>Diablo 4 Best Classes Ranked - Which Class Is Best For New Players</title><updated>2023-06-11T13:11:39.012573+00:00</updated><content type="html">Diablo 4 has finally arrived, tasking you with defeating Lilith and the forces of Hell. At launch, Diablo 4 has five classes to pick from, with each class having its own unique pros and cons. While seasoned Diablo veterans will likely already know which class they are rolling with first, new players might be unsure which one will give them the best experience. &lt;br&gt; Here are the pros and cons for each class and which ones will be the easiest to master. The classes are ranked from most newcomer-friendly to least, all according to an experience set to World Tier 1 difficulty, the game's beginner-friendly mode. &lt;br&gt; The Necromancer is a fan-favorite class in Diablo and there is a reason for it. The Necromancer is both the most powerful damage-focused class and fairly simple. This class focuses on creating minions from dead enemies and can even use dead enemies' bones to attack foes. They can also have the ability to make corpses explode, making them more powerful as more enemies die around them. &lt;br&gt; The biggest benefits of the Necromancer class are the Minions and the Book of the Dead, which allow you to pick from a variety of different minions, unlocking more as you level up. Having an extra set of hands on the battlefield is a big boon to newcomers, making it feel like you have extra help, even if you are playing alone. &lt;br&gt; As for the downsides of the Necromancer, the main issue new players will find with this class--and the other damage-focused classes--is how squishy you can be, especially if you are playing alone. You will need to learn to keep your distance and focus on enemies getting too close to you, otherwise you might find yourself dying frequently, especially on higher World Tiers. &lt;br&gt; The Sorcerer comes in just under the Necromancer in terms of approachability, only missing slightly due to it not being as much of a powerhouse as the Necromancer. While the Sorcerer deals a bit less damage, the skills are far easier to understand; the system of regenerating mana for more powerful attacks is fairly simple. Sorcerer's can harness the power of the elements to deal a ton of damage to enemies in large areas, with skills that focus on ice, fire, lightning, and more. &lt;br&gt; The Sorcerer does have some abilities that provide them with extra defense in the middle of combat, but they have limited mobility compared to the other classes and the health pool isn't as deep. Luckily, the majority of attacks are ranged and you can deal damage to many enemies at the same time, so you won't find yourself getting overwhelmed by large groups too often. The Enhancement system for Sorcerer is also fairly simple, providing powerful passive bonuses depending on which skills you currently have equipped. &lt;br&gt; The Druid functions as a hybrid class, with high-damage magic abilities and wild beast forms that can tank more damage than some of the other classes. During the beta for Diablo 4, there were complaints that the Druid wasn't as offensively capable as the other classes, but a build focused on area-of-effect attacks and defensive buffs can create a capable damage dealer that won't go down as quickly as some of the squishier classes. &lt;br&gt; The Druid's main fault is how cooldown-heavy the class can be, with you needing to bide time and take some damage between large attacks. Even with the ability to switch to different animal forms, which let you shred enemies at close range, you might spend a decent amount of time waiting for cooldowns to end. However, being able to have both defensive abilities and powerful attacks makes Druid a nice, middling class for newbies. &lt;br&gt; The Rogue is easily the least newcomer-friendly class in Diablo 4 from a mechanical sense, due to this class's focus on dealing large amounts of damage to single targets and using buffs and debuffs to your advantage. The Rogue uses a mixture of melee attacks and ranged attacks, many of which inflict debuffs like vulnerable. After making an enemy vulnerable, they take additional damage. To maximize this class you will need to focus on activating debuffs on enemies before using your bigger damage abilities. &lt;br&gt; The Rogue also has to take advantage of the Imbuement system, which lets you imbue some abilities with either poison, ice, or shadow. Imbuement only affects the next two abilities used, so you have to know which combos you are going to use ahead of time before activating it. The Rogue's special system is the Specializations, which provides special bonuses and buffs, assuming you do whatever the requirements are of each Specialization. You will need to build your skills around each different kind, making it one of the more complicated characters to build. &lt;br&gt; The Rogue's biggest flaw is that it's the class that struggles with large groups the most. There are plenty of abilities that deal damage in a large area, but your primary attacks are all single target focused. You will need to dash and roll around the battlefield to keep from getting surrounded. Rogue's have very high damage potential, but it takes more game knowledge than new players might have for their first character. &lt;br&gt; The Barbarian is the main tank-focused class, using a vast arsenal of melee weapons to slice and bash enemies at close range. Barbarians have the special ability to rotate through different weapon types using the Weapon Arsenal mechanic, with different Barbarian skills available to use depending on the weapons currently equipped. While rotating through different weapon types might sound a bit difficult, it's fairly easy to grasp, especially since you will slowly unlock new abilities as you level up. &lt;br&gt; The most newcomer-friendly part about the Barbarian is that it's the tank class, making it much easier to survive massive amounts of damage. The trade-off is that you don't deal as much damage as the other classes, but if you're new to Diablo and playing alone, you will be grateful for the larger health pool. You can pick skills, like Bleed abilities, to get more damage out of the Barbarian. The reason the Barbarian falls at the bottom of the list is that it can be very difficult to take down bosses and some of the tougher enemies alone, due to the lower damage output and the need to get in close to deal damage. This shouldn't put anyone off from trying it, but you might find yourself unhappy with how long it takes to kill enemies. &lt;br&gt; Check out GameSpot's Diablo 4 Guides Hub for more information about the five classes and other important aspects of Sanctuary.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;詳細句子文法解析：&lt;br&gt;1. "Diablo 4 has finally arrived, tasking you with defeating Lilith and the forces of Hell." - 這個句子是一個現在分詞片語(tasking you)，用來表達主詞(Diablo 4)所做的事情，即讓你去打敗Lilith和地獄勢力。這種片語用於加強度和描述性，強調動作進行中。&lt;br&gt;2. "At launch, Diablo 4 has five classes to pick from, with each class having its own unique pros and cons." - 這個句子有兩個用逗號分隔的獨立子句。第一個子句是"At launch, Diablo 4 has five classes to pick from"，用於表達時間（開始時），有哪些選擇。第二個子句是"with each class having its own unique pros and cons"（每個職業都有其獨特的優點和缺點），用於展示每個職業都有其資格和適合性。&lt;br&gt;3. "While seasoned Diablo veterans will likely already know which class they are rolling with first, new players might be unsure which one will give them the best experience." - 這個句子是一個複合句，有兩個子句，前者是起承轉合作用，後者則是表現其展示目的。其中‘while'用來表達對比，前者(Diablo veterans)非常清楚自己的選擇，後者(new players)則可能不太確定。 &lt;br&gt;4. "Here are the pros and cons for each class and which ones will be the easiest to master." - 這個句子是一個陳述句，用來說明在接下來的內容中將會呈現各個職業的利弊與易度。&lt;br&gt;5. " The Necromancer is a fan-favorite class in Diablo and there is a reason for it." - 這個句子中的"is"是一個判斷動詞，用以說明"Necromancer是Diablo中最受歡迎的職業之一"的原因。&lt;br&gt;6. "The biggest benefits of the Necromancer class are the Minions and the Book of the Dead, which allow you to pick from a variety of different minions, unlocking more as you level up." - 這個句子是一個複合句，有兩個子句，其中一個用以說明"Necromancer職業的最大優勢"，而另一個描述Minions和the Book of the Dead兩個顯著優點，用來支持前面所提到的優勢。&lt;br&gt;7. "Having an extra set of hands on the battlefield is a big boon to newcomers, making it feel like you have extra help, even if you are playing alone." - 這個句子是一個複合句，其中前半句"Having an extra set of hands on the battlefield is a big boon to newcomers"是表述Necromancer的利益，而後半句"making it feel like you have extra help, even if you are playing alone"是解釋為什麼這是好的。&lt;br&gt;8. "The trade-off is that you don't deal as much damage as the other classes, but if you're new to Diablo and playing alone, you will be grateful for the larger health pool." - 這個句子是一個複合句，前半部分表達了職業的缺點，而後半部分解釋為什麼這個缺點對新手有利。&lt;br&gt;9. "The Rogue's biggest flaw is that it's the class that struggles with large groups the most." - 這個句子是一個陳述句，用以表達Rogue職業最大的缺陷是其對抗大群體的能力較弱。 &lt;br&gt;10. "You will need to dash and roll around the battlefield to keep from getting surrounded." - 這個句子是一個命令句，用來表達為了戰勝敵人必須要使用躲避等技能。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;單字：&lt;br&gt;1. tasking - 分配任務（針對Diablo 4主題）&lt;br&gt;2. veteran - 老手&lt;br&gt;3. pros - 優勢&lt;br&gt;4. cons - 缺點&lt;br&gt;5. mundane- 平凡的 &lt;br&gt;6. regenerating - 再生的&lt;br&gt;7. formidable - 強大的&lt;br&gt;8. offensively - 攻擊性地&lt;br&gt;9. formidable- 強大的 &lt;br&gt;10. augment - 增強&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;片語：&lt;br&gt;1. pick from - 選擇中&lt;br&gt;2. unique pros and cons - 獨特的優勢和缺點&lt;br&gt;3. be unsure - 不確定&lt;br&gt;4. at close range - 在近距離&lt;br&gt;5. in terms of - 在⋯方面&lt;br&gt;6. go down - 死亡；衰退&lt;br&gt;7. be grateful for - 對什麼感激&lt;br&gt;8. in large groups - 大群體中&lt;br&gt;9. new to - 對某事物不熟悉&lt;br&gt;10. focus on - 專注於&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;日文單字：&lt;br&gt;1. veteran - ベテラン&lt;br&gt;2. pros - プロ&lt;br&gt;3. cons - 詳細する&lt;br&gt;4. mundane - ありふれた&lt;br&gt;5. offensively - 攻撃的&lt;br&gt;6. regenerating - 再生性の&lt;br&gt;7. formidable - 威風堂々とした&lt;br&gt;8. augment - 増幅する&lt;br&gt;9. pick from - 中へ挿入する&lt;br&gt;10. unique - ユニークな&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;記憶方式：&lt;br&gt;1. tasking - 任務+ing，類似於任務中進行，相對容易記憶；&lt;br&gt;2. veteran - 聽起來很像"戰場高手"，而高手可以指老手；&lt;br&gt;3. pros - 大部分都明白"優勢(張大優點)"的意思，可以拆開記憶；&lt;br&gt;4. cons - 易混淆於音形相近的中文單詞「糊塗」，想要達到相反結果，即需避免糊塗，也就是"缺點"。&lt;br&gt;5. mundane- 拆解詞意即為世俗的，代表著平凡 &lt;br&gt;6. regenerating - regeneration 可轉換為再生，與死靈法師所管理的屍體復活相似  &lt;br&gt;7. formidable - 聽起來笨重而強大&lt;br&gt;8. offensively - offensively 和 offensive 的形式相似，只是offensive加上"-ly"，可以快速判斷與攻擊相關；&lt;br&gt;9. augment - 拆解詞意即為增強&lt;br&gt;10. in large groups - 可以將"in"視為中文中的"在"，大家在组成群體時容易感到擁擠和“大”，相對地可以聯想到群體的意思。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;相似片語: &lt;br&gt;1. to choose from - 擇一 &lt;br&gt;2. advantages and disadvantages - 優缺點 &lt;br&gt;3. express uncertainty - 表示不確定 &lt;br&gt;4. up close and personal - 近距離戰鬥 &lt;br&gt;5. in relation to - 與…相關&lt;br&gt;6. to decline - 下降；拒絕&lt;br&gt;7. thankful for - 感恩的&lt;br&gt;8. in large numbers - 大量地&lt;br&gt;9. new at - 對某事物新手&lt;br&gt;10. give attention to - 專注於&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;反義片語：&lt;br&gt;1. pick and stick - 選擇一個點就固守，代表著事情只有一種選擇，容易記憶；&lt;br&gt;2. common benefits and drawbacks - 常見的利與弊；&lt;br&gt;3. express certainty - 表明確定；&lt;br&gt;4. from a distance - 距離較遠&lt;br&gt;5. out of context - 語境不符合；&lt;br&gt;6. to rise - 上升  &lt;br&gt;7. ungrateful for - 不能感激&lt;br&gt;8. in small groups - 小群體中&lt;br&gt;9. experienced at - 對某事物經驗豐富&lt;br&gt;10. look away from - 不專注於該事物</content><link href="https://www.gamespot.com/articles/diablo-4-best-classes-ranked-which-class-is-best-for-new-players/1100-6514708/" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>