<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><id>https://github.com/weg38asyy/GameRss.git</id><title>My Game Rss</title><updated>2023-06-09T13:12:04.495384+00:00</updated><author><name>Koala</name><email>weg38asyy@gmail.com</email></author><link href="https://github.com/weg38asyy" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Personal learning of English use</subtitle><entry><id>https://www.gamespot.com/articles/striking-league-of-legends-players-reach-agreement-with-riot-to-resume-season/1100-6515000/</id><title>Striking League Of Legends Players Reach Agreement With Riot To Resume Season</title><updated>2023-06-09T13:12:04.495658+00:00</updated><content type="html">After a player strike lasting almost two weeks the LCS Players Association, the representative body for professional League of Legends players in North America has announced that it has agreed on terms that will allow the season to resume on June 14. &lt;br&gt; The LCS summer season was delayed for two weeks from its original start date of June 1 in response to the player walkout, with Riot Games threatening to cancel the season--and the region's chance at Worlds--if an agreement could not be made. The LCSPA announced today that it has made that agreement, though it continues to negotiate on some key issues that haven't been resolved. &lt;br&gt; LCSPA, Riot, and LCS teams agree on terms to resume 2023 LCS season - talks to continue on unresolved issues pic.twitter.com/xodN7XABie &lt;br&gt; The terms it has agreed to are as follows: &lt;br&gt; The terms notably fall short of the initial demands made by the LCSPA, but still represent notable improvements to conditions for pro players in North America--especially the items mandating severance pay and healthcare for players. &lt;br&gt; "The concessions below do not return the NACL fully, nor do they provide restoration for the players who lost jobs suddenly and incurred financial hardship, lost visas, or broken leases," the LCSPA statement acknowledges. "The LCSPA is committed to continuing out pursuit of any and all potential paths towards making these players more whole." &lt;br&gt; As mentioned earlier in its statement, the strike itself is a monumental event, and the LCSPA reveals that over 90% of players voted to walkout. Players in the LCS, the highest level of competitive League of Legends in North America, put their own careers on the line to support up-and-coming players in the developmental NACL league in a historic show of solidarity.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;詳細句子文法解析：&lt;br&gt;1. After a player strike lasting almost two weeks the LCS Players Association, the representative body for professional League of Legends players in North America has announced that it has agreed on terms that will allow the season to resume on June 14.&lt;br&gt;    -&gt; 這個句子是一個復合句(complex sentence)，由after引導的時間狀語從句，及主句組成。&lt;br&gt;2. The LCS summer season was delayed for two weeks from its original start date of June 1 in response to the player walkout, with Riot Games threatening to cancel the season--and the region's chance at Worlds--if an agreement could not be made.&lt;br&gt;    -&gt; 這個句子是一個複合句，由with引導的方式狀語從句，及主句組成。&lt;br&gt;3. The LCSPA announced today that it has made that agreement, though it continues to negotiate on some key issues that haven't been resolved.&lt;br&gt;    -&gt; 這個句子是一個複合句，由though引導的轉折關係從句，及主句組成。&lt;br&gt;4. LCSPA, Riot, and LCS teams agree on terms to resume 2023 LCS season - talks to continue on unresolved issues pic.twitter.com/xodN7XABie&lt;br&gt;    -&gt; 這是一個將資訊以列點的方式(column)，敘述LCSPA和Riot達成協議，LCS的季賽可以繼續進行，但開未完成的問題則還需繼續協商。&lt;br&gt;5. The terms it has agreed to are as follows:&lt;br&gt;    -&gt;這是一個簡單句(simple sentence)，主語是the terms，行為動詞是it has agreed to，意思是有關協議的事項為如下。&lt;br&gt;6. The terms notably fall short of the initial demands made by the LCSPA, but still represent notable improvements to conditions for pro players in North America--especially the items mandating severance pay and healthcare for players.&lt;br&gt;    -&gt; 這是一個複合句，由but引導的轉折關係從句，及主句組成。&lt;br&gt;7. "The concessions below do not return the NACL fully, nor do they provide restoration for the players who lost jobs suddenly and incurred financial hardship, lost visas, or broken leases," the LCSPA statement acknowledges.&lt;br&gt;    -&gt; 這是一個複合句，由句子"The concessions below do not return the NACL fully, nor do they provide restoration for the players who lost jobs suddenly and incurred financial hardship, lost visas, or broken leases,"是LCSPA聲明表達的意思。&lt;br&gt;8. "The LCSPA is committed to continuing out pursuit of any and all potential paths towards making these players more whole."&lt;br&gt;    -&gt; 這是一個簡單句，中心思想是LCSPA承諾繼續追求所有潛在的路徑，使這些玩家更加完整。&lt;br&gt;9. As mentioned earlier in its statement, the strike itself is a monumental event, and the LCSPA reveals that over 90% of players voted to walkout.&lt;br&gt;    -&gt; 這是一個複合句，由as引導的原因關係從句及主句組成。&lt;br&gt;10. Players in the LCS, the highest level of competitive League of Legends in North America, put their own careers on the line to support up-and-coming players in the developmental NACL league in a historic show of solidarity.&lt;br&gt;    -&gt; 這是一個複合句，由to支配的不定式及主句組成。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;單字：&lt;br&gt;1. league(n.)：聯盟；聯賽；社團；協會&lt;br&gt;    -&gt;聯盟(n.)：れんめい [ren-mei]&lt;br&gt;2. mandating(v.) 要求；指示；命令；指令&lt;br&gt;    -&gt;命令する(v.)：めいれいする [mei-rei suru]&lt;br&gt;3. restoration(n.)：修復；恢復；復原；回復&lt;br&gt;    -&gt;修復する(v.)：しゅうふくする [shu-fuku suru]&lt;br&gt;4. notable(adj.)：顯著的；值得注意的；著名的；重要的&lt;br&gt;    -&gt;注意する(v.)：ちゅういする [chuui suru]；注目する(v.)：ちゅうもくする [chuumoku suru]&lt;br&gt;5. hardship(n.)：苦難；困苦；悲慘境遇；困境&lt;br&gt;    -&gt;困難(n.)：こんなん [kon-nan]；苦難(n.)：くなん [ku-nan]&lt;br&gt;6. monumental(adj.)：偉大的；巨大的；紀念碑式的&lt;br&gt;    -&gt;偉大的(adj.)：いだいてき [idai-teki]；巨大的(adj.)：きょだい [kyodai]&lt;br&gt;7. solidarity(n.)：團結；團結一致；團結救濟&lt;br&gt;    -&gt;團結(n.)：だんけつ [dan-ketsu]&lt;br&gt;8. league of legends(n.)：英雄聯盟(LoL)，是一款由暴雪娛樂負責開發，大陸由腾讯代理发行的英雄对战游戏.&lt;br&gt;    -&gt;英雄聯盟(n.)：えいゆうれんめい [ei-yuu ren-mei]&lt;br&gt;9. representative(adj.)：代表性的；典型的&lt;br&gt;   -&gt; 代表(n.)：だいひょう [dai-hyou]；代表する(v.)：だいひょうする [dai-hyou suru]&lt;br&gt;10. developmental(adj.)：發展上的；發展的；發達的&lt;br&gt;    -&gt;發展(n.)：はってん [hat-ten]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;片語：&lt;br&gt;1. Fall short of (未達到某項目標；未達到某種程度；未符合標準)&lt;br&gt;    -&gt; 相似片語： measure up to&lt;br&gt;    -&gt; 反義片語： meet up to&lt;br&gt;2. Put(sth.) on the line (以....為賭注；拿某物豁出去)&lt;br&gt;    -&gt; 相似片語： gamble on&lt;br&gt;    -&gt; 反義片語： play it safe &lt;br&gt;3. Walk out (罷工)&lt;br&gt;   -&gt; 相似片語： strike&lt;br&gt;   -&gt; 反義片語： work together &lt;br&gt;4. Agree on (達成共識；達成協議；意見一致)&lt;br&gt;   -&gt; 相似片語： come to terms with&lt;br&gt;   -&gt; 反義片語： dispute, disagree&lt;br&gt;5. Continue to (一直...；繼續...不間斷；將繼續)&lt;br&gt;   -&gt; 相似片語： keep on, carry on, persist in&lt;br&gt;   -&gt; 反義片語： cease, stop, discontinue &lt;br&gt;6. Give up (放棄某事；閉關修行)&lt;br&gt;   -&gt; 相似片語： abandon &lt;br&gt;   -&gt; 反義片語： keep up, persist &lt;br&gt;7. Put oneself on the line (冒著風險對抗某件事)&lt;br&gt;   -&gt; 相似片語： risk one's reputation, stick one's neck out &lt;br&gt;   -&gt; 反義片語： play it safe, stay out of trouble &lt;br&gt;8. Let go of (放開；釋放；放手)&lt;br&gt;   -&gt; 相似片語： release, relinquish&lt;br&gt;   -&gt; 反義片語： hold onto &lt;br&gt;9. Be committed to (致力於；投入)&lt;br&gt;    -&gt; 相似或更精確的短語：be dedicated to&lt;br&gt;    -&gt; 反義片語： cancel, withdraw&lt;br&gt;10. Fall into (陷於，掉入)&lt;br&gt;    -&gt; 相似片語：immerse oneself in, be trapped in&lt;br&gt;    -&gt; 反義片語：get out of, emerge from&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;備註：&lt;br&gt;在教學中，我會用繪圖、多感官記憶和實際運用的方法來提高學生的學習效果。將語言與同步圖像顯示相結合，讓學生有視覺化的參考。另外，透過情境式的練習活動進行授課，幫助學生理解語言的用法。例如將學生分組進行討論，學生可用所學知識進行部分練習，驗證自己的學習成果，並互相學習交流。這種練習過程能夠激發學生積極的學習態度, 進一步增強學生的學習成就感。</content><link href="https://www.gamespot.com/articles/striking-league-of-legends-players-reach-agreement-with-riot-to-resume-season/1100-6515000/" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>