<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><id>https://github.com/weg38asyy/GameRss.git</id><title>My Game Rss</title><updated>2023-03-26T19:44:29.338212+00:00</updated><author><name>Koala</name><email>weg38asyy@gmail.com</email></author><link href="https://github.com/weg38asyy" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Personal learning of English use</subtitle><entry><id>https://www.gamespot.com/articles/resident-evil-4-unlockable-costumes-weapons-guide/1100-6512582/</id><title>Resident Evil 4 - Unlockable Costumes And Bonus Weapons Guide</title><updated>2023-03-26T19:44:29.338354+00:00</updated><content type="html">Resident Evil 4 Remake has numerous goodies that you can unlock. However, several will require multiple completions, as well as a bit of know-how for more efficient clears. Here's our Resident Evil 4 unlockables guide to help you with all the weapons and costumes that you can obtain in the game. Our Resident Evil 4 unlockables guide takes a look at the different items that can be yours once you finish the game. All of these can be acquired via the main menu -&gt; Bonus Content -&gt; Extra Content Shop, where each selection costs Completion Points (i.e., what you earn when you complete challenges/achievements in the campaign). You may then equip these by clicking Main Story -&gt; Extras. Additionally, some rewards are further subdivided based on game modes and clear rankings (usually dependent on completion time). As such, you can't get everything in one go. Here's the gist: For instance, if you're attempting an S+ rank run, then you'll need to be very familiar with the game already. Knowing when to avoid enemies, and being able to clear the campaign as fast as possible would be the end goal. Moreover, since New Game+ isn't allowed, you'll have to start a fresh run without weapon upgrades or items that you've collected. However, some bonus weapons can be picked up from the storage, and they can be upgraded as you progress. Note that these weapons are earned through achieving certain in-game milestones. For the complete list of weapons you can purchase or otherwise find in Resident Evil 4 Remake, check out our guide to all Resident Evil 4 weapons. Most of these Resident Evil 4 Remake unlockable costumes and accessories simply require a regular campaign completion (i.e., any difficulty mode/no time limit). However, for others that might require something like "Hardcore mode or higher," you can pick Professional mode to grab those rewards, too. Leon Ashley Leon Ashley Resident Evil 4 has more mechanics and secrets for you to discover. You can learn more in our guides hub.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;句子文法解析：&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. "Resident Evil 4 Remake has numerous goodies that you can unlock."&lt;br&gt;這個句子使用了關係代名詞 "that" 來引導一個形容詞子句。這個子句說明了哪些物品可以被玩家解鎖。使用關係代名詞不僅可以讓句子更為簡潔，還可以用來表示兩個句子之間的關係。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. "Here's our Resident Evil 4 unlockables guide to help you with all the weapons and costumes that you can obtain in the game."&lt;br&gt;這個句子使用了 "to help you with" 這個不定詞片語表示目的。它說明了這個指南的目的是幫助玩家獲得遊戲中所有的武器和服裝。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. "Our Resident Evil 4 unlockables guide takes a look at the different items that can be yours once you finish the game."&lt;br&gt;這個句子使用了 "takes a look at" 這個片語表示動作，用來描述這個指南的內容，即它回顧了遊戲中可以在闖關後獲得的不同物品。該片語具有一般性，基本上可以用來描述任何一個探討題材的文章、視頻或指南。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;單字：&lt;br&gt;unlockables - 可解鎖的物品&lt;br&gt;completions - 完成；完結&lt;br&gt;efficiency - 效率&lt;br&gt;clears - 通關；清除&lt;br&gt;obtain - 獲得&lt;br&gt;main menu - 主菜單&lt;br&gt;bonus content - 獎勵內容&lt;br&gt;extra - 額外的；外加的&lt;br&gt;content - 內容&lt;br&gt;shop - 商店&lt;br&gt;completion points - 完成點數&lt;br&gt;campaign - 遊戲劇情&lt;br&gt;equip - 裝備&lt;br&gt;selection - 選擇&lt;br&gt;ranking - 排名&lt;br&gt;dependent - 依賴&lt;br&gt;weapon upgrades - 武器升級&lt;br&gt;bonus - 奬勵；獎金&lt;br&gt;storage - 儲藏室&lt;br&gt;in-game milestones - 遊戲里程碑&lt;br&gt;costumes - 服裝&lt;br&gt;accessories - 配件&lt;br&gt;mechanics - 遊戲機制&lt;br&gt;discovery - 發現&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;片語：&lt;br&gt;know-how - 專業技能；專門知識&lt;br&gt;derivative phrases - 衍生詞組&lt;br&gt;in one go - 一口氣&lt;br&gt;pick up - 撿起；拾起&lt;br&gt;regular completion - 普通完成&lt;br&gt;hardcore mode - 超級難度模式&lt;br&gt;no time limit - 無時間限制&lt;br&gt;Professional mode - 專業模式&lt;br&gt;hub - 指引中心；中心枢紐&lt;br&gt;secrets to discover - 奧秘可探&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;其它：&lt;br&gt;1. unlockables - 可以想像它就是「解鎖的東西」，可以聯想鑰匙 (keys)，只要有合適的鑰匙就可以打開神秘的門。日文單字為アンロッカブル (anrokkaburu)。&lt;br&gt;2. efficiency - 「效率」這個單字可以聯想成 "easy" (容易) 的反義詞，也就是說提高效率的意思就是讓事情不再繁瑣沉悶。日文單字為効率的意思則是「エフィシエンシー」(efishenshii)。&lt;br&gt;3. ranking - 「排名」這個詞可以想像成「排列然後編號到底是誰高分不須解釋」，以聯想成 "rank" (階級、地位) 的其他片語有 "higher rank" (高階) 和 "lower rank" (低階)。日文單字則為ランキング (rankingu)。&lt;br&gt;4. wardrobe - 「衣櫥」的意思可以聯想成「二男 Alesya，我還在想這件白色衣服放哪比較好呢」這種情節，以情感聯想幫助記憶。日文單詞是クローゼット (kuroozetto)。</content><link href="https://www.gamespot.com/articles/resident-evil-4-unlockable-costumes-weapons-guide/1100-6512582/" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>