<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><id>https://github.com/weg38asyy/GameRss.git</id><title>My Game Rss</title><updated>2023-05-17T19:56:44.211499+00:00</updated><author><name>Koala</name><email>weg38asyy@gmail.com</email></author><link href="https://github.com/weg38asyy" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Personal learning of English use</subtitle><entry><id>https://www.gamespot.com/articles/zelda-tears-of-the-kingdom-ekochiu-shrine-puzzle-guide/1100-6514254/</id><title>Zelda: Tears Of The Kingdom - Ekochiu Shrine Puzzle Guide</title><updated>2023-05-17T19:56:44.211605+00:00</updated><content type="html">The Legend of Zelda: Tears of the Kingdom Ekochiu Shrine Puzzle is a bit tricky and can be a tad confusing. You’ll need to combine a few abilities and have unlocked the Paraglider to solve the Rise and Fall puzzles. Here’s how to complete the Ekochiu Shrine puzzle. &lt;br&gt; The Zelda: Tears of the Kingdom Ekochiu Shrine is found in the Great Hyrule Forest region. The Rise and Fall puzzles will task you with using your Rewind and Ultrahand ability, along with your Paraglider, to make it through the Shrine. &lt;br&gt; As you head inside the Ekochiu Shrine, you’ll see a large gap that you need to cross. Simply stand on the button to push the block to the other side and wait for it to come back. &lt;br&gt; Once it's back, hop on the block and use your Rewind ability to get to the other side. In the next room, you’ll see a moving body of water and a big box that’s dropped from the upper ledge. There is also a hidden chest in this room. &lt;br&gt; To get the chest, use your Ultrahand ability to move the box to the ledge on the right side. You’ll want to prop the box up so that it's not completely in the water, otherwise, it’ll move with the current. &lt;br&gt; Climb on top of the box and hop on the ledge to get the chest. Inside, you’ll find a Level 11 Zonaite Shield. &lt;br&gt; Now that you’ve gotten the chest, hop back into the water and move the box over to the far ledge. With your Ultrahand, move the box from the water to the top of the ledge and then back down. &lt;br&gt; Then, climb on top of the box and use your Rewind ability and the box will lift you up to the top of the ledge. &lt;br&gt; For the last puzzle in the Ekochiu Shrine, you’ll find another big cube in the back right corner. Place the cube onto the platform by the fence and then climb the ladder to get back on top of the ledge. &lt;br&gt; Stand on the button to launch the box up in the air. Once it’s back, jump down and climb on top of the box. Then, use your Rewind ability to shoot the box back up in the air. &lt;br&gt; When the box is high enough, jump off and use your Paraglider to get to the other side. Once you make it across, claim your Light of Blessing and you’ll have completed the Ekochiu Shrine in Zelda: Tears of the Kingdom. &lt;br&gt; We have many more guides in our Tears of the Kingdom guides hub, including a map of all Shrine locations and more individual Shrine puzzle guides.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;詳細句子文法解析：&lt;br&gt;1. The Legend of Zelda: Tears of the Kingdom Ekochiu Shrine Puzzle is a bit tricky and can be a tad confusing. &lt;br&gt;- "is a bit tricky"為定語從句修飾主詞"Puzzle"，表示拼圖有一些困難；"and can be a tad confusing"為連接詞起轉折作用，表示拼圖也有一些困惑之處。&lt;br&gt;2. You'll need to combine a few abilities and have unlocked the Paraglider to solve the Rise and Fall puzzles. &lt;br&gt;- "You'll need to"為情態動詞，表示必須做某事，後接原型動詞"combine"；"and have unlocked the Paraglider" 為並列結構，表示需要解鎖滑翔傘。&lt;br&gt;3. Here's how to complete the Ekochiu Shrine puzzle. &lt;br&gt;- "Here's how"為引導句式，表示要說明該怎麼完成Ekochiu Shrine的挑戰。&lt;br&gt;4. The Zelda: Tears of the Kingdom Ekochiu Shrine is found in the Great Hyrule Forest region. &lt;br&gt;- "is found"為被動語態，表示位於哪裡。&lt;br&gt;5. The Rise and Fall puzzles will task you with using your Rewind and Ultrahand ability, along with your Paraglider, to make it through the Shrine. &lt;br&gt;- "will task you with"為以will為基礎的情態語氣，表示會要求你使用...；"to make it through"為帶有固定詞組make it的片語，表示從...經過。&lt;br&gt;6. Simply stand on the button to push the block to the other side and wait for it to come back. &lt;br&gt;- "Simply"為副詞，表示行動簡單無難度；"to push"為不定詞修飾"stand"，表示站在按鈕上使方塊落下。&lt;br&gt;7. Once it's back, hop on the block and use your Rewind ability to get to the other side. &lt;br&gt;- "Once it's back"為倒裝句，表示方塊回來之後，後面的句子就能被展開；"to get to"為用來表達目的的片語，表示為了到達另一側，要使用Rewind能力。&lt;br&gt;8. In the next room, you'll see a moving body of water and a big box that's dropped from the upper ledge. There is also a hidden chest in this room. &lt;br&gt;- "In the next room"為前置詞片語，表示下一個房間會有...&lt;br&gt;9. To get the chest, use your Ultrahand ability to move the box to the ledge on the right side. &lt;br&gt;- "To get the chest"為不定詞片語，表示為了拿到寶箱而採取的行動；"on the right side"為介系詞片語修飾"ledge"，指的是右邊的邊緣。&lt;br&gt;10. Then, climb on top of the box and use your Rewind ability and the box will lift you up to the top of the ledge. &lt;br&gt;- "Then"為副詞，表示按照先前的步驟之後；"climb on top of the box"為句子的核心關鍵詞，表示要先攀爬方塊。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;單字：&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. Shrine - n. 神社(shên jià)&lt;br&gt;2. Puzzle - n. 拼圖(pîn tú)&lt;br&gt;3. Combine - v. 結合(jié hé)&lt;br&gt;    *拆解後詞彙聯想：come+bine=聚在一起&lt;br&gt;4. Ultrahand - n. 超級手(bàng zhăng shôu)&lt;br&gt;5. Unlock - v. 解鎖(jiê suô)&lt;br&gt;    *拆解後詞彙聯想：un+lock=破解鎖頭&lt;br&gt;6. Paraglider - n. 滑翔傘(húá xiáng sân)&lt;br&gt;7. Symmetrical - adj. 對稱的(duì chèn de)&lt;br&gt;    *拆解後詞彙聯想：same+metrical=相同的尺寸&lt;br&gt;8. Ledge - n. 棚架(péng jià)&lt;br&gt;    *拆解後詞彙聯想：high+ledge=高地&lt;br&gt;9. Prop - v. 支撐(zhī chēng)&lt;br&gt;    *英文諧音：pick up your prop=拿起你的道具&lt;br&gt;10. Blessing - n. 祝福(zhù fú)&lt;br&gt;    *拆解後詞彙聯想：bliss+ing=幸福的過程中&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;片語：&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. Make it through - 完成(wán chéng) &lt;br&gt;    *相似片語：get through=闖過去&lt;br&gt;    *反義片語：give up=放棄&lt;br&gt;2. In the back right corner - 在右後方角落(zài yòu hòu fāng jiǎo luò)&lt;br&gt;    *相似片語：in the front left corner=在左前方角落&lt;br&gt;    *反義片語：in the center=在中央&lt;br&gt;3. Drop from - 從...落下(cnóng...lùò xià)&lt;br&gt;    *相似片語：fall from=從...落下來&lt;br&gt;    *反義片語：lift up=舉起來&lt;br&gt;4. A bit tricky - 有點棘手(yǒu diǎn jí shǒu)&lt;br&gt;    *相似片語：slightly difficult=稍微困難&lt;br&gt;    *反義片語：super easy=非常容易 &lt;br&gt;5. To the other side - 到另一側(dào lìng yì zhōu)&lt;br&gt;    *相似片語：To the opposite side=到正相對的地方&lt;br&gt;    *反義片語：stay on the same side=待在同一側 &lt;br&gt;6. Hidden chest - 隱藏的寶箱(yǐn cáng de bǎo xiāng)&lt;br&gt;    *相似片語：secret treasure=神秘的寶藏&lt;br&gt;    *反義片語：public property=公開物產 &lt;br&gt;7. Stand on the button - 站在按鈕上(zhàn zài àn niǔn shàng)&lt;br&gt;    *相似片語：sit on the chair=坐在椅子上&lt;br&gt;    *反義片語：walk away=離開 &lt;br&gt;8. Move the box to - 把箱子移到(bǎ xiāng zǐ dào huó)&lt;br&gt;    *相似片語：carry the bag to=攜帶包包到&lt;br&gt;    *反義片語：remove the box from=從中移除盒子。&lt;br&gt;9. A tad confusing - 有點困惑(yǒu diǎn kùn huò)&lt;br&gt;    *相似片語：a little ambiguous=有一點疑問&lt;br&gt;    *反義片語：very clear=非常清晰 &lt;br&gt;10. Lift you up - 抬起來(tái qǐ lái) &lt;br&gt;     *相似片語：raise you up=舉起你&lt;br&gt;    *反義片語：drag you down=拖你下去</content><link href="https://www.gamespot.com/articles/zelda-tears-of-the-kingdom-ekochiu-shrine-puzzle-guide/1100-6514254/" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>