<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><id>https://github.com/weg38asyy/GameRss.git</id><title>My Game Rss</title><updated>2023-03-30T13:10:59.650351+00:00</updated><author><name>Koala</name><email>weg38asyy@gmail.com</email></author><link href="https://github.com/weg38asyy" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Personal learning of English use</subtitle><entry><id>https://www.gamespot.com/articles/fortnite-fans-are-nostalgic-for-when-the-game-was-clearly-worse/1100-6512814/</id><title>Fortnite Fans Are Nostalgic For When The Game Was Clearly Worse</title><updated>2023-03-30T13:10:59.650629+00:00</updated><content type="html">Unreal Editor for Fortnite is finally here. And while over time this will change Fortnite into something that is so far beyond the Fortnite that we know today, nothing really has changed just yet. The beginning of Creative 2.0 is just a nicer version of Creative 1.0, if we're being honest. The future is extremely exciting, but it's going to take a while for folks to take full advantage of the UEFN. &lt;br&gt; While we wait for that future to arrive, the talk of the town has been two attempts to use UEFN to recreate Fortnite's Battle Royale island as it existed in Chapter 1 Season 3. Longtime Fortnite players have been in a tizzy over these, excited to usher in a new era of Old Fortnite. That new era will never actually happen, though, because the game was worse in every way and can't actually be fully restored anyway. &lt;br&gt; The first of these retro maps, Atlas Creative's Atlas OG Battle Royale, was a disastrous janky mess when it went live alongside the debut of Creative 2.0--though the Atlas folks have stabilized the map pretty well now. The second, Reboot Royale, launched a few days later and looks much nicer, but significant sacrifices were made to keep the map under the memory limit. But these are the first-ever attempts to build maps on this scale in Fortnite Creative, so some amount of jank is to be expected. &lt;br&gt; I only started playing Fortnite during Chapter 2, so I do appreciate having the chance to experience firsthand what I had only been able to see in YouTube videos. But for me, that's where the enjoyment ends--the Chapter 1 version of Fortnite's Battle Royale plays worse than the version we have now, on a map that's much worse than the one we have now, and these maps do not actually recreate the experience of playing Fortnite back then because none of the guns work the same way they did then. But that's okay. These Chapter 1 re-dos are more of a fun diversion than an actual attempt to replace the current version of Battle Royale, right? &lt;br&gt; Right? &lt;br&gt; For some folks, maybe not. There has been plenty of chatter among the Fortnite old-timers about how they can finally play the old, good version of Battle Royale, from back before it was tainted by…whatever it is they think has ruined Fortnite over the years. Their nostalgia mode is fully engaged. &lt;br&gt; I doubt anybody considers either of the new Chapter 1 maps to be real threats to the supremacy of Fortnite's main Battle Royale modes--they just aren't put together well enough, because even the new, much higher memory limit creators have with UEFN isn't enough to allow a true, full 1:1 recreation of any Fortnite island. Or at least they haven't figured out how yet. &lt;br&gt; They also can't revert the gameplay to what it was. Every gun is balanced differently than it used to be. Building mechanics are far more advanced and faster now than they were early in Chapter 1. &lt;br&gt; And so try as they might, there's no version of this where Atlas or Reboot Royale are ever able to recreate that Fortnite Chapter 1 feel for real. But even if they did, would that even be a good thing? As is the case with most live-service games, Fortnite has gotten tons of quality-of-life improvements over the years that make its baseline experience much more pleasant. While these folks can disable, for example, sprinting, sliding, and mantling on their OG maps, those features are pretty hard to give up after having them in the game for over a year. &lt;br&gt; Despite that reality, even now those Fortnite old-timers--many of whom grew up on Fortnite--are dialing up their nostalgia meters to 11 over these Chapter 1 maps. I get it. These folks have been embroiled in this FOMO-heavy ecosystem for a long time, and they simultaneously have one foot out the door and the other still logging in daily to collect their Founders V-Bucks from Save The World. For some,they're pretty much over Fortnite, but they're hooked from having invested so much time (and money) in it. They hope that these OG maps will get them back into it. &lt;br&gt; But, as is always the case with nostalgia, what these folks really want on a deeper level is to actually time travel back to Chapter 1 and re-experience it for the first time. And that won't ever happen. A hacked-together partial physical recreation of an old map might bring back those past vibes for a moment, but they'll fade sooner than later. &lt;br&gt; Because you can't truly be young again--you can only try to delude yourself into thinking you are. And these Chapter 1 maps are nothing more than fun little glimpses of the past to enjoy while Epic continues to perpetually invent the future. &lt;br&gt;  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;詳細句子文法解析：&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. "Unreal Editor for Fortnite is finally here." 為主語 + be 動詞 + 現在分詞的組合，表示「某件事情（Unreal Editor）現在已經到達了某種狀態（finally here）」的意思。&lt;br&gt;重點：現在分詞為被動語態時可代替被動語態，本文以「finally here」的現在完成式為主語的補語。&lt;br&gt;2. "While over time this will change Fortnite into something that is so far beyond the Fortnite that we know today, nothing really has changed just yet." "While" 引導的子句為時間狀語從句，逗號後的主句表示目前還沒有到達某種狀態。&lt;br&gt;重點：時間狀語從句的用法，表示「某件事情在某個時候會發生」的意思。&lt;br&gt;3. "The beginning of Creative 2.0 is just a nicer version of Creative 1.0, if we're being honest." if 引導的條件狀語從句，表示在某個假設條件下會發生什麼事情。&lt;br&gt;重點：條件狀語從句的用法，表示「如果某個條件成立，會發生什麼事情」的意思。&lt;br&gt;4. "Longtime Fortnite players have been in a tizzy over these, excited to usher in a new era of Old Fortnite." 本句為含有現在完成式的表原因的句子，強調現在完成後的結果。&lt;br&gt;重點：現在完成式+表原因的句子，用來表示一個前因後果的關係。&lt;br&gt;5. "That new era will never actually happen, though, because the game was worse in every way and can't actually be fully restored anyway." 句子含有因果關係，前面為因果，後面為結果。&lt;br&gt;重點：因果關係句中要小心逗點位置的放置使得句意清楚。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;單字：&lt;br&gt;1. Supremacy: 最高優勢、至高無上&lt;br&gt;提醒：可聯想到「至上」的意思。&lt;br&gt;2. Perpetually: 持續地、永恆不變地&lt;br&gt;提醒：可聯想到「永久」或「一直都」的意思。&lt;br&gt;3. Delude: 欺騙、哄騙、迷惑&lt;br&gt;提醒：可聯想到「De」表示否定，「lud」則與delusion（迷惑）有同源的詞源。&lt;br&gt;4. Tainted: 受污染的、受損的&lt;br&gt;提醒：可聯想到「contaminated（被汙染）」的意思。&lt;br&gt;5. Janky: 略有缺陷的、不穩定的&lt;br&gt;提醒：此單字較非正式，意為「意外故障的、功能不太穩定的」。&lt;br&gt;6. Founders: 創始者、創始人&lt;br&gt;提醒：可聯想到「開創自己的事業」的意思。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;片語：&lt;br&gt;1. Talk of the town: 全城熱話、街談巷議&lt;br&gt;相似片語：buzz around town（全城傳遞的消息）&lt;br&gt;反義片語：no talk of the town（沒有談論到的話題）&lt;br&gt;2. Hooked on: 被迷住、沉迷於…&lt;br&gt;相似片語：addicted to…（對…上了癮）&lt;br&gt;反義片語：uninterested in…（對…不感興趣）&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;其它：&lt;br&gt;1. Supremacy: 最高優勢、至高無上&lt;br&gt;日文單字：至上感&lt;br&gt;提示：透過轉換將 supremacy 轉換成中文為「最高優勢」，再翻譯成日文則為「至上感」，以聯想方式記憶。&lt;br&gt;2. Perpetually: 持續地、永恆不變地&lt;br&gt;日文單字：永遠に&lt;br&gt;提示：利用註音，將 perpetually 轉為 pèi tǎ pū lì，然後音譯成日文即為「永遠に」，以聯想方式記憶。&lt;br&gt;3. Janky: 略有缺陷的、不穩定的&lt;br&gt;日文單字：トラブりやすい&lt;br&gt;提示：透過轉換將 janky 轉換成中文為「發生故障的概率較高」，再翻譯成日文即為「トラブりやすい」，以聯想方式記憶。&lt;br&gt;4. Founders: 創始者、創始人&lt;br&gt;日文單字: 創立者（chòu lì zhě）&lt;br&gt;提示：可將 founders 轉換成中文為「創立者」，再轉為日文則為「創立者（chòu lì zhě）」，以聯想方式記憶。</content><link href="https://www.gamespot.com/articles/fortnite-fans-are-nostalgic-for-when-the-game-was-clearly-worse/1100-6512814/" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>