<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><id>https://github.com/weg38asyy/GameRss.git</id><title>My Game Rss</title><updated>2023-06-05T13:12:07.123332+00:00</updated><author><name>Koala</name><email>weg38asyy@gmail.com</email></author><link href="https://github.com/weg38asyy" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Personal learning of English use</subtitle><entry><id>https://www.gamespot.com/articles/diablo-4-secret-of-the-spring-side-quest-and-emote-guide/1100-6514781/</id><title>Diablo 4 - Secret Of The Spring Side Quest And Emote Guide</title><updated>2023-06-05T13:12:07.123592+00:00</updated><content type="html">Diablo 4 is full of side quests, and while many of them simply ask you to mow down the forces of Hell, some of them require a bit more thought. One of those is a side quest called "Secret of the Spring" which can be found just north of the first major hub city Kyovashad. This quest is started when you find a small note with a riddle on it. Here's how to complete it. &lt;br&gt; First, you will need to collect the riddle note that starts the quest off. This note can be found north of Kyovashad near the entrance to the Forsaken Quarry dungeon, marked on the map above by the red circle. The quickest path here is to leave the city via the east exit and stick to the end of the map heading north. Once you find the note, the quest will start marking a small area on the map further north from where the note was found. &lt;br&gt; The note itself reads "Beacon of warmth in winter's embrace, patience rewarded by nature's own grace." Once you reach the location indicated on the map, you will find a small pool of water, which is the spring in the name of the quest. Like some other side quests in Diablo 4, you need to use a specific emote here. What might be confusing to some is that the "patience" noted in the riddle doesn't match anything in the default emote wheel. &lt;br&gt; Instead, open the emote wheel and press the button for Customize and go down the list of unassigned emotes until you find the one labeled Wait. Add the Wait emote to your wheel and then use it next to the spring to spawn a chest. The chest only contained gold and resources for me, but that could vary person to person. The quest completes once you open up the chest. &lt;br&gt; For more information about Diablo 4, like class or dungeon guides, check out GameSpot's Diablo 4 Guides Hub.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;詳細句子文法解析：&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. "Diablo 4 is full of side quests, and while many of them simply ask you to mow down the forces of Hell, some of them require a bit more thought." - 這個句子使用"while"來表示對比，表達了一個事物在一個環境中的兩個不同屬性。使用對比詞語可以幫助增強表達的清楚度。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. "One of those is a side quest called "Secret of the Spring" which can be found just north of the first major hub city Kyovashad." - 這個句子使用"which"來連接前後句子，表達了一個關於"Secret of the Spring"這個主題的新篇章。使用關聯代詞可以幫助表達的流暢度。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. "This quest is started when you find a small note with a riddle on it." - 這個句子使用"when"來表示一個事件的開始。使用時間詞語可以幫助說明事件的起因和結果。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. "The quickest path here is to leave the city via the east exit and stick to the end of the map heading north." - 這個句子使用"the"來強調相對應的對象，幫助確定路線和方向。使用限定詞可以幫助表達更精確的訊息。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. "Once you find the note, the quest will start marking a small area on the map further north from where the note was found." - 這個句子使用"once"來表達一個條件成立即出現的結果。使用時間詞語可以幫助確認特定事件發生的先後關係。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;6. "The note itself reads "Beacon of warmth in winter's embrace, patience rewarded by nature's own grace."" - 這個句子使用"itself"強調某個對象，幫助讀者理解到重要的訊息是什麼。使用強調詞語可以幫助說明特定的內容或訊息。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;7. "Once you reach the location indicated on the map, you will find a small pool of water, which is the spring in the name of the quest." - 這個句子使用"which"來指代之前提到過的對象，幫助確認讀者正在對講的內容或場景。使用關聯代詞可以幫助表達的流暢度。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;8. "Like some other side quests in Diablo 4, you need to use a specific emote here." - 這個句子使用"like"來比較兩個不同事物的相似之處，可以幫助讀者更具體地了解整個情境。使用比較詞語可以增強表達的精確度。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;9. "Instead, open the emote wheel and press the button for Customize and go down the list of unassigned emotes until you find the one labeled Wait." - 這個句子使用"and"來串聯兩個平行的動作，幫助讀者更清楚地了解該步驟的操作流程。使用連接詞可以幫助說明多個事件之間的相關性。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;10. "The quest completes once you open up the chest." - 這個句子使用"once"來表示一個條件符合時的結果，幫助確認任務結束的準確時機。使用時間詞語可以幫助理解整個過程中各個階段和步驟之間的關係。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;單字：&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. Side quests - 側翼任務&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Hub city - 中樞城市&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. Dungeon - 地牢&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. Riddle - 謎語&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. Quickest - 最快的&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;6. Note - 筆記&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;7. Pool - 水池&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;8. Emote - 表情符號&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;9. Customize - 定製&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;10. Unassigned - 未分配的&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;容易記住的方法：&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. 側翼任務 - 「side」指側邊，經常跟主要任務相對而言&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. 中樞城市 - 「hub」和「spoke」的比喻，即中央部件和輻條形成的系統&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. 地牢 - 發音跟「捏豆」有點像&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. 謎語 - 發音跟「me」和「do」有點像，可以聯想為需要你自己來解決&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. 最快的 - 快的可以聯想為「quick」，再加上最高級的表達&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;6. 筆記 - 類似於notebook的縮寫，可以轉化為「筆手舞」&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;7. 水池 - 水的讀音為「shui」，聲韻接近於池&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;8. 表情符號 - 表情可以聯想為「emotion」，符號可以聯想為「signal」&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;9. 定製 - 可以轉化為「customize」，意指「客製化」&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;10. 未分配的 - 「unassigned」的前綴「un-」表示負面含義，再加上「assigned」（分配）的意思，可以聯想為「尚未分配」的狀態。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;片語：&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;相似片語：Reward by - 獲得回報&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;反義片語：Lose patience - 失去耐性</content><link href="https://www.gamespot.com/articles/diablo-4-secret-of-the-spring-side-quest-and-emote-guide/1100-6514781/" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>