<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><id>https://github.com/weg38asyy/GameRss.git</id><title>My Game Rss</title><updated>2023-04-25T13:13:00.835159+00:00</updated><author><name>Koala</name><email>weg38asyy@gmail.com</email></author><link href="https://github.com/weg38asyy" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Personal learning of English use</subtitle><entry><id>https://www.gamespot.com/articles/build-your-own-10-bundle-with-7-steam-games/1100-6513510/</id><title>Build-Your-Own $10 Bundle With 7 Steam Games</title><updated>2023-04-25T13:13:00.835317+00:00</updated><content type="html">Over at Fanatical, you can grab up to  seven PC games for as little as $1.43 each  with the Build Your Own Trinity bundle deal. The bundle comes in three options, starting at $5 for three games, then moving up to $8 for five games, and $10 for seven games. &lt;br&gt; Like other Fanatical build-your-own deals, you get to pick which games you want in your bundle, selecting from a list of 16 possible titles. This particular batch include first-person shooters like  Homefront: The Revolution  and  Painkiller: Black Edition,  and RPGs like  Tokyo Xanadu eX+  and  Zengeon.  &lt;br&gt; Racing games and vehicle simulators also make up nearly half of the list of possible games, including the retro-styled  Super Indie Karts,  combat racer  Crashday Redline Edition,  and minimalist F1 sim  Race Condition,  just to name a few. There are also visual novels, arcade action games, and open-world survival titles to pick from. The full list of games is listed below. &lt;br&gt; All bundles also come with a 5%-off coupon code that you can use on other Fanatical orders. All games in the bundle are delivered as Steam keys, and some of the games are confirmed to work on Steam Deck. Head over to Fanatical to start customizing your Trinity bundle now, and be sure to check out some of the other deals available, including this massive sale that sees hundreds of indie PC games discounted by up to 80%. &lt;br&gt;  Zengeon  &lt;br&gt; Best Gaming &amp; Tech Deals This Week&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;詳細句子文法解析：&lt;br&gt;1. "Over at Fanatical, you can grab up to seven PC games for as little as $1.43 each with the Build Your Own Trinity bundle deal." -&gt; 這裡使用了介係詞片語 "Over at"，表示 "在...這裡"，強調定位和位置。"as little as" 則是一個比較細微的用法，表示一個小的數量。 &lt;br&gt;2. "The bundle comes in three options, starting at $5 for three games, then moving up to $8 for five games, and $10 for seven games." -&gt; 這個句子使用了動詞不定式片語 "starting at"，表示一個起始價格。接著使用了 "then moving up to"，表示逐漸上漲。&lt;br&gt;3. "Like other Fanatical build-your-own deals, you get to pick which games you want in your bundle, selecting from a list of 16 possible titles." -&gt; "Like" 是一個引出比較片語的單詞，表示 "像..." 這個做法和其他的 "Fanatical build-your-own deals"非常像，都是由消費者選擇商品。&lt;br&gt;4. "This particular batch include first-person shooters like Homefront: The Revolution and Painkiller: Black Edition, and RPGs like Tokyo Xanadu eX+ and Zengeon." -&gt; 使用了介係詞片語 "like"，表示 "像..."。除此之外，該句也使用了泛指的詞語 “batch”(批次)，表示物品種類眾多。&lt;br&gt;5. "Racing games and vehicle simulators also make up nearly half of the list of possible games, including the retro-styled Super Indie Karts, combat racer Crashday Redline Edition, and minimalist F1 sim Race Condition, just to name a few." -&gt; 在這個句子中使用了動詞 "make up"，意思是 "組成(一部分)；占 (一定量)"。 "Including" 表示 "包括"，其中 "just to name a few" 則是一個簡短的用語，強調只是挑選了其中幾個樣品。&lt;br&gt;6. "There are also visual novels, arcade action games, and open-world survival titles to pick from." -&gt; 在這個簡單的句型中，使用了不定冠詞 "a(n)"，和"to pick from"，表示存在多個選項可以供消費者考慮。&lt;br&gt;7. "The full list of games is listed below." -&gt; 使用了名詞冠詞 "The"，強調了 "list of games" 這個具體的東西。同時使用了同形詞 (is listed and list) 用於表強調，也是精確表達用法的體現之一。&lt;br&gt;8. "-&gt; All bundles also come with a 5%-off coupon code that you can use on other Fanatical orders." -&gt; 連接詞 "also"，表 linked 不相關（非因果）連接。"Coupon code"是一個固定短語，表示產品優惠券。&lt;br&gt;9. "All games in the bundle are delivered as Steam keys, and some of the games are confirmed to work on Steam Deck." -&gt; 著重了另一個產品：Steam\ Deck，暗示部分遊戲需要另一個產品才能玩到的概念。&lt;br&gt;10. "Head over to Fanatical to start customizing your Trinity bundle now, and be sure to check out some of the other deals available, including this massive sale that sees hundreds of indie PC games discounted by up to 80%." -&gt; "Be sure to"表示 "務必"， "Including"表示 "包括；不排除"等事後修飾詞。此段強烈鼓勵消費者購買，並提供豐富選擇多元優惠。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;單字：&lt;br&gt;1. Fanatical (英音: ˌfa'nætɪkl) / 狂熱者 / 狂信者.&lt;br&gt;2. Trinity (英音: ˈtrɪnəti) / 三位一體 / 三人一組.&lt;br&gt;3. bundle (n.) ( 英音: ˈbʌndl ) (v.) ( 英音: ˈbʌndl) / 捆、包裹；打包販賣 / 包裹、打成一系列。&lt;br&gt;4. grab ( 英音: ɡræb ) / 攫取。&lt;br&gt;5. shooter ( 英音:ˈʃuːtə(r) ) / 射擊遊戲 / 拍攝人員。&lt;br&gt;6. RPG ( 英音: ˌærpiːˈdʒiː ) / 角色扮演遊戲 / 現任總理任期。&lt;br&gt;7. visual novel ( 英音:  ˈvɪʒuəl ˈnɒvl) / 視覺小說 /小冊子;小品文。&lt;br&gt;8. survival ( 英音:səˈvaɪvl ) / 生存類型遊戲 / 倖存；熬過。&lt;br&gt;9. coupon code (¥6389B9F0FD53195F07) / 優惠券碼&lt;br&gt;10. retail price / 零售價&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;典型片語：&lt;br&gt;1. 相似：Pick and choose、Bulk buying、Game deals、&lt;br&gt;2. 反義：Full price、Pay by installment、Limited edition、Sold separately。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;日文單字：&lt;br&gt;1. Fanatical (フナティカル) /狂信的（な）/ 精神病的 、狂信者.&lt;br&gt;2. Trinity ( トリニティ) / 三位一体。&lt;br&gt;3. bundle ( バンドル) /（物が）束ねられた[詰め合わせの]もの、パッケージ / 強く縛る、束縛する；（女子児童を男装にさせる目的で）髪を整えてターバンをする。&lt;br&gt;4. grab ( グラブ) / ぽんとつかむ、つかみ取る / 【- A】（チャンス・機会を）つかむ、ゲットする。&lt;br&gt;5. shooter (シューティング) / 射撃ゲーム、射撃シュミレーター /脱輪しょう兵器.&lt;br&gt;6. RPG ( ロール・プレイング) / ロールプレイングゲーム、シミュレーションゲーム。&lt;br&gt;7. visual novel (ビジュアルノベル) / ビジュアルノベル、ビジュゲー / イラストが印象的な小説風アドベンチャーゲームのサブジャンル。&lt;br&gt;8. survival (サバイバル) / サバイバル[生存]ゲーム、サバイバル・アドベンチャー; 過酷な状況下での生存.&lt;br&gt;9. coupon code (クーポンコード) / クーポン番号、優待券番号。&lt;br&gt;10. retail price ( 小売価格 ) / 通常価格,普通の売価。</content><link href="https://www.gamespot.com/articles/build-your-own-10-bundle-with-7-steam-games/1100-6513510/" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>