<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><id>https://github.com/weg38asyy/GameRss.git</id><title>My Game Rss</title><updated>2023-05-13T13:12:30.040434+00:00</updated><author><name>Koala</name><email>weg38asyy@gmail.com</email></author><link href="https://github.com/weg38asyy" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Personal learning of English use</subtitle><entry><id>https://www.gamespot.com/articles/zelda-tears-of-the-kingdom-ganondorf-final-boss-guide/1100-6514051/</id><title>Zelda: Tears Of The Kingdom - How To Beat The Final Boss</title><updated>2023-05-13T13:12:30.040700+00:00</updated><content type="html">The Legend of Zelda: Tears of the Kingdom final boss is someone that long-time fans should be familiar with. This time, an old rival has a few tricks up his sleeve. Here's our guide to help you beat the final boss in Zelda: Tears of the Kingdom. Naturally, this article contains major spoilers. &lt;br&gt; The Legend of Zelda: Tears of the Kingdom Ganondorf final boss is no longer the mummified version from the intro, nor is he the Phantom Specter that you saw in Hyrule Castle. This time, he's beefed up considerably, and he's going to test your mettle. &lt;br&gt; All of Ganondorf's attacks cause the Gloom affliction, so make sure you've got Sundelion-based meals to cleanse the debuff when necessary. Oh, and we have to mention, this is a boss battle with three and a half phases. If you want, you can take photos of each of his forms so they can be added to your compendium. &lt;br&gt; Note: We recommend placing a Travel Medallion in Hyrule Depths just before the Demon King's Army battle. Once you finish that, you'll be sent straight to Ganondorf's cavern, and it's no longer possible to save nor fast travel while you're there. As such, make sure you've got everything you need, such as the Master Sword. If you feel like you forgot some stuff, you'll have no choice but to load an earlier save and redo the Demon King's Army encounter. &lt;br&gt; Ganondorf has the following attacks, which will change based on the weapon that he's using: &lt;br&gt; Moreover, he will dodge every normal melee attack you do. You can only deal damage if you shoot him with arrows (minimal) or do a perfect dodge to follow up with a Flurry Rush (effective). &lt;br&gt; We recommend equipping weapon fuses with high attack ratings, or the Master Sword with a high-tier fuse material. A Mighty Zonaite Shield combined with another shield may also be viable for defense, in case you miss your chance to dodge. &lt;br&gt; After whittling down his HP, Ganondorf will switch to the second phase of the fight. This time, he'll summon the Phantom Ganon versions. The good news is that your Sage companions will distract most of them, so you'll probably deal with only one at a time (unless you unluckily aggro others). As usual, wait for the Sword Lunge, then dodge and Flurry Rush to counter. &lt;br&gt; After all the Phantom Ganons are dead, it's time for the next portion of this phase. We feel that this is the toughest part of the Zelda: Tears of the Kingdom Ganondorf final boss encounter, as he either retains or boosts his abilities. Moreover, all your Sage companions will be stunned for the remainder of the battle. &lt;br&gt; There are also a few important things to take note of: &lt;br&gt; After depleting Ganondorf's HP, another cutscene will play. He'll eat his Secret Stone and transform into a Demon Dragon. Despite his ominous nature, this is probably the easiest phase of the Zelda: Tears of the Kingdom final boss encounter. &lt;br&gt; Here's what happens: &lt;br&gt; At the very end, the Demon Dragon's Secret Stone on its forehead will glow. Dive to it, then destroy it with the Master Sword. This will annihilate your foe. And that's it, you've beaten the Zelda: Tears of the Kingdom Ganondorf final boss encounter. The campaign has been concluded, but you might want to check out if you got the true ending. &lt;br&gt; There are numerous mechanics and facets to learn in The Legend of Zelda: Tears of the Kingdom. For more information, you can visit our guides hub.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;詳細句子文法解析：&lt;br&gt;1. "This time, an old rival has a few tricks up his sleeve." &lt;br&gt;使用了 "has a few tricks up his sleeve" 這個片語，意思是指某個人或事情有一些變化或驚喜可以出現，就像在 ((手袖子)) 裡藏著一些特別的玩意一樣。這個片語主要是指這位老對手有了新的戰鬥方式。&lt;br&gt;2. "Naturally, this article contains major spoilers." &lt;br&gt;使用了 "contains" 這個動詞，表示某些東西(這裡是指劇情的劇透)被包含在文章中。"Naturally" 則是指當然會包含劇透，因為在介紹如何戰勝最後的關卡時難免會提到遊戲的情節發展。&lt;br&gt;3. "Once you finish that, you'll be sent straight to Ganondorf's cavern, and it's no longer possible to save nor fast travel while you're there." &lt;br&gt;在這個句子裡，使用了 "once", 表示當一件事情發生時，將會隨即發生另一件事(玩家會直接被送至 Ganondorf 的洞穴)。"no longer" 則是表示在玩家進入 Ganondorf 洞穴後就無法再進行存檔或快速移動了。&lt;br&gt;4. "This time, he's beefed up considerably, and he's going to test your mettle." &lt;br&gt;使用了 "he's beefed up considerably" 這個片語，意思是指某個東西變得更加強大或重要。"test your mettle" 則是指考驗某人的才能或勇氣，之所以使用這個片語來形容這位最終BOSS是因為這次的戰鬥將會是一個嚴峻的挑戰。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;單字：&lt;br&gt;1. final [ˈfaɪnəl] (日: ファイナル)&lt;br&gt;- 詞義：最後的，終極的&lt;br&gt;- 記憶方式：中文「最後」屬於三個字的單字，而 final 也是由五個字母組成的單字，記得最後一定要結束，最後一定為 final。&lt;br&gt;2. rival [ˈraɪvl] (日: ライバル)&lt;br&gt;- 詞義：敵對者，對手&lt;br&gt;- 記憶方式：和英文單字相近的中文「對手」，拉進來我們的英文單字就是 rival。&lt;br&gt;3. debuff [di-ˈbəf] (日: デバフ)&lt;br&gt;- 詞義：狀態異常，異常負面效果&lt;br&gt;- 記憶方式：將英文中的「de-」和「buff」兩部分拆開，「de-」的意思是取消或削弱，「buff」則是指增益效果，所以將這兩個部分結合起來就是取消或削弱的增益效果，也就是負面效果。&lt;br&gt;4. mettle [ˈmɛt(ə)l] (日: メテル)&lt;br&gt;- 詞義：勇氣，毅力，決心&lt;br&gt;- 記憶方式：mettle 的「met」讀音和「勇氣」的發音很接近，而「tle」和「毅力」、「決心」也相近，因此可將 mettle 聯想為代表勇氣和毅力的單字。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;片語：&lt;br&gt;1. up his sleeve&lt;br&gt;- 詞義：指藏有意料之外的事，意指某人秘密掌握了一些方法或策略&lt;br&gt;- 記憶方式：簡單地說，這個片語就是「藏在衣袖裏」的意思。平常我們在穿衣服的時候會將手臂伸過袖子，同樣地他人也不會意識到自己衣袖裏藏了什麼東西。因此這個片語就是描寫藏有意料之外的事，秘密掌握了一些方法或策略。&lt;br&gt;2. whittling down&lt;br&gt;- 詞義：逐漸削減，縮小&lt;br&gt;- 記憶方式：用小刀逐漸地把木頭削成自己想要的形狀，同樣的，這個片語也指逐漸削減的意思。&lt;br&gt;3. as such&lt;br&gt;- 詞義：因此，所以&lt;br&gt;- 記憶方式：as 讀音和中文的「因此」讀音很接近，而「such」可以理解為「這樣的」，合起來就代表因此，所以了。&lt;br&gt;4. have a few tricks up his sleeve&lt;br&gt;- 詞義：心中藏著一堆驚奇的招式或者方法&lt;br&gt;- 記憶方式：have 表示擁有的意思，tricks 表示招數，up his sleeve 指藏在衣袖裡，這個句子指表示，他的心中藏有讓你驚奇的招式或者方法。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;備註：&lt;br&gt;1. 日文單字：&lt;br&gt;- final - ファイナル&lt;br&gt;- rival - ライバル&lt;br&gt;- debuff - デバフ&lt;br&gt;- mettle - メテル&lt;br&gt;2. 相似片語： &lt;br&gt;- pull a trick - 滑溜的把戲 &lt;br&gt;- have an ace up one's sleeve - 有妙計,有底牌&lt;br&gt;3. 反義片語：&lt;br&gt;- straight shooter - 誠實的人&lt;br&gt;- play by the book - 按部就班</content><link href="https://www.gamespot.com/articles/zelda-tears-of-the-kingdom-ganondorf-final-boss-guide/1100-6514051/" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>