<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><id>https://github.com/weg38asyy/GameRss.git</id><title>My Game Rss</title><updated>2023-05-29T13:13:34.946497+00:00</updated><author><name>Koala</name><email>weg38asyy@gmail.com</email></author><link href="https://github.com/weg38asyy" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Personal learning of English use</subtitle><entry><id>https://www.gamespot.com/articles/why-were-worried-about-the-metal-gear-solid-3-remake-spot-on/1100-6514607/</id><title>Why We're Worried About The Metal Gear Solid 3 Remake | Spot On</title><updated>2023-05-29T13:13:34.946761+00:00</updated><content type="html">The PlayStation Showcase offered an early look at a variety of new games coming to PlayStation 5 and PlayStation VR, but the biggest reveal was undoubtedly a remake of Metal Gear Solid 3: Snake Eater. The title is one of the worst-kept secrets in the industry and, finally, it is out in the open. The immediate response, naturally, was excitement, particularly from the GameSpot team. But in the hours following, concerns began to arise. &lt;br&gt; Metal Gear Solid is one of the biggest and most iconic video game franchises of all time and Metal Gear Solid 3: Snake Eater is regarded as one of the greatest games of all time. But there is cynicism and skepticism around Konami's ability to do justice to the franchise and the game. On this week's episode of Spot On, Metal Gear Solid fans Lucy and Tamoor discuss why they're worried about the project, delving into some of the key questions that remain unanswered, and why they may be cause for concern. &lt;br&gt; Spot On is a weekly news show airing Fridays in which GameSpot's managing editor Tamoor Hussain and senior producer Lucy James talk about the latest news in games. Given the highly dynamic and never-ending news cycle of the massive video game industry, there's always something to talk about but, unlike most other news shows, Spot On will dive deep into a single topic as opposed to recapping all the news. Spot On airs each Friday.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;詳細句子文法解析：&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. "The PlayStation Showcase offered an early look at a variety of new games coming to PlayStation 5 and PlayStation VR, but the biggest reveal was undoubtedly a remake of Metal Gear Solid 3: Snake Eater."&lt;br&gt;這句話是一個複合句，其中 "but" 是轉折詞，它代表了對前面所提起的新遊戲及其展示狀況的評比和後面所提的 "Metal Gear Solid 3: Snake Eater" 的重要性提醒的對比和前後懸殊感。重點在於表達複雜情況及轉折意義。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. "The title is one of the worst-kept secrets in the industry and, finally, it is out in the open."&lt;br&gt;這句話也是一個複合句，其中 "and" 是連接詞，表示"一件事情發生了多個結果"的關係。這裡的 "The title" 是話題， "worst-kept secrets" 是形容詞短語, 用來形容話題， "finally" 表示時間， "out in the open" 是固定詞組，它表示某事公開。在这个句子中, 重點在於表達某事情公開的最終結束状态。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. "The immediate response, naturally, was excitement, particularly from the GameSpot team."&lt;br&gt;這是一個單句話，"naturally" 被放在逗号后，表示一个自然而然的结果， "particularly" 是一个副詞，表示强调与增强的状态或面对的对象，"the GameSpot team" 是一个名字，它表示固定範圍内的群体名称。这句话的重点在於宣泄标志对事物的一些情感反应。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. "But in the hours following, concerns began to arise."&lt;br&gt;"But" 在這裡是一個表轉折的连词，引出一种不一样的结果。也就是说，虽然前面不断强调各大机构纷纷表示激动，但是接下来好像，事情又出了问题，即可能存在着焦虑的心理。重点在於在句子中表達出转折以及心理状态的变化。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. "Metal Gear Solid is one of the biggest and most iconic video game franchises of all time and Metal Gear Solid 3: Snake Eater is regarded as one of the greatest games of all time."&lt;br&gt;這句話也是一个复合句，其中并列连词 "and" 表示相似或增强的关系。这句话的重点在于用形容词来形容游戏，从而表达某个目标非常成功和重要。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;6. "But there is cynicism and skepticism around Konami's ability to do justice to the franchise and the game."&lt;br&gt;"But" 仍然是连续串连词，引出而后的话就有所不同了。在這裡, 它带了去前面的"Metal Gear Solid"所表述的对游戏的高评论和赞誉，脱胎于这些背景信息引出了“褒贬不一”、“难以做到完美”的强调态度。重点在于表达矛盾心理和质疑角度。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;7. "On this week's episode of Spot On, Metal Gear Solid fans Lucy and Tamoor discuss why they're worried about the project, delving into some of the key questions that remain unanswered, and why they may be cause for concern."&lt;br&gt;這句话有三个并列的动词短语，分别是"discuss"，"delving"， "may be". 其中 "delving" 是需要注意的。重点在于用语文艺的方式表达出人们的忧虑和审美方式。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;8. "Given the highly dynamic and never-ending news cycle of the massive video game industry, there's always something to talk about"&lt;br&gt; "Given" 是一个转换性副词，它标榜出某个环境信息背景所形成的氛围或特征，即在巨大的电子游戏界领域下,不论何时都有交流内容. 重点在于描绘出一个行业的特点和特色。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;9. "unlike most other news shows, Spot On will dive deep into a single topic as opposed to recapping all the news."&lt;br&gt;"unlike" 在句子中是一个连词，用于探讨 与一級翻译或目标语不同之主题对象。这句话在许多电子新闻节目中诠释出SpotOn的优势及特性，这种特点注重深入单一话题的情节表现，而不是对所有新闻的简单总结。重点在于描述程序员在某些情况下为具体情况提供贡献而非为概括服务。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;10. "Spot On airs each Friday."&lt;br&gt;这简单的一句话拥有片体的语调，高度概括，单纯，便于记忆。重点在于确定节目的候选表现形式和转发周期。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;單字：&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. showcase 展示; n.[日]碑、展示櫥&lt;br&gt;&lt;記憶提示&gt; 比不得美女&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. reveal 揭露, 揭示; n.展现 ,展示; n.[C][U][法]曝光&lt;br&gt;&lt;記憶提示&gt;垃圾桶前揭秘大计&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. iconic 象征性的，标志性的; n.像标&lt;br&gt;&lt;記憶提示&gt;歌曲代表性人物&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. franchise 特許經銷權. 連鎖加盟權; n.公民的自由，特權，權利; n.[時]-es 特許經銷權[場所、機構、受影響的範圍等]&lt;br&gt;&lt;記憶提示&gt; 戰略護城河，/freedom/alliance&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. skepticism 懷疑論，懷疑的態度; n.[U]懷疑,多疑&lt;br&gt;&lt;記憶提示&gt;消費與懷疑&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;6. cynicism 憤世嫉俗；疑心; n.狗嘴里的烤骨頭，; 外厕沟中的一种机器&lt;br&gt;&lt;記憶提示&gt;狗狗烤骨期待&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;7. delving 深入研究，挖掘; n.(動物一)翻土雀(常指翻掘其窩穴); n.1. 树干, 树桩  2. 树根&lt;br&gt;&lt;記憶提示&gt;挖掘精神&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;8. coverage 涵蓋範圍；覆蓋; n.[U]報導，新聞內容;&lt;br&gt;&lt;記憶提示&gt;軍事防禦罩&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;9. dynamic 動力學，動力的; n.[C]动力学，有力量的，精力充沛的; n.[C]有活力的人&lt;br&gt;&lt;記憶提示&gt;主動攻取的人&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;10. recap 篇一结束的时候 ，概括； n.[C]概要医歩表，扣帐纪录表&lt;br&gt;&lt;記憶提示&gt;精简，概要&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;片語：&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. out in the open {片語} 明朗的, 公開的  eg. You can’t keep it a secret any longer- it's out in the open。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;相似片語: public knowledge, open secret;&lt;br&gt;反義片語: covert, undercover &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. cause for concern {片語} 引起关切、忧虑的原因   eg   那次地震留下的房子间隔不足是引起广泛关注和关注的原因。 &lt;br&gt;相似片语：grounds for concern, subject of concern ;&lt;br&gt;反义片语：things that ease the mind, things put people's minds at rest.</content><link href="https://www.gamespot.com/articles/why-were-worried-about-the-metal-gear-solid-3-remake-spot-on/1100-6514607/" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>