<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><id>https://github.com/weg38asyy/GameRss.git</id><title>My Game Rss</title><updated>2023-03-22T17:40:29.761566+00:00</updated><author><name>Koala</name><email>weg38asyy@gmail.com</email></author><link href="https://github.com/weg38asyy" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Personal learning of English use</subtitle><entry><id>https://www.gamespot.com/articles/john-wick-4s-first-cut-was-extremely-long-were-so-screwed-director-remembers-thinking/1100-6512600/</id><title>John Wick 4's First Cut Was Extremely Long: "We're So Screwed," Director Remembers Thinking</title><updated>2023-03-22T17:40:29.761889+00:00</updated><content>At 169 minutes, John Wick: Chapter 4 is the longest entry in the Keanu Reeves action series so far, but it was originally even longer. Director Chad Stahelski told IndieWire that the studio never gave him a mandate about length, but when the first cut came in at 225 minutes, or 3 hours and 45 minutes, they knew it was too long. "To be really honest with you, zero was planned out," Stahelski said. "Our first cut was three hours and 45 minutes, and it felt like three hours and 45 minutes. We were like, oh, we're so screwed." The lengthy runtime was due in part to how the first cut originally spent more time focusing on the film's new characters. However, Stahelski and editor Nathan Orloff pared it back to make sure the focus was on Wick. "I wanted to make sure that he was still the center of the universe, that everything always led back to him even though we were cutting away from him," Orloff said. Orloff said the idea was to "compress, compress, compress" and to cut out any instances of characters repeating an idea they had already expressed. "No repeated ideas. It's a very linear story, so there wasn't a ton of reconstruction or rearrangement we could do. It was just a matter of sifting out what we didn't need," he said. For comparison, the longest runtime in the series so far was John Wick Chapter 3: Parabellum, which was 131 minutes. John Wick Chapter 2 was 122 minutes and the original John Wick was 101 minutes. In addition to Keanu Reeves as John Wick, the film brings back Ian McShane and Laurence Fishburne, while newcomers include Bill Skarsgard, Donnie Yen, and Clancy Brown. Lance Reddick returns as Charon in one of his final roles following his recent passing at the age of 60. The movie opens in theaters on March 24.  Apart from John Wick 4, a spinoff titled Ballerina starring Ana de Armas is in production.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;詳細句子文法解析：&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. "At 169 minutes, John Wick: Chapter 4 is the longest entry in the Keanu Reeves action series so far, but it was originally even longer." &lt;br&gt;   這個句子是屬於複合句，包含了兩個用逗號隔開的主要子句和一個連接詞字句。其中，第一個主要子句指出電影長度，第二個主要子句則描述了它的先前版本。而副詞子句 "but it was originally even longer" 則是用來表達對比關係。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. "Director Chad Stahelski told IndieWire that the studio never gave him a mandate about length, but when the first cut came in at 225 minutes, or 3 hours and 45 minutes, they knew it was too long." 這個句子也是複合句，主要由一個主要子句和一個用 "but" 連接的副詞子句組成。主要子句描述了導演受到的指示，副詞子句則表達了一個對比。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. "The lengthy runtime was due in part to how the first cut originally spent more time focusing on the film's new characters." 這個句子的結構是應用了複合句，其中主語是 "The lengthy runtime"，動詞是 "was due"，副詞片語 "in part" 表明了原因的部分性，而 "how the first cut originally spent more time focusing on the film's new characters" 則是用來描述相關的過程和原因。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. "Orloff said the idea was to "compress, compress, compress" and to cut out any instances of characters repeating an idea they had already expressed." 這個句子是由一個主要子句和一個 and 連接的並列句組成。其中主要子句中有一個補語 "the idea"，並且它是由動詞 "was" 和 to 動詞短語 "compress, compress, compress" 構成的。而並列句則意味著 "cutting out"。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. "The movie opens in theaters on March 24."這是一個簡單陳述句，主語是 "The movie"，動詞是 "opens"。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;單字：&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. Mandate (n.): 命令；指令。記憶技巧：mandate 中有 "man"，可以聯想為 "男人" 制定的 "命令"。&lt;br&gt;   日語單字：指令 (しれい/shirei)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Pared (v.): 消除，削減。記憶技巧：pared 中有 "pair"，這裡可以想成要將雙重多餘的東西 "削減" 到一個。&lt;br&gt;   日語單字：削減 (さくげん/sakugen)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. Linear (adj.): 直線的，線性的。記憶技巧：linear 中有 "line"，可聯想為數學中的 "直線"。&lt;br&gt;   日語單字：直線的 (ちょくせんてき/chokusenteki)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. Compression (n.): 壓縮，縮小。 記憶技巧：compression 中有 "press"，像壓壓縮縮一樣，可以幫助記憶。&lt;br&gt;   日語單字：圧縮 (あっしゅく/asshuku)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. Reconstruction (n.): 重建，復原。 记憶技巧：reconstruction 中有"construction"，如果某物建造不好，必須重來 "重建"。&lt;br&gt;   日語單字：再建 (さいけん/saiken)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;片語：&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. to be screwed：很難、很棘手。例句：We're so screwed if we can't finish this project on time.（如果我們不能按時完成這個項目，那就太難了）&lt;br&gt;   相似片語：to be in trouble (進退兩難)，to be in a fix (處於困境)&lt;br&gt;   反義片語：to be out of trouble (擺脫困境)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. center of the universe：宇宙的中心。這裡是用來形容 John Wick 是整部電影的核心。例句：My wife thinks she's the center of the universe, but I know better.（我妻子以為自己是宇宙的中心，但我知道情況不是這樣的）&lt;br&gt;   相似片語：core of the matter（事情的核心）&lt;br&gt;   反義片語：at the margins（處於邊緣）&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. for comparison：做比較。這段片語意味著接下來的句子是要和之前的事情做比較。例句：For comparison, last year's sales were much higher than this year's.（為了作比較，去年的銷售量比今年要高得多）。&lt;br&gt;   相似片語：in comparison with (和...比較起來)&lt;br&gt;   反義片語：standalone（獨立的）&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. in production：正在製作中。這個片語用來描述 Ballerina 的狀態。例句：The sequel is currently in the pre-production phase.（續集正在進行前期製作）&lt;br&gt;   相似片語：in development（正在開發中）&lt;br&gt;   反義片語：completed（已完成）&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;其它：&lt;br&gt;1. John Wick Chapter 4 的預定上映日期: 3月24日&lt;br&gt;2. Lance Reddick (Charon 的演員), 已於2022年3月3日逝世，享年60歲。</content><link href="https://www.gamespot.com/articles/john-wick-4s-first-cut-was-extremely-long-were-so-screwed-director-remembers-thinking/1100-6512600/" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>