<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><id>https://github.com/weg38asyy/GameRss.git</id><title>My Game Rss</title><updated>2023-05-05T13:11:28.273720+00:00</updated><author><name>Koala</name><email>weg38asyy@gmail.com</email></author><link href="https://github.com/weg38asyy" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Personal learning of English use</subtitle><entry><id>https://www.gamespot.com/articles/destiny-2s-older-raid-exotics-will-soon-be-easier-to-obtain/1100-6513860/</id><title>Destiny 2's Older Raid Exotics Will Soon Be Easier To Obtain</title><updated>2023-05-05T13:11:28.274000+00:00</updated><content type="html">A welcome recent change in Destiny 2 has seen the addition of raid and dungeon Triumphs that increase the likelihood of getting the random Exotic weapons associated with those activities. In other words, completing optional objectives makes it more likely that you'll obtain the very rare, highly desirable Exotics as you repeat those raids and dungeons. But this is only true for a select number of those activities, something that will be changing in the upcoming Season of the Deep. &lt;br&gt; The Exotics from five more raids will soon have Triumphs that boost your personal drop rate. This is only for randomly dropped Exotics, but notably, these boosts will be attached to existing Triumphs. These are retroactive, meaning if you've already completed the Triumphs in question, you'll immediately have the boosted drop rate. &lt;br&gt; This applies to One Thousand Voices (the fusion rifle from Last Wish), Eyes of Tomorrow (the rocket launcher from Deepstone Crypt), Collective Obligation (the pulse rifle from Vow of the Disciple), Vex Mythoclast (the fusion rifle from Vault of Glass), and Touch of Malice (the scout rifle from Kingsfall). &lt;br&gt; While this is a notable improvement for those who have put in the time to unlock these Triumphs but haven't lucked into these raids' Exotics, it's one of multiple Exotic-centric changes coming in Season 21. Bungie will also be introducing a new means of focusing Exotic armor you already own, allowing you to get better stat rolls on them, and will swap Exotic engram drops in place of certain Pinnacle rewards each week. &lt;br&gt; Here are the specific bonuses you'll receive for completing each Triumph in these raids:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;詳細句子文法解析：&lt;br&gt;1. "A welcome recent change"，表示這個變化是歡迎的，welcome是形容詞，recent則是形容此變化發生的時間點。&lt;br&gt;2. "has seen the addition of"，表示新的變化添加了什麼，has seen表示過去知道一個事件或者發生的事情。&lt;br&gt;3. "that increase the likelihood"，後面接到的是一個關係代詞，表示這個變化導致了一個結果。&lt;br&gt;4. "Exotics as you repeat those raids and dungeons"，exotic表示一種非常罕見且令人嚮往的東西，as you repeat表示當你重複這些活動時。&lt;br&gt;5. "But this is only true for a select number of those activities"，但是這只適用於部分活動，select number表示選擇性的。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;6. "something that will be changing"，這個句子表示這將是一個變化，并且是將要發生的。&lt;br&gt;7. "The Exotics from five more raids will soon have Triumphs"，此句子表示即將有五個新的活動會有triumphs。&lt;br&gt;8. "Notably, these boosts will be attached to existing Triumphs"，這裡的notably表示值得注意的，attached表示附加，existing triumps則是指已經存在的triumphs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;9. "if you've already completed the Triumphs in question, you'll immediately have the boosted drop rate"，此處表示如果你已經完成特定的triumphs，那么你立刻將擁有增強的掉落率。&lt;br&gt;10. "it's one of multiple Exotic-centric changes coming in Season 21"，此句表示這是Season 21中的許多放重話的更改之一。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;單字：&lt;br&gt;1. Triumph 記憶方式：因為令人興奮所以triumph&lt;br&gt;2. Exotic 記憶方式：外來的exotic，陌生又稀有&lt;br&gt;3. dungeon 日文單字 手下の洞窟(shitate no dokutsu) 記憶方式：手下有洞穴&lt;br&gt;4. addition 日文單字 追加(tsuika) 記憶方式：可以老貓追加到本子上（tsuika箸本）&lt;br&gt;5. likelihood 日文單字 可能性(kanou sei) 記憶方式：看她的臉色，猜可能性（kanou sei）&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;6. randomly 日文單字 無作為(furiesai) 記憶方式：無作為的炮彈(furiurusanai bougan)&lt;br&gt;7. boost 日文單字 引き起こす(hikiokosu) 記憶方式：boost是強烈提高，&lt;br&gt;8. personal 日文單字 個人(kojin) 記憶方式：以kojin視角享受&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;9. fusion 日文單字 融合(yuugou) 記憶方式：將我和你yuu(gou)起來&lt;br&gt;10. scout 日文單字 偵察(teisatsu) 記憶方式：偵探一定要偵(tеi)satsu&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;片語：&lt;br&gt;1. 類：optional objectives 可選擇的目標；反：mandatory tasks 強制任務&lt;br&gt;2. 類：highly desirable 非常令人嚮往；反：totally undesirable 極可怕的&lt;br&gt;3. 類：coming soon 即將來臨；反：moving away 遠離&lt;br&gt;4. 類：retroactive 不溯及既往的；反：forward-looking 向前看的&lt;br&gt;5. 類：notably 值得注意的；反：unremarkably 不值得注意的</content><link href="https://www.gamespot.com/articles/destiny-2s-older-raid-exotics-will-soon-be-easier-to-obtain/1100-6513860/" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>