<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><id>https://github.com/weg38asyy/GameRss.git</id><title>My Game Rss</title><updated>2023-05-27T13:11:51.976766+00:00</updated><author><name>Koala</name><email>weg38asyy@gmail.com</email></author><link href="https://github.com/weg38asyy" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Personal learning of English use</subtitle><entry><id>https://www.gamespot.com/articles/trials-of-osiris-rewards-this-week-in-destiny-2-may-26-30/1100-6514591/</id><title>Trials Of Osiris Rewards This Week In Destiny 2 (May 26-30)</title><updated>2023-05-27T13:11:51.976880+00:00</updated><content type="html">The Trials of Osiris are live once again in Destiny 2, and after the Season 21 patch introduced some big changes to the sandbox, expect to see a few new strategies being used in this PvP activity. Before you head down to visit Saint-14 and get your passage card stamped, make a turn by Xur to see what gear the Agent of the Nine has for sale this weekend. Here's a look at where you'll play Trials of Osiris this weekend and what weapons you can earn. &lt;br&gt; Map: Endless Vale &lt;br&gt; Season of the Deep is adding some excellent new rewards to the Trials pool, and if you're a fan of shaders, then there's a glorious golden one to grab from this multiplayer event. Alongside the Glorious Patina shader, Trials will also have some new Exotic cosmetic gear to unlock, including a new Ghost shell, ship, and Sparrow. Glorious Patina will only be available to players who go Flawless during Season 21, and the weapon pool is being updated with The Messenger pulse rifle and the Unexpected Resurgence glaive as possible prizes. &lt;br&gt; A new emblem is also being added, but you'll need to get a Flight of the Pigeon medal for every win and open the Flawless chest at the Lighthouse to obtain it. The other big change to Trials this season is the debut of an introductory quest that provides a proper tutorial for new Trials players, and completing it will reward players with the Astral Horizon Trials Shotgun. &lt;br&gt; Trials Passage offerings are also being updated to provide a better experience, starting with Passage of Wealth. This will now grant +75 Trials reputation for every win and an additional bonus for your current major rank in Trials, up to +150 total. Passage of Mercy will now forgive two losses if you have not yet been Flawless for the week, and after going Flawless, it reverts back to a state where it forgives a single loss on each card after you reset it. &lt;br&gt; This season's core game mode is Dominion, which Bungie says was chosen because it is overall faster, promotes more varied engagements, and provides a healthier sandbox variety. As a reminder, Trials weapons carry the Alacrity Origin Trait, which gives you increased aim assist, reload speed, stability, and range on these weapons when you're the last living member of a fireteam or running solo. You can also choose to swap to the Crucible Origin trait, One Quiet Moment, which greatly enhances your gun's reload speed when you reload while out of combat. &lt;br&gt; Trials goes live from Friday's daily reset at 10 AM PT / 1 PM ET until the weekly reset at the same time the following Tuesday. Make sure to pay a visit to Saint-14 in the Tower to pick up a Trials card, which will dictate certain bonuses (such as whether you get bonus rewards at certain milestones or if a loss will be forgiven). Your ultimate goal in the Trials of Osiris is for you and the other two players in your fireteam to achieve a "Flawless" run, in which you win seven matches without losing any. &lt;br&gt; Go Flawless and you'll earn a trip to the Lighthouse and receive some special rewards, including the Adept weapons. These have additional stat bonuses, making them among the most coveted items you can get your hands on. Your Trials Passage--the card you purchase from Saint-14 that grants you access to the mode and tracks your wins--does not track your losses, so you can keep playing and earning rewards even if you lose out on a Flawless run.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;句子文法解析：&lt;br&gt;1. "The Trials of Osiris are live once again in Destiny 2" ，live這個形容詞的意思是"正在進行"，在這個句子中被用來表示活動正在進行中。&lt;br&gt;2. "Before you head down to visit Saint-14 and get your passage card stamped"，head down to (去某個特定的地方)是一個片語，表示"去某個地方"。此外，get your passage card stamped是一個動詞短語，表示"去拿你的進入證並註明已經開始（當場戳章）"。&lt;br&gt;3. "Trials will also have some new Exotic cosmetic gear to unlock"，to unlock是一個動詞短語，用來強調可以解鎖新的裝備。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;單字：&lt;br&gt;1. Strategies [n.]：策略，記憶方式：[拆解後詞彙聯想：strategy（策略）、ies(複數形)]&lt;br&gt;2. Sandbox [n.]：沙盤遊戲，記憶方式：[英文諧音：三明治內的沙子]&lt;br&gt;3. Glorious [adj.]：光榮的，記憶方式：[英文諧音：高樓大廈上的 Reesie's]&lt;br&gt;4. Glaive [n.]：鏢；飛鏢，記憶方式：[英文諧音：奇異博士的劍]&lt;br&gt;5. Forgiveness [n.]：寬恕，記憶方式：[拆解後詞彙聯想：for[給予]'+give+[給予的動作]+ ness[態度/狀態]，表示給予一種態度的寬恕。]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;片語：&lt;br&gt;1. 相似片語：To have a shot at something（有機會成功做某件事情）。反義片語：To have no shot at all（毫無機會成功做某件事情）。&lt;br&gt;2. 相似片語：Up to（最多；多達）。反義片語：At the minimum（至少）。&lt;br&gt;3. 相似片語：Keep playing（繼續玩）。反義片語：Stop playing（停止玩遊戲）。 &lt;br&gt;4. 相似片語：Winning streak（連勝）。反義片語：Losing streak (連敗)。 &lt;br&gt;5. 相似片語：Make a turn（轉向；轉彎）。反義片語：Go straight（直走）。 &lt;br&gt;6. 相似片語：Get your hands on（得到；取得）。反義片語：Lose your grip on (失去控制)。&lt;br&gt;7. 相似片語：Flawless run（完美的比賽表現）。反義片語：Imperfect run（不完美的比賽表現）。 &lt;br&gt;8. 相似片語：Head down（下去）。反義片語：Head up（更高地走）。&lt;br&gt;9. 相似片語：Passage of Wealth（豐裕的通道）。反義片語：Passage of poverty（貧窮的通道）。&lt;br&gt;10. 相似片語：A trip to the Lighthouse（到燈塔去）。反義片語：A trip to the dark（到黑暗中去）。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;日文單字：&lt;br&gt;1. Strategies [n.]：戦略[せんりゃく] &lt;br&gt;2. Sandbox [n.]：砂場[すなば]&lt;br&gt;3. Glorious [adj.]：栄光の[eikou no]&lt;br&gt;4. Glaive [n.]：鏢[より] &lt;br&gt;5. Forgiveness [n.]：寛容[かんよう]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;備註：&lt;br&gt;1. 以上所提供的單字、片語、和日文單字，皆可作為學生的背誦材料，幫助學生擴充詞彙和邏輯理解。根據學生的英文水平和學習需求，老師可以酌情調整難易度和進度，以達到最好的教學效果。&lt;br&gt;2. 在學生學習英文的同時，中文翻譯也非常重要，可以有效地幫助學生理解句子。老師可以採取多種方法（例如投影片中給出的中文解釋；口頭解釋將復合句更細分）來教授學生。</content><link href="https://www.gamespot.com/articles/trials-of-osiris-rewards-this-week-in-destiny-2-may-26-30/1100-6514591/" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>