<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><id>https://github.com/weg38asyy/GameRss.git</id><title>My Game Rss</title><updated>2023-05-25T13:14:07.407412+00:00</updated><author><name>Koala</name><email>weg38asyy@gmail.com</email></author><link href="https://github.com/weg38asyy" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Personal learning of English use</subtitle><entry><id>https://www.gamespot.com/articles/five-nights-at-freddys-help-wanted-2-announced-for-playstation-vr-2/1100-6514537/</id><title>Five Nights At Freddy's: Help Wanted 2 Announced For PlayStation VR 2</title><updated>2023-05-25T13:14:07.407621+00:00</updated><content type="html">The Five Nights At Freddy's series is getting a new addition in the form of a sequel to the franchise's thrilling VR game, Five Nights At Freddy's: Help Wanted. Five Nights At Freddy's: Help Wanted 2 was announced at the 2023 PlayStation Showcase with a short teaser trailer. &lt;br&gt; The trailer takes place in a structurally questionable elevator which seems to be descending at an alarming speed. "We know how challenging it can be to find a place where you feel that you truly belong, and to find a job that treats you mostly with respect, and infrequently, with contempt," an automated voiceover says over the elevator's intercom. "For that reason, we are excited to inform you that you did an adequate enough job the first time around to have you back. Also, there were no other applicants." &lt;br&gt; You need a javascript enabled browser to watch videos. &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;        Want us to remember this setting for all your devices?&lt;br&gt;       &lt;br&gt; Sign up or Sign in now!&lt;br&gt;       &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;        By clicking 'enter', you agree to GameSpot's&lt;br&gt;                        Terms of Use and&lt;br&gt;        Privacy Policy &lt;br&gt; enter &lt;br&gt; Now Playing: Five Nights at Freddy's Help Wanted 2 - Teaser Trailer | PS VR2 Games &lt;br&gt; The elevator's lights flicker, revealing posters that feature two familiar characters from the franchise: Circus Baby and Bonnie. The elevator then crashes--though the player occupying it seems to survive--before the trailer reveals the game's title screen. &lt;br&gt; First released in 2019, the original Help Wanted game marked the franchise's first foray into VR, putting players in the shoes of a Fazbear Entertainment employee, challenging players to complete various minigames while fending off attacks from haunted animatronics, and it seems the sequel will follow a similar format. &lt;br&gt; "Help Wanted 2 will feel familiar to players who experienced the first game, but with all new games, locations, story, and animatronics," says a recently published PlayStation blog post about the game. "Do your best to complete your work as fast and as diligently as you can, but be careful. One wrong move at this job can lead to… unexpected consequences. Utilizing the enhanced power and fidelity of PSVR 2, this title will be the most immersive, heart-racing Five Nights at Freddy’s title ever." &lt;br&gt; No concrete details about gameplay have been revealed, and there is no confirmed release date at this time. What has been confirmed, however, is the game's platform. Five Nights At Freddy's: Help Wanted 2 is set to launch on PSVR 2.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;句子文法解析：&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. The Five Nights at Freddy's series is getting a new addition in the form of a sequel to the franchise's thrilling VR game, Five Nights at Freddy's: Help Wanted.&lt;br&gt;- 「getting」是現在進行式，用以表示系列正在獲得新的作品。&lt;br&gt;- 「in the form of」是片語，意思是以...的形式出現。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Five Nights at Freddy's: Help Wanted 2 was announced at the 2023 PlayStation Showcase with a short teaser trailer.&lt;br&gt;- 「was announced」使用被動語態，說明 Help Wanted 2 是被宣布的。&lt;br&gt;- 「with a short teaser trailer」為介係詞片語，表示 Help Wanted 2 宣傳使用短片預告。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. The trailer takes place in a structurally questionable elevator which seems to be descending at an alarming speed.&lt;br&gt;- 「takes place in」是片語，表示發生在某個場所。&lt;br&gt;- 「questionable」用來形容事情或物體有問題或有瑕疵。&lt;br&gt;- 「at an alarming speed」表示速度極快，引人憂慮。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. "We know how challenging it can be to find a place where you feel that you truly belong, and to find a job that treats you mostly with respect, and infrequently, with contempt," an automated voiceover says over the elevator's intercom.&lt;br&gt;- 「know + it + to be」是固定搭配，用來表達對某事頗有瞭解。&lt;br&gt;- 「where you feel that you truly belong」是關係子句，用來修飾「a place」。&lt;br&gt;- 「that treats you mostly with respect, and infrequently, with contempt」是形容詞子句，說明找工作的過程和感受。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. "For that reason, we are excited to inform you that you did an adequate enough job the first time around to have you back. Also, there were no other applicants."&lt;br&gt;- 「For that reason」為連接詞，表示引出原因。&lt;br&gt;- 「adequate enough」用來形容工作表現「足夠好」。&lt;br&gt;- 「the first time around」是片語，表示指的是上一次。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;6. The elevator's lights flicker, revealing posters that feature two familiar characters from the franchise: Circus Baby and Bonnie.&lt;br&gt;- 「flicker」表示快速閃爍。&lt;br&gt;- 「feature」用來表示書面語中的「有...的特點或特徵」。&lt;br&gt;- 「franchise」在此為名詞，表示權利之經銷或特許經營權。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;7. The elevator then crashes--though the player occupying it seems to survive--before the trailer reveals the game's title screen.&lt;br&gt;- 「then」表示時間順序上隨即發生，標明出事件先後。&lt;br&gt;- 「seems to」表示似乎；這是在描述玩家的運氣看起來很不錯。&lt;br&gt;- 「reveals」表示顯示出、揭露出等意思。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;8. First released in 2019, the original Help Wanted game marked the franchise's first foray into VR, putting players in the shoes of a Fazbear Entertainment employee, challenging players to complete various minigames while fending off attacks from haunted animatronics, and it seems the sequel will follow a similar format.&lt;br&gt;- 「marked」表示是某事重要、有意義的起點或時刻。&lt;br&gt;- 「foray into」是片語，意指企業/個人於某尚未進行過、未曾涉足過的產業領域當中嘗試。&lt;br&gt;- 「putting players in the shoes of」是一個非正式用法，用來表示讓玩家想像成是某個角色。&lt;br&gt;- 「challenging players to」表示讓玩家嘗試...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;9. "Help Wanted 2 will feel familiar to players who experienced the first game, but with all new games, locations, story, and animatronics," says a recently published PlayStation blog post about the game.&lt;br&gt;- 「feel familiar」是感覺上非常熟悉的意思。&lt;br&gt;- 「experienced」是經歷、經驗過的意思。&lt;br&gt;- 「all new」是全新的，意思是和上一部完全不一樣。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;10. "Do your best to complete your work as fast and as diligently as you can, but be careful. One wrong move at this job can lead to… unexpected consequences. Utilizing the enhanced power and fidelity of PSVR 2, this title will be the most immersive, heart-racing Five Nights at Freddy’s title ever."&lt;br&gt;- 「as...as」表示在某種程度上。&lt;br&gt;- 「diligent」是表示認真、勤奮的形容詞。&lt;br&gt;- 「one wrong move can lead to unexpected consequences」則是一個警語，表示稍有差池便可能產生嚴重的後果。&lt;br&gt;- 「immersive」表示全景的、涵蓋性的、沉浸式的。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;單字：&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. addition - 新增物；額外的東西。（中文記憶提醒：加上 something）&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. franchise - 特許經營權；特權或經營權。（中文記憶提醒：fran(chise) + (dis)pense 分發特權)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. sequel - （某事物的）續集。（中文記憶提醒：(se) go 後面的一些事情，繼續的故事）&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. animated - 活潑的；生氣勃勃的；逼真的。（中文記憶提醒：一個很熱鬧度過動畫的時光）&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. foray - 突犯；襲擊；進攻。（中文記憶提醒：成功的「突犯入侵關鍵領域」）&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;6. diligence - 勤勉；用功；堅毅不拔。（中文記憶提醒：一點一滴的做功課是實現「鑄成大器」的良方）&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;7. immersion - 沉浸；專注；陶醉。（中文記憶提醒：(im)→in + (mer)ge → 完全融入、深陷其中）&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;8. challenging - 具挑戰性的；考驗人的。（中文記憶提醒：有挑戰性的事物讓你感覺像是想哭的(charea) ling理更好）&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;9. adequate - 足夠的；適合的；恰當的。（中文記憶提醒：ad-to (到達) + -equate(n) (夠用) → 到達需求量的程度）&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;10. automated - 自動化的；機器化的；簡化操作的。（中文記憶提醒：使用自動化設備可以讓你做更多的事情）&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;片語：&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;相似片語： &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. in the form of - 以...的形式。（中文片語：形式態式; 萬物形式） &lt;br&gt;2. feel familiar - 有點熟悉。（中文片語：感覺就像開個玩笑一樣） &lt;br&gt;3. unexpected consequences - 意料之外的後果。（中文片語：亂來會出事）&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;反義片語：&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. unfamiliar surroundings - 不熟悉的環境。（中文片語：異鄉陌客） &lt;br&gt;2. anticipated outcome - 預期的結果。（中文片語：預料中得出來的結論）</content><link href="https://www.gamespot.com/articles/five-nights-at-freddys-help-wanted-2-announced-for-playstation-vr-2/1100-6514537/" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>