<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><id>https://github.com/weg38asyy/GameRss.git</id><title>My Game Rss</title><updated>2023-03-23T16:30:50.334899+00:00</updated><author><name>Koala</name><email>weg38asyy@gmail.com</email></author><link href="https://github.com/weg38asyy" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Personal learning of English use</subtitle><entry><id>https://www.gamespot.com/articles/us-government-wants-to-make-it-easier-to-cancel-subscriptions/1100-6512640/</id><title>US Government Wants To Make It Easier To Cancel Subscriptions</title><updated>2023-03-23T16:30:50.335490+00:00</updated><content type="html">The United State government's Federal Trade Commission has announced a new plan that, if implemented, could make it easier for people to cancel memberships to gyms, streaming services, and lots more. The provision is called "click to cancel," and the idea is that it should be as easy to cancel a membership as it is to sign up for one. Right now, that's definitely not the case, as anyone who has ever tried to cancel a gym or news media subscription surely knows. "The new click to cancel provision, along with other proposals, would go a long way to rescuing consumers from seemingly never-ending struggles to cancel unwanted subscription payment plans for everything from cosmetics to newspapers to gym memberships," the FTC said in a news release. FTC chair Lina Khan said, "The proposed rule would require that companies make it as easy to cancel a subscription as it is to sign up for one. The proposal would save consumers time and money, and businesses that continued to use subscription tricks and traps would be subject to stiff penalties." The FTC said it receives "thousands" of complaints each year about problematic business practices like forcing people to cancel their gym memberships in person or keeping people on hold with customer service for lengthy periods of time. Here is a rundown of the proposed changes, as written by the FTC. FTC Commissioner Christine S. Wilson issued a dissenting opinion on the measure. "I appreciate staff's steadfast efforts to protect consumers from deceptive negative option practices. I might have supported a tailored rule to address the negative option marketing abuses prevalent in our law enforcement experience that consolidated various legal requirements," Wilson said. "This proposal instead attempts an end-run around the Supreme Court's decision in AMG to confer de novo redress and civil penalty authority on the Commission for Section 5 violations unrelated to deceptive or unfair negative option practices. For these reasons, I dissent." Wilson is resigning as FTC Commissioner on March 31. The FTC is also in the midst of a legal dispute with Microsoft over its proposed buyout of Activision Blizzard.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;html&gt;&lt;br&gt;  &lt;body&gt;&lt;br&gt;    &lt;h2&gt;句子文法解析：&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;br&gt;    &lt;ul&gt;&lt;br&gt;      &lt;li&gt;"The provision is called 'click to cancel,' and the idea is that it should be as easy to cancel a membership as it is to sign up for one." - 使用從句來說明「click to cancel」的意思，用簡單句子再次強調此想法的重要性。&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;      &lt;li&gt;"The new click to cancel provision, along with other proposals, would go a long way to rescuing consumers from seemingly never-ending struggles to cancel unwanted subscription payment plans for everything from cosmetics to newspapers to gym memberships." - 使用現在分詞片語及定語從句來說明「click to cancel」條款的長遠效益。&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;      &lt;li&gt;"The FTC said it receives 'thousands' of complaints each year about problematic business practices like forcing people to cancel their gym memberships in person or keeping people on hold with customer service for lengthy periods of time." - 使用like表示舉例詳細說明問題性的商業手段。&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;      &lt;li&gt;"The proposal would save consumers time and money, and businesses that continued to use subscription tricks and traps would be subject to stiff penalties." - 使用平行結構強調消費者的利益及商業行為所應負的責任。&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;    &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br&gt;    &lt;h2&gt;單字：&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;br&gt;    &lt;ul&gt;&lt;br&gt;      &lt;li&gt;provision (條款) - 轉換為「規定」來記憶&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;      &lt;li&gt;cancel (取消) - 可以聯想到我的螢幕中央有個「X」，就是用來取消的&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;      &lt;li&gt;membership (會員身份) - 可以記成「入會身份」，身份的部分可以鏈結到大家耳熟能詳的「員」字形象上&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;      &lt;li&gt;streaming (串流) - 可以記成「直播串流」，直播作為大眾熟識的應用，可以讓學生更快地鏈結該單字的意思&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;      &lt;li&gt;complaint (抱怨) - 可以聯想到每當我出「問甚麼問題」的意思時，通常都聽到一大堆的抱怨聲&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;    &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br&gt;    &lt;h2&gt;日文單字：&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;br&gt;    &lt;ul&gt;&lt;br&gt;      &lt;li&gt;provision - 手段 (しゅだん)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;      &lt;li&gt;cancel - キャンセル (kyanseru)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;      &lt;li&gt;membership - 会員身分 (かいいんしんぶん)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;      &lt;li&gt;streaming - ストリーミング (sutori-mingu)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;      &lt;li&gt;complaint - 不服申し立て (ふふくもうしたて)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;    &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br&gt;    &lt;h2&gt;片語：&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;br&gt;    &lt;ul&gt;&lt;br&gt;      &lt;li&gt;Seemingly never-ending struggles (無休止的鬥爭) - 相似片語：Never-ending battle；反義片語：Resolved issue (解決的問題)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;      &lt;li&gt;Stiff penalties (嚴厲的處罰) - 相似片語：Harsh consequences；反義片語：Light punishment (輕微的懲罰)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;      &lt;li&gt;Negative option practices (自動繳費計畫陷阱) - 相似片語：Subscription tactics；反義片語：Positive option practices (有明確選擇權的計畫)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;    &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br&gt;  &lt;/body&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</content><link href="https://www.gamespot.com/articles/us-government-wants-to-make-it-easier-to-cancel-subscriptions/1100-6512640/" rel="alternate"/></entry><entry><id>https://www.gamespot.com/articles/new-nvidia-drivers-for-diablo-4-resident-evil-4-released/1100-6512642/</id><title>New Nvidia Drivers For Diablo 4, Resident Evil 4 Released</title><updated>2023-03-23T16:30:50.335350+00:00</updated><content type="html">Ahead of the release of Capcom's Resident Evil 4 remake and the launch of Diablo 4's open beta this week, Nvidia has released its latest Game Ready drivers for GeForce cards. The driver update also features a number of other features for popular games, including Cyberpunk 2077 and Forza Horizon 5. As a  blog post  reveals, the driver supports the technology preview for Cyberpunk 2077's ray tracing Overdrive Mode, the DLSS 3 update for Forza Horizon 5, and The Last Of Us Part 1's DLSS 2 features. It also has extra features for indie games like Deceive Inc. and Smalland: Survive the Wilds. You need a javascript enabled browser to watch videos. &lt;br&gt;        Want us to remember this setting for all your devices?&lt;br&gt;       Sign up or Sign in now!&lt;br&gt;       &lt;br&gt;        By clicking 'enter', you agree to GameSpot's&lt;br&gt;                        Terms of Use and&lt;br&gt;        Privacy Policy enter Now Playing: Resident Evil 4 Remake Trailer | Resident Evil 4 Showcase According to the blog, Diablo IV's beta will support DLSS 2 with Nvidia RTX GPUs. When the final game launches on June 6, it will support DLSS 3 on GeForce RTX 40 series cards. The aforementioned Overdrive Mode will add path tracing to Cyberpunk 2077, though this driver has only a sneak peek of the full implementation that will be added later. Resident Evil 4 launches alongside Diablo 4's beta this Friday, March 24. In GameSpot's Resident Evil 4 review, critic Kurt Indovina gave the game a 10/10, calling it a masterful new version of one of the greatest games ever made. "Like the Resident Evil 2 remake before it, the studio has used advancements in technology and design to modernize an iconic survival-horror and action game by placing emphasis on capturing the spirit of the original, and respectfully evoking the same sense of atmosphere and tone that the original developers aspired to," they wrote.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;詳細句子文法解析：&lt;br&gt;1. "Ahead of the release of Capcom's Resident Evil 4 remake and the launch of Diablo 4's open beta this week, Nvidia has released its latest Game Ready drivers for GeForce cards."&lt;br&gt;此句話中，使用了介系詞"ahead of"從事將來的動作。這個說法指稱，在某事件發生之前有某部分事情完成。進一步來說，起因為即將上市的Resident Evil 4重製版和Diablo 4測試版推出。所以為了保障遊戲玩家的權益，Nvidia推出了最新版本的Game Ready driver。&lt;br&gt;2. "The driver update also features a number of other features for popular games, including Cyberpunk 2077 and Forza Horizon 5."&lt;br&gt;此句話中涉及到以features作為名詞的複數使用方式。這種用法相當於“特性”或“功能”，指的是將所有包括這些特性或功能的特性和功能進行清單管理之意。因此，此句話意味著這次的軟體更新支援更多的著名遊戲，例如Cyberpunk 2077和Forza Horizon 5。&lt;br&gt;3. "As a blog postI reveals, the driver supports the technology preview for Cyberpunk 2077's ray tracing Overdrive Mode, the DLSS 3 update for Forza Horizon 5, and The Last Of Us Part 1's DLSS 2 features."&lt;br&gt;這個句子中，使用了冠詞"a"，而非"the"，展示出一個未知的部分。在此情況下，冠詞"a"揭示出作者是指網誌的一篇文章，而不是所有網誌文章。此句話也涉及到主要聯合使用3個分句：支援Cyberpunk 2077超載模式中的射線追蹤技術預覽、支援Forza Horizon-5的DLSS 3更新和支援DLSS 2功能的The Last Of Us Part 1。這個例句向讀者呈現了非常專業、技術性的專利設定。&lt;br&gt;4. "Resident Evil 4 launches alongside Diablo 4's beta this Friday, March 24."&lt;br&gt;這句話選用了介系詞“alongside”，帶有“平行、與...一起”的含義。所以，Resident Evil 4的重製版和Diablo 4測試版將會在同一時間同步運行。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;單字：&lt;br&gt;1. Launches - 發射；啟動；展開(Noun/Verb.) (日文：打ち上げ Chūkō ("ch" 的發音跟中文的"ch" 很像))&lt;br&gt;2. Beta - 測試版本(Test version of a product or software) (日文：ベータ版 Bēta-ban)&lt;br&gt;3. Implement - 實施；貫徹；履行(Verb.) (日文：実行する Jikkō suru)&lt;br&gt;4. Update - 更新；升級(Verb.) (日文：ユぴーだとする Yupī da to suru)&lt;br&gt;5. Showcase - 展示(Optional) (日文：ショーケース Shōkēsu)&lt;br&gt;6. Algorithm - 演算法；詞操作法(Noun.) (日文：アルゴリズム Arugorizumu)&lt;br&gt;7. Overdrive - 超速運行(Noun, indicating a state of top or extreme performance) (日文：オーバードライブ Ōbādoraibu)&lt;br&gt;8. Atmosphere - 氛圍(Noun.) (日文：アトモスフィア Atomosufia)&lt;br&gt;9. Preview - 預覽(Noun/Verb) (日文：プレビュー Purebyū)&lt;br&gt;10. Technology - 技術；科技(Noun.) (日文：テクノロジー Tekunorojī)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;單字記憶方式：&lt;br&gt;1. Launches日語發音為“Chūkō”，中文意思大概是“啟動”，可以聯想一把鑰匙要開啟一門大門。媒名與日期，留下的"((CAPCOM品牌)) Resident Evil 4的beta將在"2022年06月02日""這句話中的"(launches)"，這不難記管理期&lt;br&gt;2. Beta這動詞是指產品或軟體的測試版本，因此可以直接聯想到日本同音的“Bēta”。媒體名註，拿此代表成功；&lt;br&gt;3. Implement描繪了實務運作資料的動作。中文聯想成為實施，達成。 &lt;br&gt;4. Update有更新與升級的意思，和日語的“Yupī da to suru”（升級）有一樣的音，在抽象的IT領域中着重表示知識的更新與傳達。 &lt;br&gt;5. Showcase，自今年3月18日 Capcom 舉行的安排展宣段上推出與畫面紹介間的唯一新視頻亮相，以提示重製版的規劃竣工將于不久假期饑渴玩家與品牌迷手拉手。相對應地，中文應表示成 展出/展覽/展銷。   &lt;br&gt;6. Algorithm可以取字首或末兩秒作為結合聯想。算為+解謎公式。 &lt;br&gt;    &lt;br&gt;     选拔+尔踍+入倒，聯想概括成某天(或核鑰說) 信息不通過，专家们不断地计算和 Debugger 就像一个解释代码公式的演化,觸動心感慨無奈； &lt;br&gt;7. Overdrive這是個描述當你玩遊戲的時候，感光元件用的效能非常高，使得產生火焰的速度接近畫面的刷新率。聯想火箭花費所有燃料向露西前進！ &lt;br&gt;8. Atmosphere，在某個地方感到的典型情境切片尺風貌。利用油畫製造一些氾濫的方式：p i a r s t y   g r &lt;br&gt;9. Preview -含義就是预览；前瞻性。信息幹擾后使用手符忍受不了戀物癖    窺視、預覽　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　&lt;br&gt;10. Today's world is dominated by the power of technology. Middle Eastern countries like Bahrain's technology have either invented any new technology nor contributed much to develop those invention of technology.。獨立人士的游戏也不是问都没问就可以发布，创作出来的游戏一定有多少种测试设备。當然，中文依舊保持召數字辨識阿基米德與多邻国的比拼。 &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;       &lt;br&gt;     &lt;br&gt; 片語：&lt;br&gt; 1. Ahead of - (The action should take depending on some time in future) 提前;預先;在⋯之前(all different versions for"before" in simple present tense.)&lt;br&gt; 相似片語: Prior to(路上) &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; 2. Alongside - 根據使用(describing context)而有許多解釋; 就近;沿著某物的旁邊；跟…一起。&lt;br&gt; 相似片語: Parallel to(平行於); Close to&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; 其它：&lt;br&gt; ※ 此代表示学术討論之用的api原始碼 ：&lt;div&gt;Kurt Indovina gave the game a &lt;span class="num"&gt;10/10&lt;/span&gt;, calling it a masterful new version of one of the greatest games ever made. &amp;ldquo;Like the Resident Evil 2 remake before it, the studio has used advancements in technology and design to modernize an iconic survival-horror and action game by placing emphasis on capturing the spirit of the original, and respectfully evoking the same sense of atmosphere and tone that the original developers aspired to,&amp;rdquo; they wrote.&lt;/div&gt; 。综上，此部分核心内容在解释蛋码“div”所表现的 HTML 的类("num")如何起伏变化相应程度值，以及不容错认的精美评价加分，以订阅节日玩家反复选择購買保值性可能。</content><link href="https://www.gamespot.com/articles/new-nvidia-drivers-for-diablo-4-resident-evil-4-released/1100-6512642/" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>