<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><id>https://github.com/weg38asyy/GameRss.git</id><title>My Game Rss</title><updated>2023-03-31T13:11:08.895374+00:00</updated><author><name>Koala</name><email>weg38asyy@gmail.com</email></author><link href="https://github.com/weg38asyy" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Personal learning of English use</subtitle><entry><id>https://www.gamespot.com/articles/how-dungeons-dragons-honor-among-thieves-makes-dd-easy-to-understand-for-newbies/1100-6512854/</id><title>How Dungeons &amp; Dragons: Honor Among Thieves Makes D&amp;D Easy To Understand For Newbies</title><updated>2023-03-31T13:11:08.895669+00:00</updated><content type="html">Dungeons &amp; Dragons: Honor Among Thieves is in theaters March 31, and the big-screen epic tale has, thus far, been met with very positive reviews. Over at GameSpot sister site Metacritic, the movie is sitting pretty with a score of 71 and that had to be thanks, in some small part, to the fact that this is a film that is approachable for everyone, whether you've mounted your own D&amp;D campaign or not. &lt;br&gt; When it comes to a property with such deep lore over several decades, properly capturing it in a way that appeals to longtime fans is daunting. However, according to the film's writers and directors, Jonathan Goldstein and John Francis Daley, that wasn't even the hard part. Instead, it was finding a way of explaining everything to people with no knowledge of D&amp;D that was the real hurdle. &lt;br&gt; "[That was the] bigger challenge even than appealing to the fans, because we knew we had the material with the lore and the 50 years of history behind us to really give players of the game something that they will appreciate," Daly explained to GameSpot. "The bigger challenge was to give something to the people who have absolutely nothing to do with Dungeons &amp; Dragons--or know nothing about it--a movie that they will also enjoy. And what I would say is, you know, we were very authentic. Everything--every spell that you see--is accurate, is true-to-life authentic. All of our creatures, or monsters or environments are all part of the lore. But again, you do not have to know anything about that for it to work." &lt;br&gt; According to Goldstein, accomplishing that meant not leaving too heavily on established lore when building the story. &lt;br&gt; "I think a lot of people assume that we sort of took this vast law and then whittled it down to our movie," he said. "But in a way, it was the opposite. We started with our characters. What kind of details could we tell about these people that you would invest in and care about? And then that naturally led to the narrative. Okay, where do we want to put them? What do we want to throw at them in terms of monsters and challenges and things? And luckily, the world of D&amp;D is so vast that there's 20 different options for each of those moments. So it made our job easier." &lt;br&gt; Ultimately, what they ended up with is a movie drenched in elements of Dungeons &amp; Dragons gameplay, from creatures and powers to locations and plot elements, that is easy to understand. Much like Marvel does with some of its bigger comic book concepts in the MCU, Honor Among Thieves is easily accessible, despite its deep history. And if you're new to the world of D&amp;D and that interests you, there are dozens of books, campaigns, and deep dives into the lore waiting once the film wraps up. &lt;br&gt; If you are a fan, though, don't think you were disregarded when it came to building this movie. After all, nobody is going to be as excited to see a live-action mimic chest attempting to eat people more than a D&amp;D fan that's found themselves on the wrong side of one in a previous campaign. &lt;br&gt; Dungeons &amp; Dragons: Honor Among Thieves is in theaters Friday.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;詳細句子文法解析：&lt;br&gt;1. "Dungeons &amp; Dragons: Honor Among Thieves is in theaters March 31, and the big-screen epic tale has, thus far, been met with very positive reviews." &lt;br&gt;這是一個複合句，包含了兩個獨立子句：主要子句為"Dungeons &amp; Dragons: Honor Among Thieves is in theaters March 31"，第二個子句則是"the big-screen epic tale has, thus far, been met with very positive reviews."，兩個子句由"and"連結。值得注意的文法重點為動詞時態，"is"使用現在進行式，"has been met"使用現在完成式，表現了一個正在進行的狀態，以及一個已經完成的動作延續到現在的狀態。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. "According to the film's writers and directors, Jonathan Goldstein and John Francis Daley, that wasn't even the hard part." &lt;br&gt;這是一個複合句，包含兩個從屬子句。其中一個是由"That"引導的同位語從句，修飾先行詞"the hard part"。另一個則是由"According to"開頭的介詞片語，表達作者得到的資訊來源。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. "And what I would say is, you know, we were very authentic." &lt;br&gt;這是一個複合句，有兩個從屬子句。其中一個是由"What"引導的同位語從句，用來補充對前面內容給予的回應。另一個是"you know"所引導的插入語，運用口語化的表達方式，更貼近生活中的對話內容。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. "But in a way, it was the opposite." &lt;br&gt;這是一個複合句，包含主要子句和從屬子句。從屬子句由"But"引導，表達主句的相反意思，使句子結構更為豐富。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. "And if you're new to the world of D&amp;D and that interests you, there are dozens of books, campaigns, and deep dives into the lore waiting once the film wraps up." &lt;br&gt;這是一個複合句，包含兩個獨立子句，"And"與"If"相連。其中，"If"引導的是一個條件句，"If you're new to the world of D&amp;D and that interests you"表達了一種假設，後面是主句，表述的是一個事實或者結果，句式結構比較優美。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;單字：&lt;br&gt;1. Approachable：易接近的；易理解的&lt;br&gt;容易記憶的方法：聯想「A考 Prep 規劃布置」，因為這個單字的拼音和它的意思相近。&lt;br&gt;日文單字：アプローチ可能(アプローチかのう)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Whittled：削減；切削；修剪&lt;br&gt;容易記憶的方法：聯想成「提木桿」，本來木頭很長，被削成想要的形狀。&lt;br&gt;日文單字：削減する(さくげんする)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. Lore：知識；學問；故事；傳說&lt;br&gt;容易記憶的方法：聯想成「樂兒」，語音類似，可以記得名詞給人感性而又充滿故事感的氛圍。&lt;br&gt;日文單字：ロア(ろあ)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. Authentic：真實的；可信的；有根據的&lt;br&gt;容易記憶的方法：聯想成「阿蒂的簽名」，意思是阿蒂真的簽了名，因此是真的、可信的。&lt;br&gt;日文單字：正真な(まっしぐらな)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. Narrative：敘述；故事&lt;br&gt;容易記憶的方法：聯想成「奶茶瑞視」，瑞視（日本製）也有「敘述、故事」的意思，透過這個聯想可以记起这个单字。&lt;br&gt;日文單字：説話(せわ)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;片語：&lt;br&gt;1. In terms of：在...的條件下；就...而言&lt;br&gt;類似片語：With respect to (相較之下)&lt;br&gt;反義片語：Out of terms with (不一致)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Mount a campaign：發起一個運動或活動&lt;br&gt;類似片語：Launch a scheme（發起一個密謀）&lt;br&gt;反義片語：Withdraw from an activity（退出）&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. Drenched in：充滿；濕透&lt;br&gt;類似片語：Filled with（充滿）&lt;br&gt;反義片語：Deprived of (被剝奪)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;其它：&lt;br&gt;1. 建議學生可以透過閱讀英語原文，並對其中的單字、語法有所了解，并用中文概括文章大意及實際內容加深理解，提高聽、說、讀、寫能力。&lt;br&gt;2. 英文單字的發音對學習有很大的影響，建議學生注意語音，經常練習聽力和口語能力。&lt;br&gt;3. 在學習單字的過程中，除了記憶，也要注意單字的應用。加強英文閱讀和寫作能力的同時，也需要運用單詞來增強自己的容詞和副詞修飾式，能更有效的達到提高英語文教能力的目的。</content><link href="https://www.gamespot.com/articles/how-dungeons-dragons-honor-among-thieves-makes-dd-easy-to-understand-for-newbies/1100-6512854/" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>