<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><id>https://github.com/weg38asyy/GameRss.git</id><title>My Game Rss</title><updated>2023-06-13T13:11:17.569317+00:00</updated><author><name>Koala</name><email>weg38asyy@gmail.com</email></author><link href="https://github.com/weg38asyy" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Personal learning of English use</subtitle><entry><id>https://www.gamespot.com/articles/all-scosglen-altar-of-lilith-locations-in-diablo-4/1100-6514822/</id><title>All Scosglen Altar Of Lilith Locations In Diablo 4</title><updated>2023-06-13T13:11:17.569569+00:00</updated><content type="html">Scosglen is a region in the northern part of Diablo 4's world, which you will traverse in the mid to late campaign. Scattered throughout this region are Altars of Lilith, a type of collectible that awards small, permanent bonuses of finding them. These Altars are typically tucked away in small corners, hidden in the open-world environment. Below we have maps of all 34 Altar of Lilith locations in Scosglen, split into the eastern, western, and northern parts of the region. &lt;br&gt; If you are in the area of an Altar of Lilith but unsure exactly where it is, check for small nooks in the map, as these Altars are frequently tucked into small corners. Sometimes they are also hidden inside buildings and can even be behind breakable objects in the environment. More often than not, each Altar of Lilith won't be immediately visible upon entering an area. There are also a few Altars inside a Stronghold, but you can exit without finishing it as soon as you find the Altar of Lilith if you want to. &lt;br&gt; Collecting an Altar of Lilith in Diablo 4 provides two types of benefits. The first is the more immediate bonus, which provides a permanent benefit to all of your characters in that same world. This bonus can include increased maximum health, increased maximum Murmuring Obols capacity, and flat stat boosts, like +2 Dexterity. &lt;br&gt; Finding an Altar of Lilith also provides 10 Region Renown. Each region has its own Renown, with five tiers of rewards provided at different amounts of total renown. Collecting all of the Altars of Lilith in a single region will provide just about one tiers worth of Renown, depending on which tier you are currently at. &lt;br&gt; For more Diablo 4 guides, like class builds, check out GameSpot's Diablo 4 Guides Hub.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;詳細句子文法解析：&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. "Scosglen is a region in the northern part of Diablo 4's world" - 這是一個簡單的陳述句，主題是Scosglen，動詞是"is"，其後的修飾語指出在哪裡。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. "which you will traverse in the mid to late campaign" - 這是一個限制性從句，先置於句子的主體Scosglen後，由「which」引導說明其隨後句子的時間及意義。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. "Scattered throughout this region are Altars of Lilith, a type of collectible that awards small, permanent bonuses of finding them" - 這是一個複合句，包含一個獨立子句"Scattered throughout this region are Altars of Lilith"及其敘述的內容。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. "These Altars are typically tucked away in small corners, hidden in the open-world environment" - 這是一個簡單的陳述句，主題是These Altars，動詞是"are"，其後的修飾語說明位置及特徵。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. "Below we have maps of all 34 Altar of Lilith locations in Scosglen, split into the eastern, western, and northern parts of the region" - 這是一個複合句，包含一個獨立子句"Below we have maps of all 34 Altar of Lilith locations in Scosglen"，以及由"split into the eastern, western, and northern parts of the region"引導的從句，其用意是說明前述句子提供的地圖資料。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;6. "If you are in the area of an Altar of Lilith but unsure exactly where it is, check for small nooks in the map, as these Altars are frequently tucked into small corners" - 這是一個條件句與時間形容詞從句複合句，前者的目的是說明後者所述情況(當你不確定Altar of Lilith的位置)，後者則指出解決方法及其特徵。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;7. "Sometimes they are also hidden inside buildings and can even be behind breakable objects in the environment" - 這是一個簡單的陳述句，指出另一種可能的Altar of Lilith位置。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;8. "More often than not, each Altar of Lilith won't be immediately visible upon entering an area" - 這是一個簡單的陳述句，指出Altar of Lilith通常不會很明顯，必須仔細尋找。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;9. "There are also a few Altars inside a Stronghold, but you can exit without finishing it as soon as you find the Altar of Lilith if you want to" - 這是一個複合句，包含一個獨立子句"There are also a few Altars inside a Stronghold"及其限制性從句，由"but"引導說明解決方案。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;10. "Collecting an Altar of Lilith in Diablo 4 provides two types of benefits" - 這是一個簡單的陳述句，指出Altar of Lilith的收集會產生兩種好處。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;單字：&lt;br&gt;1. traverse 翻轉、橫越。中文聯想：這個單字和"cross"有相近的意思，與路徑有關。&lt;br&gt;2. scattered 分散；散布。中文聯想：和"分散"這個中文單字發音相近。&lt;br&gt;3. collectible 收藏品。中文聯想：遺物，遺失。&lt;br&gt;4. tucked away 藏起來的。中文聯想：tucked是襯邊的意思，裝飾性的設計，因此Tucked away有一種藏匿起來的意思。&lt;br&gt;5. nook 角落。中文聯想："n"字型道路上有一個沒有信號燈的交通熱點，通常也是插頭的一個角落，所以可以聯想到nook表示的是一個角落、陰暗角落等位置。&lt;br&gt;6. frequently 頻繁地。中文聯想：「很勤勞 -&gt; 頻繁」，設法和"勤勞方面的含意"聯想在一起。&lt;br&gt;7. breakable 可破壞的。中文聯想：和"Frangible"這個單字意思類似。&lt;br&gt;8. environment 環境。中文聯想：和中文的詞語會彼此影響，考慮到環境的影響。&lt;br&gt;9. renown 名譽、聲譽。中文聯想：認真打完任務或考試的"好名聲"。&lt;br&gt;10. hub 中心。中文聯想：「專任營運據點」 -&gt; 中心。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;片語：&lt;br&gt;相似片語： gather up 收集，簡單明了的收集片語。&lt;br&gt;反義片語： scatter around 散佈，相對於"聚集"的approaching而言，"scatter"即是"散佈"的意思</content><link href="https://www.gamespot.com/articles/all-scosglen-altar-of-lilith-locations-in-diablo-4/1100-6514822/" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>