<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><id>https://github.com/weg38asyy/GameRss.git</id><title>My Game Rss</title><updated>2023-06-25T13:11:40.427278+00:00</updated><author><name>Koala</name><email>weg38asyy@gmail.com</email></author><link href="https://github.com/weg38asyy" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Personal learning of English use</subtitle><entry><id>https://www.gamespot.com/articles/forza-horizon-1-and-forza-horizon-2-will-go-offline-on-august-22/1100-6515467/</id><title>Forza Horizon 1 And Forza Horizon 2 Will Go Offline On August 22</title><updated>2023-06-25T13:11:40.427586+00:00</updated><content type="html">Turn 10 Studios announced it will shut down its online services for Forza Horizon and Forza Horizon 2 on August 22. The reason for this is so the studio "can focus on our most current games." &lt;br&gt; Thanks to a Forza blog post, we know that you'll still be able to play offline in single-player modes. But online features such as matchmaking, leaderboards browsing, and downloading of online user-generated content, including liveries, vinyls, tuning setups, and photos, will all disappear. &lt;br&gt; It's also worth mentioning that Forza Horizon 2 Presents Fast &amp; Furious will also go offline. But if you've already purchased any of these games, you can still redownload them whenever you want. &lt;br&gt; Turn 10 Studios shared its thoughts on closing online services for both Forza Horizon 1 and 2 by saying: &lt;br&gt; "We know our community has fond memories of exploring Colorado and Southern Europe in Forza Horizon 1 and 2, from meeting new friends on road trips to sharing liveries, photos, and tunes, and we thank you all for your incredible passion, support and dedication over the last decade." &lt;br&gt; Forza Horizon was released on the Xbox 360 in 2012, while Forza Horizon 2 was released in 2014 and came out on the Xbox 360 and Xbox One. Both received excellent reviews upon release, with Forza Horizon receiving an 8.5 in our review and Forza Horizon 2 receiving an 8. &lt;br&gt; For more Xbox-related news, check out our story on how The Elder Scroll 6 doesn't have a platform yet, and is five-plus years away and how Xbox would suffer "irreparable harm" if it went back on CoD PlayStation promises.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;詳細句子文法解析：&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. Turn 10 Studios announced it will shut down its online services for Forza Horizon and Forza Horizon 2 on August 22.&lt;br&gt;   - 分析：這是一個複合句，其中宣布停止電玩服務的部分為主要子句，而"Forza Horizon and Forza Horizon 2"是這個主要子句的賓語。其中宣布停止電玩服務的部分是主要的主詞+動詞，告訴讀者開始句子主要表達的動作或事件。而賓語告訴我們這個動作針對某個特定的事物。 &lt;br&gt;   - 文法重點：複合句，主要子句加賓語&lt;br&gt;   &lt;br&gt;2. The reason for this is so the studio "can focus on our most current games."&lt;br&gt;   - 分析：這是一個複合句，其中表示原因的部份為主要子句，而引言則為這個複合句的從屬子句。從屬子句說明主詞所說的原因。&lt;br&gt;   - 文法重點：複合句，主要子句加從屬子句&lt;br&gt;   &lt;br&gt;3. Thanks to a Forza blog post, we know that you'll still be able to play offline in single-player modes.&lt;br&gt;   - 分析：這是一個複合句，其中"Thanks to a Forza blog post"為表示原因的從屬子句，主要子句是"You'll still be able to play offline in single-player modes." &lt;br&gt;   - 文法重點：複合句，從屬子句&lt;br&gt;   &lt;br&gt;4. But online features such as matchmaking, leaderboards browsing, and downloading of online user-generated content, including liveries, vinyls, tuning setups, and photos, will all disappear.&lt;br&gt;   - 分析：這是一個簡單句，因為主詞和動詞都在同一個簡單的子句中。&lt;br&gt;   - 文法重點：簡單句&lt;br&gt;   &lt;br&gt;5. It's also worth mentioning that Forza Horizon 2 Presents Fast &amp; Furious will also go offline.&lt;br&gt;   - 分析：這是一個簡單句，其中主詞和動詞都寫在同一個子句中。&lt;br&gt;   - 文法重點：簡單句&lt;br&gt;   &lt;br&gt;6. But if you've already purchased any of these games, you can still redownload them whenever you want.&lt;br&gt;   - 分析：這是一個複合句，首先各位還沒有買的人當然不會去重下載，盡管如此，指向"but if"表示條件的狀態語句被添加到句子中以指出前提必須具備 (即，如果你已經購買了這些遊戲) 才會發生某件事情 (即，你還可以在任何時間重下載) 。&lt;br&gt;   - 文法重點：複合句，條件句&lt;br&gt;   &lt;br&gt;7. Turn 10 Studios shared its thoughts on closing online services for both Forza Horizon 1 and 2 by saying:&lt;br&gt;   - 分析：這是一個簡單句，其中用到了形容詞子句來形容 Turn 10 Studio。省略的內容為 Turn 10 Studios 所想的 `(thoughts)`。&lt;br&gt;   - 文法重點：簡單句，形容詞子句&lt;br&gt;   &lt;br&gt;8. "We know our community has fond memories of exploring Colorado and Southern Europe in Forza Horizon 1 and 2, from meeting new friends on road trips to sharing liveries, photos, and tunes, and we thank you all for your incredible passion, support and dedication over the last decade."&lt;br&gt;   - 分析：這是一個複合句，其中句子"We know our community has fond memories..." is主要子句 as ,並以連接詞"and"連接所有感謝相關的詞組。&lt;br&gt;   - 文法重點：複合句&lt;br&gt;   &lt;br&gt;9. Forza Horizon was released on the Xbox 360 in 2012 while Forza Horizon 2 was released in 2014 and came out on the Xbox 360 and Xbox One.&lt;br&gt;   - 分析：這是一個複合句，在這種情況下，使用逗號分開開始時間(Time Marker)。&lt;br&gt;   - 文法重點：複合句，時間標記、逗號分隔&lt;br&gt;   &lt;br&gt;10. Both received excellent reviews upon release, with Forza Horizon receiving an 8.5 in our review and Forza Horizon 2 receiving an 8.&lt;br&gt;   - 分析：這是一個複合句，其中這個句子的 "Both received excellent reviews upon release" 為通過2個介詞短語和omma 與關鍵詞脫穎而出。這使用反轉句子結構，將修飾語放在詞語的前面，以避免過多的介詞短語。 &lt;br&gt;   - 文法重點：複合句，介詞短語、反轉句子結構&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;單字：&lt;br&gt;1. announce (公告) - 英文諧音方法：把announce視作"安~宁~斯"(An-Nounce)，將"安"連接到一個MP3與"宁"之後再連接到另一個MP3，之後說"安斯An-S"&lt;br&gt;   日文單字：発表(happyou)&lt;br&gt;   &lt;br&gt;2. offline (離線) - 拆解後詞彙聯想：拆成 "off" and "line"，off表沒有，line表線，暗示著 在沒線之外&lt;br&gt;   日文單字：オフライン(ofurain)&lt;br&gt;   &lt;br&gt;3. disappear (消失) - 英文諧音方法：把disappear跟dissapeer(朝貢)聯想在一起，兩者的發音很相似&lt;br&gt;   日文單字：消える(kieru)&lt;br&gt;   &lt;br&gt;4. purchase (購買) - 拆解後詞彙聯想：拆成"pur(貼近)" and  "chase(追逐)", 直接暗示著貼近追逐貨物的行為&lt;br&gt;   日文單字：購入(kounyuu)&lt;br&gt;   &lt;br&gt;5. memories (回憶) - 英文諧音方法：把memories跟mummies木乃伊聯想在一起，下意識地想到一些被保存下來的事物&lt;br&gt;   日文單字：思い出(omoide)&lt;br&gt;   &lt;br&gt;6. exploring (探索) - 英文單字復習：-ing為所謂的現在分詞，有時被稱為進行中形式，其中動詞+ ing一般被用作動詞形容詞或作為現在或過去時的一部分。&lt;br&gt;   日文單字：探検(tanken)&lt;br&gt;   &lt;br&gt;7. community (社區) - 拆解後詞彙聯想：拆解社區成 "社(shè, 此) &amp; 區(qū, 局)", 指程序運作範圍，網路環境上某一群體(局)的使用同一系統和安裝在不同主機上的同一套程式，在此情況下的區，即社群。&lt;br&gt;   日文單字：コミュニティ(komyuniti)&lt;br&gt;   &lt;br&gt;8. fond (挚爱的) - 英文諧音方法：把fond跟繁忙(funny)，聯想在一起，因為當你忙碌時認可和者的時間少。因此你結束所做的是布滿挚爱感覺。&lt;br&gt;   日文單字：好きな(sukina)&lt;br&gt;   &lt;br&gt;9. dedication (獻身) - 英文諧音方法：把dedication和"the days Asian"聯想到一起，有時候英文萬聖節在日本被簡稱為" the days Asian",視作一種對集體事業的自我獻身(毀滅)。&lt;br&gt;   日文單字：献身(kenshin)&lt;br&gt;   &lt;br&gt;10. reviews (回顧) - 拆解後詞彙聯想：拆成 "re(再次)" and  "views(看法)", 暗示著在看上前者評論測試&lt;br&gt;   日文單字：レビュー(rebyuu)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;片語：&lt;br&gt;1. 相似片語：online services (線上服務), 反義片語：offline services (離線服務)&lt;br&gt;2. 相似片語：single-player modes (單人模式), 反義片語：multiplayer modes (多人模式)&lt;br&gt;3. 相似片語：user-generated content (使用者產生的內容), 反義片語：officially generated content (官方發布的內容)&lt;br&gt;4. 相似片語：focus on (集中於), 反義片語：divert from (偏離，分散)&lt;br&gt;5. 相似片語：excellent reviews (優秀評價), 反義片語：poor reviews (差評) &lt;br&gt;6. 相似片語：shut down (關閉), 反義片語：start up (啟動) &lt;br&gt;7. 相似片語：exploring Colorado and Southern Europe (探索科羅拉多州和南歐), 反義片語：avoiding Colorado and Southern Europe (避開科羅拉多州和南歐) &lt;br&gt;8. 相似片語：redownload them (重新下載他們), 反義片語：deleted them permanently (永久刪除它們) &lt;br&gt;9. 相似片語：share liveries, photos, and tunes (分享外套、照片和音響), 反義片語：keep liveries, photos, and tunes private(保持外套、照片和音響私人)&lt;br&gt;10. 相似片語：matchmaking and leaderboards browsing(配對和排行榜瀏覽)，反義片語：playing alone and avoiding scoreboards(單獨遊玩且避開排行榜)</content><link href="https://www.gamespot.com/articles/forza-horizon-1-and-forza-horizon-2-will-go-offline-on-august-22/1100-6515467/" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>