<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><id>https://github.com/weg38asyy/GameRss.git</id><title>My Game Rss</title><updated>2023-04-14T13:11:03.629123+00:00</updated><author><name>Koala</name><email>weg38asyy@gmail.com</email></author><link href="https://github.com/weg38asyy" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Personal learning of English use</subtitle><entry><id>https://www.gamespot.com/articles/get-up-to-15-games-for-10-in-the-latest-fanatical-bundle/1100-6513256/</id><title>Get Up To 15 Games For $10 In The Latest Fanatical Bundle</title><updated>2023-04-14T13:11:03.629381+00:00</updated><content type="html">The publisher Handy Games is celebrating its 23rd anniversary this month with a massive build-your-own bundle at Fanatical. With this deal, you can grab up to 15 Hand Games-published titles for just $10. There is also a three-game option for $3 and a seven-game tier for $6 if you want a smaller bundle. &lt;br&gt; Fanatical’s DIY deals usually offer a wide swathe of games to pick from, but the Handy Games Anniversary bundle has a whopping 39 games and DLC packs to choose from. &lt;br&gt; Some notable options include the 3D action-adventure Scarf and the side-scrolling shoot-’em-up Sine Mora EX. There are also 2D platformers like Giana Sisters (multiple titles), strategy games like Nexus: The Jupiter Incident, arcade flying games like Skydrift Infinity, and so much more. This is even the perfect opportunity to pick up the “so bad it’s good” cult adventure game, The Mystery of the Druids, for cheap. &lt;br&gt; There are dozens of other titles to pick from. Check the full lineup below, or head over to Fanatical to build your bundle. Along with your games, you also get a free 5%-off coupon code to use on other Fanatical orders. &lt;br&gt; One Hand Clapping &lt;br&gt; Best Gaming &amp; Tech Deals This Week&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;詳細句子文法解析：&lt;br&gt;- The publisher Handy Games is celebrating its 23rd anniversary this month with a massive build-your-own bundle at Fanatical.&lt;br&gt;句子主詞為 The publisher Handy Games，謂詞為 is celebrating，其後修飾成分為其23週年，使用其後置形式修飾此主詞。with a massive build-your-own bundle at Fanatical 為進一步的說明，表示其慶祝週年活動的方式，也是介系詞短語作用。&lt;br&gt;- With this deal, you can grab up to 15 Hand Games-published titles for just $10.&lt;br&gt;句子主詞為 you，謂詞為 can grab，其後使用介系詞短語 With this deal 作為修飾其謂詞之用，表示條件。&lt;br&gt;- There is also a three-game option for $3 and a seven-game tier for $6 if you want a smaller bundle.&lt;br&gt;句子主詞為 There，謂詞為 is，其後使用 Is 方式形式代替一個以 a three-game option 和 a seven-game tier 為主詞之複合句，這些主詞後緊接著 for $3 和 for $6 的價格為謂詞。if you want a smaller bundle 為條件子句，表示前述主詞價格為小型慶祝套餐，額外勾選此選項之用。&lt;br&gt;- Fanatical’s DIY deals usually offer a wide swathe of games to pick from, but the Handy Games Anniversary bundle has a whopping 39 games and DLC packs to choose from.&lt;br&gt;句子主詞為 Fanatical's DIY deals，謂詞為 usually offer；其後使用介系詞短語 to pick from 作為句子核心選擇之用；but 之後的句子改以特殊狀態字從句表示动态; the Handy Games Anniversary bundle 為進一步說明，這是此慶隆禮包的詳細項目資料。&lt;br&gt;- Some notable options include the 3D action-adventure Scarf and the side-scrolling shoot-’em-up Sine Mora EX.&lt;br&gt;使用 Some + 名詞 從句，表示了一些注意事項，其中 include 表示 「包含於...之中」；and 之後以舉例方式包含細節說明。&lt;br&gt;- This is even the perfect opportunity to pick up the “so bad it’s good” cult adventure game, The Mystery of the Druids, for cheap.&lt;br&gt;主詞為 This，謂詞為 is，表示「這條目是」；接著 use -ing 代替動詞作為一個 reduced clause；to pick up 在此使用為取得的意思，another word for purchase，而「它」所指的 antecedent 為下文中的 The Mystery of the Druids。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;單字：&lt;br&gt;- celebrate：慶祝、慶典&lt;br&gt;記憶方法：`celebrate` ，既然是要慶祝，所以就像 `celebrity` 表示「名人」一樣，可以聯想起這個字。&lt;br&gt;- massive：巨大的、龐大的&lt;br&gt;記憶方法：`massive` 的英文解釋就是大、堅固的，因此我們可以直接將「大」與其聯繫起來。&lt;br&gt;- option：選擇、選項&lt;br&gt;記憶方法：`option` 的發音和 "選" 後半部的 "擇" 基本一樣，可以通過發音聯繫「選擇」與其意思。&lt;br&gt;- cheap：便宜的、不貴的&lt;br&gt;記憶方法：`cheap` 類似於「小氣、吝嗇」的意思，在物品上有「貨值低廉」的涵義。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;片語：&lt;br&gt;- build-your-own bundle：自選慶祝套餐&lt;br&gt;- side-scrolling shoot-’em-up：橫向捲軸型遊戲&lt;br&gt;- so bad it’s good：因為太差了所以很好&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;相似片語： &lt;br&gt;- all or nothing：非此即彼、完全的一切&lt;br&gt;- more or less：或多或少、大體上&lt;br&gt;反義片語： &lt;br&gt;- give-and-take：妥協；相互給予和接受&lt;br&gt;- win-win situation：雙贏局面</content><link href="https://www.gamespot.com/articles/get-up-to-15-games-for-10-in-the-latest-fanatical-bundle/1100-6513256/" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>