<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><id>https://github.com/weg38asyy/GameRss.git</id><title>My Game Rss</title><updated>2023-06-15T13:11:47.873997+00:00</updated><author><name>Koala</name><email>weg38asyy@gmail.com</email></author><link href="https://github.com/weg38asyy" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Personal learning of English use</subtitle><entry><id>https://www.gamespot.com/articles/bayonetta-origins-discounted-to-best-price-yet/1100-6511308/</id><title>Bayonetta Origins Discounted To Best Price Yet</title><updated>2023-06-15T13:11:47.874237+00:00</updated><content type="html">Bayonetta Origins: Cereza and the Lost Demon released earlier this year, but you can already save big on the excellent spin-off at Amazon. Bayonetta Origins is on sale for only $43. And if you don't mind a preowned copy, you can get  Bayonetta Origins for $40  at GameFly. It will come with the original case, too. &lt;br&gt;   &lt;br&gt; Bayonetta Origins is quite the departure from the mainline series. You play as two characters, Cereza and Cheshire, simultaneously as you navigate a colorful world from an isometric perspective. There's still action combat, but Bayonetta Origins is more puzzle- and narrative-focused. &lt;br&gt; Despite big changes in style and tone, Bayonetta Origins is more than worthy of its name. It earned a 9/10 in our Bayonetta Origins review. &lt;br&gt; "Bayonetta Origins: Cereza and The Lost Demon is a testament to thinking outside the box," critic Jessica Howard wrote. "While I don't suspect Platinum Games will pivot to this new style of gameplay and storytelling in future Bayonetta games in the same way Breath of the Wild or God of War (2018) shifted the direction of their respective franchises, I cannot help but be thankful that the studio trusted the vision of its team enough to create this experience. Though with how fantastic every aspect of the game is, I understand why the developer did." &lt;br&gt; As a prequel, you can enjoy Bayonetta Origins even if you haven't played the other three games in the franchise. That said, we'd highly recommend playing all three of them. Bayonetta 3, which released last fall, is discounted to $45 at Amazon. &lt;br&gt; For more Nintendo Switch deals, check out the huge Hyper Max sale on digital games. &lt;br&gt; You need a javascript enabled browser to watch videos. &lt;br&gt;          Want us to remember this setting for all your devices?        &lt;br&gt; Sign up or Sign in now!        &lt;br&gt;          By clicking 'enter', you agree to GameSpot's                         Terms of Use and         Privacy Policy &lt;br&gt; enter &lt;br&gt; Best Gaming &amp; Tech Deals This Week&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;詳細句子文法解析：&lt;br&gt;1. "Bayonetta Origins: Cereza and the Lost Demon released earlier this year, but you can already save big on the excellent spin-off at Amazon." - 過去式+already+S+動詞原形 - 已達成某個狀態，強調現在的情況比預期的早。例如：已經做完作業(already finished my homework)&lt;br&gt;2. "Bayonetta Origins is on sale for only $43." - on sale - 特價促銷的意思。&lt;br&gt;3. "And if you don't mind a preowned copy, you can get Bayonetta Origins for $40 at GameFly." - if S + 動詞過去式，就S會做這個動作的情況 - 強調一個條件，當這個條件符合時，才會發生後面的事。例如：如果天氣好，我們可以去戶外(if it's a nice day, we can go outside)&lt;br&gt;4. "There's still action combat, but Bayonetta Origins is more puzzle- and narrative-focused." - but - 但、然而的轉折詞，用意為引出對比或不同狀態。例如：我很喜歡看電影，但我不喜歡看恐怖片(I love watching movies, but I don't like horror movies)&lt;br&gt;5. "Despite big changes in style and tone, Bayonetta Origins is more than worthy of its name." - Despite + N/V-ing - 即使...，強調某個情況下仍然發生了另一件事情。例如：即使下雨，我還是會去跑步(Despite the rain, I still go for a run)&lt;br&gt;6. "It earned a 9/10 in our Bayonetta Origins review." - 介系詞+ 後置定語(our Bayonetta Origins review) - 加強對名詞修飾的描述。例如：我們在台灣的一間小餐廳(dining in our little restaurant in Taiwan)&lt;br&gt;7. ""Bayonetta Origins: Cereza and The Lost Demon is a testament to thinking outside the box," critic Jessica Howard wrote." - a testament to + N/V-ing - 是...的證明，使某件事情有了具體的載體。例如：這本書是你個人成長的證明(This book is a testament to your personal growth)&lt;br&gt;8. "While I don't suspect Platinum Games will pivot to this new style of gameplay and storytelling in future Bayonetta games in the same way Breath of the Wild or God of War (2018) shifted the direction of their respective franchises, I cannot help but be thankful that the studio trusted the vision of its team enough to create this experience." - While + S + 動詞，S + 順比，并列式 - 連接兩個因果關係，強調兩個情況的比較。例如：當我上小學時，我會堅持做完功課，過後才去玩(While I was in elementary school, I always finished my homework before playing)&lt;br&gt;9. "As a prequel, you can enjoy Bayonetta Origins even if you haven't played the other three games in the franchise." - As + S + 動詞，S + 動詞 - 作為、身為某個人或物 - 強調某個身份。例如：作為你的朋友，我不會騙你(As your friend, I won't lie to you)&lt;br&gt;10. "That said, we'd highly recommend playing all three of them." - That said - 表示說完前面的話，進一步補充下文。例如：我同意你的看法，不過我的意見是...(That said, I agree with your opinion, but my opinion is...)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;單字：&lt;br&gt;1. excellent - 優秀的、出色的 (日文：優秀な、すばらしい)&lt;br&gt;2. spin-off - 衍生物、衍生作品 (日文：スピンオフ、スピンオフ作品)&lt;br&gt;3. preowned - 二手的、舊的 (日文：中古の)&lt;br&gt;4. franchise - 授權經營、特許專營 (日文：シリーズ作品)&lt;br&gt;5. departure - 分離、出發 (日文：出発、離れること)&lt;br&gt;6. narrative - 故事的、敘事的 (日文：物語的な、語り手の)&lt;br&gt;7. pivot - 旋轉、中心點 (日文：回転、中心)&lt;br&gt;8. respective - 各自的、 分別的 (日文：それぞれの、各自の)&lt;br&gt;9. prequel - 前傳、前篇 (日文：前日譚、プリクエル)&lt;br&gt;10. recommend - 推薦、建議 (日文：推薦する、勧める)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;(單字輔助：可以使用「編號+中文解釋+英文單字」的方式記憶)&lt;br&gt;1.【優秀的】出色的物品或表現  excellent&lt;br&gt;2.【衍生物】派生出來的作品  spin-off&lt;br&gt;3.【二手的】不是全新的、多有使用過的  preowned&lt;br&gt;4.【授權經營】知名品牌的授權經營商品  franchise&lt;br&gt;5.【分離】撇開一個特定的形式或樣式  departure&lt;br&gt;6.【故事的】關聯到故事的事情  narrative&lt;br&gt;7.【旋轉】原地轉動一個物體  pivot&lt;br&gt;8.【各自的】分別歸屬的體系  respective&lt;br&gt;9.【前傳】一個系列出品之前的段落  prequel&lt;br&gt;10.【推薦】向人推薦物品或行為  recommend&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;片語：&lt;br&gt;1. 相似片語 - on sale - 特價、打折&lt;br&gt;   反義片語 - at regular price - 常價、原價&lt;br&gt;2. 相似片語 - shift in direction - 方向調整、轉型&lt;br&gt;   反義片語 - remain as is - 保持原樣、沒有變化&lt;br&gt;3. 相似片語 - out of the box - 創意、突破常規的&lt;br&gt;   反義片語 - inside the box - 安於現狀、沒有創意&lt;br&gt;4. 相似片語 - according to - 根據、依照&lt;br&gt;   反義片語 - in spite of - 不管、儘管&lt;br&gt;5. 相似片語 - live up to - 符合、達到&lt;br&gt;   反義片語 - fall short of - 未達到、不符合&lt;br&gt;6. 相似片語 - consider that - 考慮到、綜合分析&lt;br&gt;   反義片語 - dismiss that - 忽視、不認為重要&lt;br&gt;7. 相似片語 - despite the fact that - 儘管、雖然&lt;br&gt;   反義片語 - because of - 因為、由於&lt;br&gt;8. 相似片語 - as such - 確切的、正是、實際上&lt;br&gt;   反義片語 - in any other way - 沒有其他的方式、即不可能&lt;br&gt;9. 相似片語 - make the most of - 善加利用、充分利用&lt;br&gt;   反義片語 - waste away - 浪費、荒廢&lt;br&gt;10. 相似片語 - in comparison with - 與...相比、相對地&lt;br&gt;    反義片語 - uniquely - 獨特地、非凡地</content><link href="https://www.gamespot.com/articles/bayonetta-origins-discounted-to-best-price-yet/1100-6511308/" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>