<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><id>https://github.com/weg38asyy/GameRss.git</id><title>My Game Rss</title><updated>2023-06-03T13:13:51.774301+00:00</updated><author><name>Koala</name><email>weg38asyy@gmail.com</email></author><link href="https://github.com/weg38asyy" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Personal learning of English use</subtitle><entry><id>https://www.gamespot.com/articles/diablo-4-secret-of-the-spring-side-quest-and-emote-guide/1100-6514781/</id><title>Diablo 4 - Secret Of The Spring Side Quest And Emote Guide</title><updated>2023-06-03T13:13:51.774939+00:00</updated><content type="html">Diablo 4 is full of side quests, and while many of them simply ask you to mow down the forces of Hell, some of them require a bit more thought. One of those is a side quest called "Secret of the Spring" which can be found just north of the first major hub city Kyovashad. This quest is started when you find a small note with a riddle on it. Here's how to complete it. &lt;br&gt; First, you will need to collect the riddle note that starts the quest off. This note can be found north of Kyovashad near the entrance to the Forsaken Quarry dungeon, marked on the map above by the red circle. The quickest path here is to leave the city via the east exit and stick to the end of the map heading north. Once you find the note, the quest will start marking a small area on the map further north from where the note was found. &lt;br&gt; The note itself reads "Beacon of warmth in winter's embrace, patience rewarded by nature's own grace." Once you reach the location indicated on the map, you will find a small pool of water, which is the spring in the name of the quest. Like some other side quests in Diablo 4, you need to use a specific emote here. What might be confusing to some is that the "patience" noted in the riddle doesn't match anything in the default emote wheel. &lt;br&gt; Instead, open the emote wheel and press the button for Customize and go down the list of unassigned emotes until you find the one labeled Wait. Add the Wait emote to your wheel and then use it next to the spring to spawn a chest. The chest only contained gold and resources for me, but that could vary person to person. The quest completes once you open up the chest. &lt;br&gt; For more information about Diablo 4, like class or dungeon guides, check out GameSpot's Diablo 4 Guides Hub.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;詳細句子文法解析：&lt;br&gt;1. "Diablo 4 is full of side quests, and while many of them simply ask you to mow down the forces of Hell, some of them require a bit more thought." -&gt; 該句為主要子句和時間子句的複雜句。主要者句指出了Diablo 4 中有很多支線任務，時間子句則解釋了這些任務多半只需要玩家打倒惡魔即可完成。&lt;br&gt;2. "One of those is a side quest called "Secret of the Spring" which can be found just north of the first major hub city Kyovashad." -&gt; 該句為主要子句和定語從句的複雜句。主要子句是指「Secret of the Spring」是其中的一個支線任務。定語從句對「Secret of the Spring」進一步解釋「它位於主城Kyovashad以北」。&lt;br&gt;3. "This quest is started when you find a small note with a riddle on it." -&gt; 該句為主要子句和時間從句的簡單複合句。主要子句指這個任務是當你找到帶謎題的小紙條時開始的。時間從句解釋了何時會觸發這個任務的條件。&lt;br&gt;4. "Here's how to complete it." -&gt; 該句為簡單句，指出下文將要提供如何解決這個任務的答案。&lt;br&gt;5. "Once you find the note, the quest will start marking a small area on the map further north from where the note was found." -&gt; 該句為主要子句和時間子句的複雜句。主要子句是指，依照帶謎紙條所提示，在地圖上會標識出一個較之前所找到的紙條北方一些的小地區；時間子句並補充說此標識將會隨著你進度走向而移動。&lt;br&gt;6. "The note itself reads "Beacon of warmth in winter's embrace, patience rewarded by nature's own grace."" -&gt; 該句為簡單句，用以解釋帶謎的紙條為何如此重要。&lt;br&gt;7. "Once you reach the location indicated on the map, you will find a small pool of water, which is the spring in the name of the quest." -&gt; 該句為主要子句和未定義從句的複合句。主要子句指出當你到達被標示在地圖上的位置，你會發現一個小水池，即是這個支線任務中提到的「泉源」；未定義從句解釋了什麼是「泉源」。&lt;br&gt;8. "Like some other side quests in Diablo 4, you need to use a specific emote here." -&gt; 該句為簡單句，指出此一支線任務跟其它任務一樣，需要觸發一個特定技能才可以完成。&lt;br&gt;9. "What might be confusing to some is that the "patience" noted in the riddle doesn't match anything in the default emote wheel." -&gt; 該句為主要子句和名詞子句的複雜句。主要子句指出，謎題中的「耐心」並不能在預設技能輪中找到對應的技能；名詞子句進一步說明這些技能指的是遊戲中默认的一些觸發技能環。&lt;br&gt;10. "The quest completes once you open up the chest." -&gt; 該句為簡單句，指出當你開啟所得到的寶箱時，任務即完成了。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;單字：&lt;br&gt;1. side quests - 側線任務 / サイドクエスト&lt;br&gt;2. mow down - 擊毀；鎮壓殲滅 / なぎ倒す&lt;br&gt;3. forces - 力量；勢力；軍隊 / 力、勢力、軍隊&lt;br&gt;4. require - 需要 / 必要&lt;br&gt;5. thought - 思考；想法；頭腦 / 考え、思考、心理&lt;br&gt;6. riddle - 謎語 / 謎、クイズ&lt;br&gt;7. collect - 收集；取回 / コレクションする&lt;br&gt;8. location - 位置 / ロケーション&lt;br&gt;9. spawn - 出現、複製 / スポーンする&lt;br&gt;10. chest - 箱子 / チェスト&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;單字記憶提示：&lt;br&gt;1. [側邊的線條任務[，想像角色沿著遊戲中的道路走，突然看到一條[邊線]，就像是心血管?沿著邊緣線側邊]，把線條完整求解的道路就是[側邊的線條任務]&lt;br&gt;2. [易懂詞義提醒]，用于表示除草；除掉；消滅之意。&lt;br&gt;3. [暗示錯身單除]，forces與法斯科的發音相似，需要注重發音。&lt;br&gt;4. [仿音]，兩個字母Q和U聚在一起，就一點一滴而言了。&lt;br&gt;5. [針對後半語境]，用于表達對主觀想法、判斷等思考過程。&lt;br&gt;6. [單獨查名詞譯法]，意味著謎語或謎題。&lt;br&gt;7. [真正在遊戲中收集]收集各種物品可以升級或換取獎勵，每當你拿著高貴的東西時，就是要['收集']&lt;br&gt;8. [地點意識強]，指某物或某人特定的定位。&lt;br&gt;9. [真正在遊戲中取得]，指按下一定的鍵后，遊戲中所生成的對象出現在螢幕上。&lt;br&gt;10. [類比箱子]，對於這個單詞，很多玩家第一時間會想到遊戲中的箱子。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;片語：&lt;br&gt;1. simply ask - 只是要求 / 単純に求める&lt;br&gt;2. a bit more thought - 再多想一些 / もう少し考える&lt;br&gt;3. stick to - 遵循；堅持 / 固守&lt;br&gt;4. be found - 被發現；被找到 / 見つけられる&lt;br&gt;5. marked on - 標出於 / 指定された&lt;br&gt;6. further north - 更向北方 / もっと北へ&lt;br&gt;7. be confused - 被困擾；迷惑不解 / 混乱する&lt;br&gt;8. match to - 符合；相互配合 / 一致する&lt;br&gt;9. in the name of - 以………命名 / …の名において&lt;br&gt;10. completes once - 完成一次 / 一度完了する&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;類似片語：&lt;br&gt;1. simply put - 简单来说 / 簡単に言うと&lt;br&gt;2. take more effort - 需要更多的努力 / もっと努力する&lt;br&gt;3. stay on the path - 留在這條路上 / 道を外れない&lt;br&gt;4. be located - 位於 / 位置する&lt;br&gt;5. pointed out - 指出 / 指摘する&lt;br&gt;6. go further - 更进一步 / 一段進む&lt;br&gt;7. be perplexed - 被迷惑；被困惑 / 当惑する&lt;br&gt;8. correspond to - 符合;相符 / 対応する&lt;br&gt;9. in honor of - 向……致敬 / の名において&lt;br&gt;10. finalize once - 最后一次/ 終了する&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;反義片語：&lt;br&gt;1. complex problem - 繁複問題 / 複雑な問題&lt;br&gt;2. take less effort - 需求諸多省卻之事 / より少ない努力を要する&lt;br&gt;3. stray from the path - 離開道路 / 道にはぐれる&lt;br&gt;4. moved from - 從……移動 / 移動する&lt;br&gt;5. remove from - 徹底移除 / 取り除く&lt;br&gt;6. go backward - 追溯 / 後戻っている&lt;br&gt;7. obvious - 顯而易見 / もちろん&lt;br&gt;8. mismatch to - 不吻合；相互間不配合 / 不一致&lt;br&gt;9. in memory of - 為紀念……/ ……に捧げる&lt;br&gt;10. initialization - 初期设定 / 初期化</content><link href="https://www.gamespot.com/articles/diablo-4-secret-of-the-spring-side-quest-and-emote-guide/1100-6514781/" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>