<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><id>https://github.com/weg38asyy/GameRss.git</id><title>My Game Rss</title><updated>2023-04-08T13:10:40.951549+00:00</updated><author><name>Koala</name><email>weg38asyy@gmail.com</email></author><link href="https://github.com/weg38asyy" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Personal learning of English use</subtitle><entry><id>https://www.gamespot.com/articles/prime-gaming-april-2023-free-games/1100-6512818/</id><title>Amazon Prime Members Can Claim 3 Free Games, Including Wolfenstein: The New Order</title><updated>2023-04-08T13:10:40.951791+00:00</updated><content type="html">Prime Gaming's free games lineup for April 2023 features a whopping 15 games, and the first three freebies are available now, including Wolfenstein: The New Order. All of this month's free games can be claimed by anyone with an active Amazon Prime membership. As always, the free games are joined by loot drops for popular multiplayer titles like Valorant, Overwatch 2, and Hearthstone. &lt;br&gt; Just like the past few months, the free games unlock weekly throughout the month, rather than the old strategy of dropping all of them on the first of the month. The first trio of games that are live now can be seen below, followed by the schedule for the rest of the month. &lt;br&gt;   &lt;br&gt; Wolfenstein: The New Order is arguably the most notable free game of the bunch. Once claimed, you'll receive a DRM-free key that can be redeemed on GOG. Originally released in 2014, Wolfenstein: The New Order rebooted the iconic series in style. To this day, it still has some of the best writing and storytelling within its genre. &lt;br&gt; A couple of classic games may pique your nostalgia senses later this month. Icewind Dale: Enhanced Edition is an isometric role-playing game set in the Dungeons &amp; Dragons universe. Meanwhile, SNK's Metal Slug 4 will appeal to those who like action-packed run-and-gun games. Metal Slug 4 first launched on the Neo Geo MVS arcade system before being ported to a bunch of different consoles and PC. &lt;br&gt; Near the end of the month, metroidvania fans should absolutely check out Grime. This side-scrolling action-adventure takes cues from Dark Souls with its challenging, methodical. combat system. Its large interconnected world, unique weapons system, gorgeous 2.5D visuals, and wide variety of baddies make Grime one of the best Souls-like metroidvanias around. &lt;br&gt; In addition to the free games that subscribers can keep forever, April has also brought a refreshed Prime Gaming Channel lineup. Subscribers can stream four games via Amazon's Luna cloud streaming service throughout the month: Yakuza Kiwami 2, The Jackbox Games Party Pack 3, Horizon Chase Turbo, and The Adventure Pals. &lt;br&gt; Additionally, as a new perk, Amazon has partnered with Partie, a video game matchmaking service. A free Partie Plus membership will be offered to Prime members, offering voice and video chat and other exclusive features. Additional Partie perks will be rolled out for Prime subscribers throughout the year. &lt;br&gt; The free in-game loot rounds out the offerings. You can claim in-game content for online multiplayer games, including PUBG, Overwatch 2, League of Legends, Valorant, Hearthstone, World of Warcraft (with an expensive mount), and more. &lt;br&gt; If you aren't an Amazon Prime member, new subscribers can get a free 30-day trial, which you can then use to claim and keep the freebies. &lt;br&gt; Best Gaming &amp; Tech Deals This Week &lt;br&gt;  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;詳細句子文法解析：&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. "the first three freebies are available now" - 本句中的現在式「are available」表示現在正在發生的事情，用來強調現在可用的免費遊戲，讓讀者感受到現在性的強烈。&lt;br&gt;2. "All of this month's free games can be claimed by anyone with an active Amazon Prime membership" - 本句是一個複合句，連接詞為「by」，表示透過什麼手段。句子的主詞是「All of this month's free games」，謂語是「can be claimed」，被動結構讓這個行為更顯客觀性，句子最後是一個定語從句，修飾主詞。&lt;br&gt;3. "The first trio of games that are live now can be seen below" - 本句中用了關代詞「that」來引出定語從句，修飾「the first trio of games」，假設關代詞使用不當或者遺漏，句意就無法明確。&lt;br&gt;4. "Wolfenstein: The New Order is arguably the most notable free game of the bunch" - 本句中的「arguably」表示「有人認為」、「或許」的意思，用於論點或觀點成立有爭議，要讓讀者了解「最有價值的免費遊戲」是一個可以被帶來爭議討論的觀點。&lt;br&gt;5. "Icewind Dale: Enhanced Edition is an isometric role-playing game set in the Dungeons &amp; Dragons universe" - 本句中的連接詞「is」緊接下來的單字「an」，連起來形成「是...的」這種語法結構，用來描述Icewind Dale是一款角色扮演遊戲。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;單字：&lt;br&gt;1. lineup - 陣容、陣容表&lt;br&gt;2. freebie - 免費贈品&lt;br&gt;3. subscription - 訂閱、購買規格&lt;br&gt;4. duo - 二人組合、二重唱&lt;br&gt;5. loot - 收獲、掠奪&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;日文單字：&lt;br&gt;1. freebie - 無料の贈り物（むりょうのおくりもの）&lt;br&gt;2. loot - 戦利品（せんりひん）&lt;br&gt;3. subscription - 購読（こうどく)&lt;br&gt;4. bundle - 関連商品セット（かんれんしょうひんせっと）&lt;br&gt;5. duo - 二人(ふたり)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;片語：&lt;br&gt;1. live now - 現在直播中；dead now - 現在已終止&lt;br&gt;2. Nostalgia senses - 思鄉病，感傷情懷&lt;br&gt;3. Methodical combat system - 有條理的戰鬥系統；chaotic combat system - 混亂的戰鬥系統&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;相似片語：&lt;br&gt;1. live up to - 相當於、達到（期望）&lt;br&gt;2. check out - 查看、看一看&lt;br&gt;3. be joined by - 與某人聯手&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;反義片語：&lt;br&gt;1. live down -美名败坏&lt;br&gt;2. check in -  簽注登记&lt;br&gt;3. leave (sb.) out - 把 (某人) 排除在外</content><link href="https://www.gamespot.com/articles/prime-gaming-april-2023-free-games/1100-6512818/" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>