<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><id>https://github.com/weg38asyy/GameRss.git</id><title>My Game Rss</title><updated>2023-03-27T18:09:48.558926+00:00</updated><author><name>Koala</name><email>weg38asyy@gmail.com</email></author><link href="https://github.com/weg38asyy" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Personal learning of English use</subtitle><entry><id>https://www.gamespot.com/articles/former-forza-horizon-studio-head-starts-new-studio-lighthouse-games/1100-6512726/</id><title>Former Forza Horizon Studio Head Starts New Studio Lighthouse Games</title><updated>2023-03-27T18:09:48.559103+00:00</updated><content type="html">Former founder and studio head of Forza Horizon developer Playground Games, Gavin Raeburn, has started a new AAA studio called Lighthouse Games. The studio is based in Leamington Spa and currently working on an unannounced IP. Lighthouse Games is composed of other former Playground Games veterans such as director Nick Wheelwright and creative director Jon Davis-Hunt. “I’m delighted that 30 former colleagues and other industry heavyweights have chosen to join me at Lighthouse. With Horizon, Playground and I created one of the most successful Xbox franchises of all time," Raeburn explained in a statement. He continued: "We delivered significant commercial success year after year, to massive critical acclaim following the success from my time at Codemasters leading Dirt, Grid, and F1. That DNA is now at Lighthouse, and with it, we intend to build something truly special using all our experience to create a new genre-defining franchise.” As the team is currently working on its first game, it is also looking to hire for open positions including lead-level designer and senior online engineer. There have been many new studios being formed lately by veterans from big studios including former Need for Speed developers at Fuse Games and former Apex Legends developers at Wildlight Entertainment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;詳細句子文法解析：&lt;br&gt;1. "...has started a new AAA studio called Lighthouse Games." &lt;br&gt;    - 運用了完整的現在完成式 (Present Perfect) 來描述Gavin Raeburn最近成立了一間遊戲公司Lighthouse Games，在目前這個時間點仍持續進行中，同時代表動作的完成性與現在時間的連結。&lt;br&gt;2. "The studio is based in Leamington Spa and currently working on an unannounced IP."&lt;br&gt;    - 運用了現在進行式 (Present Continous) 表示不斷進行並且還在持續進行中，同時用現在分詞 (working) 進一步描述了正在進行的活動-正在開發一個未公佈的新遊戲。&lt;br&gt;3. "I’m delighted that 30 former colleagues and other industry heavyweights have chosen to join me at Lighthouse."&lt;br&gt;    - 運用了過去完成式 (Past Perfectt) 來描述在過去某個時間（Founder and studio head of Forza Horizon developer 之前）的動作已經完成 - 已經有30位前同事和業界精英選擇跟著 Gavin Raeburn加入 Lighthouse Games。&lt;br&gt;4. "We delivered significant commercial success year after year, to massive critical acclaim following the success from my time at Codemasters leading Dirt, Grid, and F1."&lt;br&gt;   - 運用了-ing字尾 (gerunds) 來形成名詞片語directing Dirt, Grid, and F1進而形容my time at Codemasters, 這個公司的成功也因此引起了極大的歡呼 － 用了雙重的形容詞搭配&lt;br&gt;5. "That DNA is now at Lighthouse, and with it, we intend to build something truly special using all our experience to create a new genre-defining franchise."&lt;br&gt;    - 運用了倒三角式的排列法，將前文的名詞DNA一般化，修飾整個Lighthouse company，強調表示Lighthouse Games 具有Codemasters和Playground的基因，定義了認知和技能等等特點。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;單字：&lt;br&gt;1. unannounced (adj.) - 未公佈的，未經宣告的&lt;br&gt;2. franchise (n.) - 特许经营权，连锁企业，授权生产&lt;br&gt;3. veteran (n.) - 老手，老兵，退役军人&lt;br&gt;4. acclaimed (adj.) - 受到高度赞扬的&lt;br&gt;5. intend (v.) - 打算，计划&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;片語：&lt;br&gt;1. of all time - 有史以来，史上最，使用来强调世界上历史 ‘之前’，无人能够超越或胜任 &lt;br&gt;例如： This is the best book of all time. (這是有史以來最好的書)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;其它：&lt;br&gt;1. 英文文法解析：&lt;br&gt;   現在完成式 (Present Perfect) - 表示動作是在過去某個時間開始的，但它與當前時間有聯結。當有 "for" 或 "since"相結合時, 還含一段時間的範圍&lt;br&gt;   例句：I have been to New York twice. (我已經去過紐約兩次。)&lt;br&gt;   &lt;br&gt;2. 英文單字釋義：&lt;br&gt;- unannounced: 'un'表"非"，"announced" 則是分詞，其实是 "announce" 的动词-ed的形式，所以顧名思義，「未公佈的」is a good way to remember the word.&lt;br&gt;- franchise: “一系列拥有连锁特许经营权的商物，著作权等等”，要注意在法律保护範疇。&lt;br&gt;- veteran: 老練而具经验的，曾經的经历久為人知，變得瞭如指掌的，通常和积累相联想到。&lt;br&gt;- acclaimed："ac-"原意是強調語氣，"（to）claim" 是宣稱或斷言，被珍視及肯定看法或欣賞&lt;br&gt;- intend：意圖，意欲，在決定或階段而言时常出现&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. 英文單字日文說明：&lt;br&gt;- unannounced:  未公表の、発表されなかった&lt;br&gt;- franchise: フランチャイズ&lt;br&gt;- veteran: ベテラン、退役軍人、老練な人&lt;br&gt;- acclaimed: 高評価された、絶賛された&lt;br&gt;- intend: 意図する、企図する、思う</content><link href="https://www.gamespot.com/articles/former-forza-horizon-studio-head-starts-new-studio-lighthouse-games/1100-6512726/" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>