<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><id>https://github.com/weg38asyy/GameRss.git</id><title>My Game Rss</title><updated>2023-05-19T13:12:53.259108+00:00</updated><author><name>Koala</name><email>weg38asyy@gmail.com</email></author><link href="https://github.com/weg38asyy" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Personal learning of English use</subtitle><entry><id>https://www.gamespot.com/articles/zelda-tears-of-the-kingdom-marari-in-shrine-guide/1100-6514310/</id><title>Zelda: Tears Of The Kingdom - Eventide Island Marari-In Shrine Guide</title><updated>2023-05-19T13:12:53.259314+00:00</updated><content type="html">The Legend of Zelda: Tears of the Kingdom Marari-In Shrine is fairly well-hidden. That's because it's tucked away in a corner of the map that you probably won't visit unless you go off the beaten path. Here's our guide to help you find the Eventide Island Marari-In Shrine in Zelda: Tears of the Kingdom. &lt;br&gt; The Legend of Zelda: Tears of the Kingdom Marari-In Shrine can be found on Eventide Island, which is all the way at the southeastern tip of the world map. Basically, if you've been to Lurelin Village to help repair its buildings, there's a good chance that you've seen another landmass in the distance (i.e. past the "dagger" of the cove). You can go ahead and create a seafaring vehicle, such as a bunch of logs attached together, along with a Zonai Fan and a Steering Stick, to make your way there. &lt;br&gt;   &lt;br&gt; Upon arrival, you'll notice that Bokoblins and other monsters populate this area. Eliminate them as you see fit, then make your way to the northern portion of the main island. &lt;br&gt; There, you'll meet an NPC named Sesami. He'll inform you that there's a pirate ship patrolling the place, and that the vessel disappeared behind a cove. &lt;br&gt;   &lt;br&gt; Head to the coast near the opposite/smaller island this time. You should see the entrance to the Pirate Hideout behind the cove. There, you can take out more enemies as you proceed. &lt;br&gt; As for the Zelda: Tears of the Kingdom Marari-In Shrine, you'll spot it just opposite the prow of the ship. The problem is that there are spikes sticking out of the ledge. Thankfully, the ship itself has several wooden planks. Go ahead and attach these to form a makeshift bridge. &lt;br&gt;   &lt;br&gt; Upon crossing, tag and enter the Shrine. It's a Rauru's Blessing, and you'll get a Ruby from the chest. In any case, this is but one of many activities that you can do in the game. Don't forget to take a look at our Shrine locations main guide for all the other challenges that you can tackle. Likewise, since you're within the vicinity, you might as well obtain Midna's Helmet while you're here. &lt;br&gt; There are numerous mechanics and facets to learn in The Legend of Zelda: Tears of the Kingdom. For more information, you can visit our guides hub.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;詳細句子文法解析：&lt;br&gt;1. "The Legend of Zelda: Tears of the Kingdom Marari-In Shrine is fairly well-hidden."--這是一個主語+動詞+形容詞的句子結構，形容詞fairly用來描述well-hidden的程度。&lt;br&gt;2. "That's because it's tucked away in a corner of the map that you probably won't visit unless you go off the beaten path."--這是一個因果關係的句子，因為藏匿在地圖的一個角落裡，所以可能需要走冒險路線才會找到。&lt;br&gt;3. "Here's our guide to help you find the Eventide Island Marari-In Shrine in Zelda: Tears of the Kingdom."--這是一個提示/介紹的句子，我們要用我們的指南來幫助你找到位於Eventide Island的Marari-In Shrine。&lt;br&gt;4. "The Legend of Zelda: Tears of the Kingdom Marari-In Shrine can be found on Eventide Island" --這是一個陳述句，用來描述在Eventide Island可以找到Marari-In Shrine。&lt;br&gt;5. "Basically, if you've been to Lurelin Village to help repair its buildings, there's a good chance that you've seen another landmass in the distance (i.e. past the "dagger" of the cove)."--這是一個條件句，基本上只要你曾經去過Lurelin Village 幫助修繕建築，很有可能你已經在遠處看到了另外一個陸塊（過了海灣的“匕首”的那邊）。 &lt;br&gt;6. "You can go ahead and create a seafaring vehicle, such as a bunch of logs attached together, along with a Zonai Fan and a Steering Stick, to make your way there."--這是一個命令句，給了指示來建造一個海船或類似的交通工具，&lt;br&gt;7. " Eliminate them as you see fit, then make your way to the northern portion of the main island." --這是一個段落的開始句子，告訴你解決掉敵人之後，要往北部走。&lt;br&gt;8. "There, you'll meet an NPC named Sesami." --這是一個描述位置與角色的句子，指向的地方是該遊戲中的某處位置，你將遇到一個名為Sesami的NPC。&lt;br&gt;9. "Head to the coast near the opposite/smaller island this time."--這是一個指示句，指向接下來需要前往的一個相對較小的海島。&lt;br&gt;10. "In any case, this is but one of many activities that you can do in the game"--這是一個轉折句，用來表示本屆仍有很多其他的活動可以進行。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;單字:&lt;br&gt;1. well-hidden (adj.) [拆解後詞彙聯想：well(好) + hidden(藏匿)，表示非常深藏不露的意思]&lt;br&gt;    日文單字：うまく隠された（umaku kakusareta）&lt;br&gt;2. tucked away (phrasal verb) [拆解後詞彙聯想：tuck(塞入) + away(遠離)，表示放在離人遠的地方，不容易被找到]&lt;br&gt;    日文單字: 隠す（kakusu）&lt;br&gt;3. off the beaten path (phrasal verb) [拆解後詞彙聯想: 由於確立的道路通常都是密集的，因此另開創路線需要越過已經會走的路程，而不製定的道路不必走密集的路程。正在創建一個不需要人走的新道路，它更適合在給定的情況下使用]&lt;br&gt;    日文單字：定められた道路から外れた場所 (sadamerareta michi kara hazureta basho)&lt;br&gt;4. landmass (n.) [拆解後詞彙聯想：land(陸地) + mass(大量)，表示大量的陸地]&lt;br&gt;    日文單字：大陸（tairiku）&lt;br&gt;5. seafaring (adj.) [拆解後詞彙聯想：sea(海) + faring(行經)，表示航行海洋的，有關航海的]&lt;br&gt;    日文單字：航海（kouka）&lt;br&gt;6. eliminate (v.) [拆解後詞彙聯想：eliminate(排除)，表示決定性的除去]&lt;br&gt;    日文單字：省かれる (habinukareru)&lt;br&gt;7. NPC (abbr.) [拆解後詞彙聯想：NPC(Non Playable Character)，表示遊戲中的“非玩家角色”]&lt;br&gt;    日文單字: NPC(エヌピーシー) &lt;br&gt;8. cove (n.) [拆解後詞彙聯想：cove(海灣)，表示一個小型海灣]&lt;br&gt;    日文單字：海辺の小湾のような場所(namihata no kowan no youna basho)&lt;br&gt;9. makeshift (adj.) [拆解後詞彙聯想：make(做) + shift(改變)，表示描繪暫時性的東西]&lt;br&gt;    日文單字：代用の(deyouno)&lt;br&gt;10. vicinity (n.) [拆解後詞彙聯想：vicinity(附近) ，表示非常接近]&lt;br&gt;    日文單字：近傍（kinbou）&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;片語:&lt;br&gt;相似片語： &lt;br&gt;1. off the beaten track (離人所履之地) --意義與off the beaten path相同，表示一條不被人們通常所走的路徑。&lt;br&gt;2. hidden from view (視線屏障中) --類似well-hidden這個單字的意義，表示某物/某地很難被看到。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;反義片語：&lt;br&gt;1. in plain sight (一目瞭然) --和2. hidden from view相反，意思是指某物/場所是顯而易見，容易被發現的。&lt;br&gt;2. well-known (眾所皆知) --和well-hidden相反，表示一個普遍已經人人皆知的事實。</content><link href="https://www.gamespot.com/articles/zelda-tears-of-the-kingdom-marari-in-shrine-guide/1100-6514310/" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>