<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><id>https://github.com/weg38asyy/GameRss.git</id><title>My Game Rss</title><updated>2023-06-19T13:11:45.469066+00:00</updated><author><name>Koala</name><email>weg38asyy@gmail.com</email></author><link href="https://github.com/weg38asyy" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Personal learning of English use</subtitle><entry><id>https://www.gamespot.com/articles/save-big-on-aliens-dark-descent-ahead-of-next-weeks-launch/1100-6513712/</id><title>Save Big On Aliens: Dark Descent Ahead Of Next Week's Launch</title><updated>2023-06-19T13:11:45.469343+00:00</updated><content type="html">Aliens: Dark Descent launches next Tuesday, June 20, and if you're looking for a deal on preorders--Fanatical and Green Man Gaming are offering 18% off the game's PC edition (Steam key). You can  preorder a Steam key for Aliens: Dark Descent  for $32.79 ($40). &lt;br&gt;   &lt;br&gt; Aliens: Dark Descent features an original story set in the Aliens franchise, with the player leading soldiers against Xenomorphs. The game is a real-time tactical action game, and players can customize the abilities, weapons, and other qualities of their soldiers. &lt;br&gt; You can also forge paths by choosing shortcuts and establishing safe zones in order to defend against the dangerous Xenomorphs. &lt;br&gt; The game's official marketing material promises plenty of iconic Aliens monsters like Facehuggers and Alien Queens, as well as brand new enemies called rogue human commandos. &lt;br&gt; Aliens: Dark Descent isn't the only PC game that's available to preorder at a discount from Fanatical. You can also grab Armored Core 6 for more than 10% off. Meanwhile, if you're looking for some bargains you can play now, check out  Fanatical's various bundle deals  and the Humble Choice lineup for June, which you can get for only $8 with our promo code GAMESPOT8. &lt;br&gt; Disclaimer: GameSpot and Fanatical are both owned by Fandom. &lt;br&gt; Best Gaming &amp; Tech Deals This Week&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;詳細句子文法解析：&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. "Aliens: Dark Descent launches next Tuesday, June 20, and if you're looking for a deal on preorders--Fanatical and Green Man Gaming are offering 18% off the game's PC edition (Steam key). You can preorder a Steam key for Aliens: Dark Descent for $32.79 ($40)."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;這是一個複合句，前半部分是主句，後半部分是條件狀語從句。使用if引導條件狀語從句，表示如果符合某一條件，就會得到某種好處。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. "Aliens: Dark Descent features an original story set in the Aliens franchise, with the player leading soldiers against Xenomorphs."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;這是一個複合句，由兩個並列的獨立子句組成。使用with來引導一個描述子句，表示進一步補充前面的主句信息。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. "The game is a real-time tactical action game, and players can customize the abilities, weapons, and other qualities of their soldiers."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;這是一個複合句，由兩個並列的獨立子句組成。使用and來把兩個獨立子句連接起來，表示一種并列的關系。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. "You can also forge paths by choosing shortcuts and establishing safe zones in order to defend against the dangerous Xenomorphs."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;這是一個簡單句。使用also來表示添加和前面路徑沒有任何關系，單獨出現在句子中表示進一步的補充說明。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. "The game's official marketing material promises plenty of iconic Aliens monsters like Facehuggers and Alien Queens, as well as brand new enemies called rogue human commandos."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;這是一個複合句，由兩個並列的獨立子句組成。使用as well as來把兩個獨立子句連接起來，表示添加的進一步說明信息。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;6. "Aliens: Dark Descent isn't the only PC game that's available to preorder at a discount from Fanatical. You can also grab Armored Core 6 for more than 10% off."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;這是一個複合句，由兩個並列的獨立子句組成。使用that's引導一個從句，說明主句限制的條件。使用also來添加進一步說明信息。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;7. "Meanwhile, if you're looking for some bargains you can play now, check out Fanatical's various bundle deals and the Humble Choice lineup for June, which you can get for only $8 with our promo code GAMESPOT8."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;這是一個複合句。使用if引導一個條件狀語從句，使用which引導一個非限定性定語從句，對前面deals的進一步描述。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;8. "Disclaimer: GameSpot and Fanatical are both owned by Fandom."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;這是一個簡單句。使用冒號表示對前一句話進一步的疏析和說明。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;9. "Best Gaming &amp; Tech Deals This Week"&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;這是一個簡單句，表示主題。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;單字：&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. launch 發射；開始(v.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. preorder 預購(v.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. franchise 特權經營權；專賣權(n.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. tactical 戰術的；有計畫的(adj.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. customize 定制(v.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;6. ability 能力(n.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;7. weapon 武器(n.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;8. establish 建立(v.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;9. defend 防禦(v.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;10. iconic 標誌性的；代表性的(adj.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;單字記法：&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. launch - 音讀「蘭丘」，詞彙聯想：貨運發射台在蘭丘上。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. preorder - 詞性變化費解？不如記住是「先行預訂」就對了。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. franchise - 音讀「法蘭西斯」，跟巴黎那個「法國地帶」有關係...（？）&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. tactical - 音讀「塔克妙可」，貼上粉紫色防水標籤，像做運動需要有計劃一樣需要有戰略。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. customize - 音讀「客製化」，定制屬於你自己的遊戲！&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;6. ability - 音讀「阿比利」，拆成額二層詞彙變成「阿三比利：你能力3」。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;7. weapon - 音讀「雨萬」，形象上像九尾狐的九柄寶劍之一，吐出光芒。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;8. establish - 音讀「伊思泰比」，拆成額三層詞彙變成「伊-思-泰比結婚了！」。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;9. defend - 音讀「地-逢」，看拼音TSU和動作像機器人企圖防禦。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;10. iconic - 音讀「眼底胖了」，像雅緻或定風波的那個胖眼。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;相似片語：     &lt;br&gt;1. Dark Descent- 相似片語：Blackout, Deadly Drive, Cold Chaos, Cryptic Caverns。&lt;br&gt;2. Real-time - 相似片語：Live-action，Direct-to-video，Unscripted Reality TV Show。&lt;br&gt;3. Customize abilities - 相似片語：Tailor instructions、Cater to demand、Adjust training methods。&lt;br&gt;4. Establish safe zones - 相似片語：build a safety net.&lt;br&gt;5. Brand new - 相似片語：Freshly minted, New and Improved。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;反義片語：&lt;br&gt;1. Definitely not - 就是相反，死不瞑目，根本不管用。&lt;br&gt;2. Not a bit - 一些也不，一點也不，同樣是強調否定。&lt;br&gt;3. No way - 絕對不可能，決不可能，感嘆反對。&lt;br&gt;4. Unhelpful - 無用的；無益的，反向描述有用的事物。&lt;br&gt;5. Doesn't compare - 無法比擬，相比之下，竟然說得遜一些。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;日語單字：&lt;br&gt;1. launch - 打ちあげる&lt;br&gt;2. preorder - プレオーダーする&lt;br&gt;3. franchise - フランチャイズ&lt;br&gt;4. tactical - 戦術的な&lt;br&gt;5. customize - カスタマイズする&lt;br&gt;6. ability - 能力&lt;br&gt;7. weapon - 武器&lt;br&gt;8. establish - 設立する&lt;br&gt;9. defend - 防御する&lt;br&gt;10. iconic - 象徴的な&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;相似片語：&lt;br&gt;1. Dark Descent - ダーク降下、ダーク響&lt;br&gt;2. Real-time - リアルタイム、リアルタイム制作&lt;br&gt;3. Customize abilities - 能力をカスタマイズする、能力を編集する&lt;br&gt;4. Establish safe zones - 安全ゾーンを設立する、安全地帯を定める&lt;br&gt;5. Brand new - ブラン・ニュー、新たな、全く新しい&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;反義片語：&lt;br&gt;1. Definitely not - 絶対違う、まったく違う、違うことに決まっている&lt;br&gt;2. Not a bit - 少しも、全く、微塵も&lt;br&gt;3. No way - 無理、不可能、まさか&lt;br&gt;4. Unhelpful - 役に立たない、無力な、無益な&lt;br&gt;5. Doesn't compare - 比べられない、かけ離れている、比べるにもならない</content><link href="https://www.gamespot.com/articles/save-big-on-aliens-dark-descent-ahead-of-next-weeks-launch/1100-6513712/" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>