<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><id>https://github.com/weg38asyy/GameRss.git</id><title>My Game Rss</title><updated>2023-06-17T13:10:59.298472+00:00</updated><author><name>Koala</name><email>weg38asyy@gmail.com</email></author><link href="https://github.com/weg38asyy" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Personal learning of English use</subtitle><entry><id>https://www.gamespot.com/articles/preorder-pikmin-4-for-49-ahead-of-next-months-launch/1100-6513258/</id><title>Preorder Pikmin 4 For $49 Ahead Of Next Month's Launch</title><updated>2023-06-17T13:10:59.298811+00:00</updated><content type="html">We're just a month away from the release of the long-awaited Pikmin 4. The Nintendo Switch-exclusive sequel launches on July 21. Preorders cost $60 at major retailers, including at Walmart where you can get a free stainless steel water bottle with your order. But if you don't mind waiting a couple days after launch to start playing, you can preorder Pikmin 4 for just $49 at Super Shop. Pikmin 4 preorders are already discounted to $55 on Super Shop, but using the GameSpot exclusive promo code GMSPTPIK at checkout drops the price down to $49. &lt;br&gt; Saving $11 on your Pikmin 4 preorder at Super Shop is a great deal, but there is one caveat: unlike preorders from some other retailers, you won't receive your order on release day (July 21). Luckily, Super Shop offers fast and free shipping, and all orders will be shipped on launch day--so you won't have to wait very long to start playing. &lt;br&gt; If you know you won't be able to wait an extra day or two, our Pikmin 4 preorder guide details all the ways you can buy your copy of the game before launch. Of course, you’ll have to pay full price, but that extra cash may be worth it to some. &lt;br&gt; While you're at Super Shop preordering Pikmin 4, you can  pick up The Legend of Zelda: Tears of the Kingdom for $60  with GameSpot's promo code GMSPTZLDA. Similarly, digital buyers can save $30 if they buy both Pikmin 4 and Zelda using Nintendo eShop vouchers. &lt;br&gt; Best Gaming &amp; Tech Deals This Week&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;詳細句子文法解析：&lt;br&gt;1. We're just a month away from the release of the long-awaited Pikmin 4. ["be (just) A + 時間 away from + N/Ving"句型]，用來表示離某事情發生或開始還有多少時間&lt;br&gt;2. The Nintendo Switch-exclusive sequel launches on July 21. [形容詞+名詞+連接詞+形容詞+名詞"句型，用來修飾並定義名詞."]&lt;br&gt;3. Preorders cost $60 at major retailers, including at Walmart where you can get a free stainless steel water bottle with your order. [代名詞+可以+動詞被略去的"句型，常用在廣告或促銷文案中，此結構用來表達某行動是允許或建議的]&lt;br&gt;4. But if you don't mind waiting a couple days after launch to start playing, you can preorder Pikmin 4 for just $49 at Super Shop. ["if"條件句型]&lt;br&gt;5. Pikmin 4 preorders are already discounted to $55 on Super Shop, but using the GameSpot exclusive promo code GMSPTPIK at checkout drops the price down to $49. [使用"-ing" 形式來表達動作的主體，即Pikmin 4，類似於被動語態]&lt;br&gt;6. Saving $11 on your Pikmin 4 preorder at Super Shop is a great deal, but there is one caveat: unlike preorders from some other retailers, you won't receive your order on release day (July 21). [分號的用法，來表示前後句之間有些關聯，常用於長句中分割成相互獨立的部分]&lt;br&gt;7. Luckily, Super Shop offers fast and free shipping, and all orders will be shipped on launch day--so you won't have to wait very long to start playing. [用兩個連字符號來為某種事物予以歸類，描述說明更加清晰]&lt;br&gt;8. If you know you won't be able to wait an extra day or two, our Pikmin 4 preorder guide details all the ways you can buy your copy of the game before launch. [用"-ing" 形式來表達"guides" 作為"our" 的中心]&lt;br&gt;9. Of course, you’ll have to pay full price, but that extra cash may be worth it to some. ["of course" 常用於認為某件事情是顯然的時候]&lt;br&gt;10. While you're at Super Shop preordering Pikmin 4, you can pick up The Legend of Zelda: Tears of the Kingdom for $60 with GameSpot's promo code GMSPTZLDA. [表示同時進行兩種或多種行動時，常使用"while + 动名词" 结构.]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;單字：&lt;br&gt;1. preorders（預購）- 預購 &gt; 日:予約（よやく）&lt;br&gt;2. retailers（零售商）- 銷售店 &gt; 日:小売店（こうりてん）&lt;br&gt;3. exclusive（高級）- 獨賣、獨佔 &gt; 日:独占的（どくせんてき）&lt;br&gt;4. launch（推出）- 發射、發行 &gt; 日:発売（はつばい）&lt;br&gt;5. preorder（預購）- 預購 &gt; 日:予約（よやく）&lt;br&gt;6. stainless steel（不鏽鋼）- 不鏽鋼 &gt; 日:ステンレス鋼（すてんれすこう）&lt;br&gt;7. promo code（促銷代碼）- 促銷代碼 &gt; 日:プロモーションコード（ぷろもーしょんこーど）&lt;br&gt;8. discount（折扣）- 打折 &gt; 日:割引（わりびき）&lt;br&gt;9. fast（快）- 快 &gt; 日:早い（はやい）&lt;br&gt;10. worth（價值）- 值得 &gt; 日:価値あり（かちあり）&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;片語：&lt;br&gt;1. Similar phrase: Just a stone's throw away （一箭之遥）&lt;br&gt;2. Antonym phrase: Far away from （遠離）</content><link href="https://www.gamespot.com/articles/preorder-pikmin-4-for-49-ahead-of-next-months-launch/1100-6513258/" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>