<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><id>https://github.com/weg38asyy/GameRss.git</id><title>My Game Rss</title><updated>2023-03-26T19:42:29.909083+00:00</updated><author><name>Koala</name><email>weg38asyy@gmail.com</email></author><link href="https://github.com/weg38asyy" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Personal learning of English use</subtitle><entry><id>https://www.gamespot.com/articles/resident-evil-4-unlockable-costumes-weapons-guide/1100-6512582/</id><title>Resident Evil 4 - Unlockable Costumes And Bonus Weapons Guide</title><updated>2023-03-26T19:42:29.909326+00:00</updated><content type="html">Resident Evil 4 Remake has numerous goodies that you can unlock. However, several will require multiple completions, as well as a bit of know-how for more efficient clears. Here's our Resident Evil 4 unlockables guide to help you with all the weapons and costumes that you can obtain in the game. Our Resident Evil 4 unlockables guide takes a look at the different items that can be yours once you finish the game. All of these can be acquired via the main menu -&gt; Bonus Content -&gt; Extra Content Shop, where each selection costs Completion Points (i.e., what you earn when you complete challenges/achievements in the campaign). You may then equip these by clicking Main Story -&gt; Extras. Additionally, some rewards are further subdivided based on game modes and clear rankings (usually dependent on completion time). As such, you can't get everything in one go. Here's the gist: For instance, if you're attempting an S+ rank run, then you'll need to be very familiar with the game already. Knowing when to avoid enemies, and being able to clear the campaign as fast as possible would be the end goal. Moreover, since New Game+ isn't allowed, you'll have to start a fresh run without weapon upgrades or items that you've collected. However, some bonus weapons can be picked up from the storage, and they can be upgraded as you progress. Note that these weapons are earned through achieving certain in-game milestones. For the complete list of weapons you can purchase or otherwise find in Resident Evil 4 Remake, check out our guide to all Resident Evil 4 weapons. Most of these Resident Evil 4 Remake unlockable costumes and accessories simply require a regular campaign completion (i.e., any difficulty mode/no time limit). However, for others that might require something like "Hardcore mode or higher," you can pick Professional mode to grab those rewards, too. Leon Ashley Leon Ashley Resident Evil 4 has more mechanics and secrets for you to discover. You can learn more in our guides hub.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;句子文法解析：&lt;br&gt;1. "Resident Evil 4 Remake has numerous goodies that you can unlock." &lt;br&gt;此句為複合句，主要由兩個部分所構成。前半部份為"Resident Evil 4 Remake has numerous goodies"的陳述句，後半部份則為"that you can unlock"的修飾子句，用來昭示前半部份所提到的獎勵都可以被解鎖。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. "Our Resident Evil 4 unlockables guide takes a look at the different items that can be yours once you finish the game."&lt;br&gt;此句為複合句，主要由兩個部分所構成，前半部份為"Our Resident Evil 4 unlockables guide takes a look at the different items"的陳述句，後半部份則為"that can be yours once you finish the game."的修飾子句，用來說明前半部份所提到的不同獎勵在完成遊戲後都可以成為你的物品。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. "All of these can be acquired via the main menu -&gt; Bonus Content -&gt; Extra Content Shop, where each selection costs Completion Points (i.e., what you earn when you complete challenges/achievements in the campaign)."&lt;br&gt;此句為複合句，主要由兩個部分所構成，前半部份為"All of these can be acquired via the main menu -&gt; Bonus Content -&gt; Extra Content Shop"的陳述句，後半部份為"where each selection costs Completion Points (i.e., what you earn when you complete challenges/achievements in the campaign)."的修飾子句，用來告知前半部份所提到的獎勵都可以在Bonus Content -&gt; Extra Content Shop中購買，而其中每個選項都需使用完成點數（做出挑戰或完成成就可獲得）才可購買到。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;單字：&lt;br&gt;1. unlockables - 可解鎖的奬勵/道具&lt;br&gt;相似片語：achievements (成就)&lt;br&gt;2. clear - 通過/完成某個關卡&lt;br&gt;相似片語：finish, complete&lt;br&gt;3. subdivided - 分成多個子類別/細分&lt;br&gt;相似片語：categorized, classified, segmented&lt;br&gt;4. modes - 模式/遊戲模式&lt;br&gt;相似片語：settings, options&lt;br&gt;5. milestones - 里程碑/關鍵進度&lt;br&gt;相似片語：achievements (成就), benchmarks&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;片語：&lt;br&gt;1. 在完成遊戲後 - once you finish the game&lt;br&gt;相似片語：after completing the game, when you finish the game&lt;br&gt;反義片語：before finishing the game&lt;br&gt;2. 獲得某些獎勵 - obtain certain rewards&lt;br&gt;相似片語：acquire specific prizes&lt;br&gt;反義片語：lose out on rewards&lt;br&gt;3. 完成挑戰/達成成就 - complete challenges/achievements&lt;br&gt;相似片語：accomplish tasks/goals, finish missions/rewards&lt;br&gt;反義片語：fail challenges/achievements&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;其它：&lt;br&gt;1. unlockable這個單字可以透過聯想的方式來記，例如將單字解拆成un-lock-able，un為負面前綴詞，可理解成"不會打開"，lock是鎖的意思，able則代表有能力做的意思，因此這個詞可以想像成"自己無法打開的鎖"，即需要完成一些任務/達成成就才能打開的特殊獎勵。&lt;br&gt;2. 挑戰/成就可以透過轉換的方式來記，例如"challenge"可以聯想到中文"挑戰"四個字，意思是人們為了超越自己而去嘗試做一些困難的事情；"achievement"可以轉換成中文"成就"，代表經過努力做出一些讓人刮目相看的成績。</content><link href="https://www.gamespot.com/articles/resident-evil-4-unlockable-costumes-weapons-guide/1100-6512582/" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>