<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><id>https://github.com/weg38asyy/GameRss.git</id><title>My Game Rss</title><updated>2023-04-21T13:12:10.255223+00:00</updated><author><name>Koala</name><email>weg38asyy@gmail.com</email></author><link href="https://github.com/weg38asyy" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Personal learning of English use</subtitle><entry><id>https://www.gamespot.com/articles/street-fighter-6-dlc-season-1-announced-akuma-returns-a-k-i-debuts/1100-6513457/</id><title>Street Fighter 6 DLC Season 1 Announced: Akuma Returns, A.K.I. Debuts</title><updated>2023-04-21T13:12:10.255432+00:00</updated><content type="html">The Street Fighter 6 Showcase unveiled the first set of downloadable fighters for Street Fighter 6, and it will include three returning fighters and one brand-new entrant. &lt;br&gt; First up is Rashid, who debuted as part of Street Fighter V's launch roster and will hit SF6 in Summer 2023. His unique moveset--one that harnesses tornadoes and other wind-based powers--quickly made him not only a fan favorite, but also a potent competitive character throughout SFV's lifespan. &lt;br&gt; The second DLC character in Season 1 is A.K.I, a mysterious woman with pale white skin who will launch in Fall 2023. Her moveset makes use of both her skills in Chinese martial arts but also massive claws she dons on each hand. &lt;br&gt; The Psycho Power-imbued Ed, who made his playable debut as a DLC character in Street Fighter V, will release Winter 2024. Ed was trained by Balrog to be a boxer, though his style is much more about speed than his mentor's raw power. &lt;br&gt; Akuma will be last, coming in Spring 2024, and he will need no introduction to longtime Street Fighter fans. The Satsui-no-Hado-corrupted Shotokan will bring his offense-heavy moveset to SF6, which will include his trademark move, Raging Demon. &lt;br&gt; Street Fighter 6 will fully launch June 2 for Xbox Series X|S, PlayStation 4, PlayStation 5, and PC. A demo has released for PlayStation 4 and 5, and it will hit Xbox and PC on April 26.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;句子文法解析：&lt;br&gt;1. "The Street Fighter 6 Showcase unveiled the first set of downloadable fighters for Street Fighter 6, and it will include three returning fighters and one brand-new entrant." &lt;br&gt;（這句顯示Street Fighter 6 Showcase進行了一次發佈，並介紹了鬥士們的下載，包括三位返回的鬥士和一位全新的鬥士。）&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;解析：這是一個複合句，前半部分是主句，後半部分是從屬子句。主句描述了Street Fighter 6 Showcase的活動內容，從屬子句給出了更具體的信息。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. " First up is Rashid, who debuted as part of Street Fighter V's launch roster and will hit SF6 in Summer 2023."&lt;br&gt;（首先是現在推出的鬥士Rashid, 他首次出現在Street Fighter V的啟動名單中，並將於2023年夏季登陸SF6。）&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;解析：這是一個複合句，主句描述了現在即將推出的新鬥士Rashid，從屬子句給出了Rashid過去的紀錄和未來的安排。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. "Her moveset makes use of both her skills in Chinese martial arts but also massive claws she dons on each hand."&lt;br&gt;（她的招式結合了她在中國武術上的技能，還使用了她在雙手上戴著的巨大爪子。）&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;解析：這是一個簡單句，介紹了女鬥士A.K.I的特點。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. "The Psycho Power-imbued Ed, who made his playable debut as a DLC character in Street Fighter V, will release Winter 2024."&lt;br&gt;（注入Psycho Power的Ed，在Street Fighter V中首次以DLC角色的形式亮相，將於2024年冬季發布。）&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;解析：這是一個複合句，主句介紹了注入了Psycho Power的鬥士Ed的情況，從屬子句描述該角色先前在Street Fighter V中的表現。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. "Akuma will be last, coming in Spring 2024, and he will need no introduction to longtime Street Fighter fans."&lt;br&gt;（Akuma將成為最後一個，於2024年春季推出，長時間的Street Fighter球迷不需要介紹。）&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;解析：這是一個複合句，主句提到了最後一名鬥士是Akuma，從屬子句解釋了他在Street Fighter粉絲中的知名度。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;6. "Street Fighter 6 will fully launch June 2 for Xbox Series X|S, PlayStation 4, PlayStation 5, and PC." &lt;br&gt;（Street Fighter 6 將完整地在 6 月 2 日推出 Xbox Series X|S、PlayStation 4、PlayStation 5 和 PC。）&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;解析：這是一個簡單句，說明了Street Fighter 6的全平台上市時間。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;7. "A demo has released for PlayStation 4 and 5, and it will hit Xbox and PC on April 26."&lt;br&gt;（PlayStation 4和 5 已經發布了演示版，並將於4月26日推出 Xbox 和 PC 版本。）&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;解析：這是一個複合句，主句說明了PlayStation上已經發佈了演示版，從屬子句指出演示版將在4月26日推出Xbox和PC版本。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;8. "His unique moveset--one that harnesses tornadoes and other wind-based powers--quickly made him not only a fan favorite, but also a potent competitive character throughout SFV's lifespan."&lt;br&gt;（他獨特的招式組合 - 利用龍捲風和其他風力技能 - 迅速使他成為粉絲的最愛，同時在整個SFV的發展過程中也是一名強大的競爭鬥士。）&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;解析：這是一個簡單句，介紹了Rashid作為一個表現出色的鬥士，具有獨特的招式和強大的競爭力。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;9. "Her moveset makes use of both her skills in Chinese martial arts but also massive claws she dons on eac手。 爪子","Talon"]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;單字：debut [デビュー], martial arts [武道], demo [デモ], release [リリース], unique [ユニーク], competitive [実力のある], favorite [お気に入り], potent [有力な], harnesses [利用する], tornadoes [竜巻], claws [きぞく]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;拆解後詞彙聯想:&lt;br&gt;- debut: "de"代表"開始"，"but"代表"但是"，因此debut可以聯想為什麼很多明星在出道後開始面臨各種困難，但是仍然堅持在演藝界發展。&lt;br&gt;- martial arts: "martial"代表"軍事"，"arts"代表"藝術"，因此martial arts可以聯想到某種使用技能作為藝術表現的軍事風格。&lt;br&gt;- demo: demo是"演示版本"的縮寫，可以聯想到點擊體驗、短暫體驗等。&lt;br&gt;- release: "re"代表"再一次"、"lease"代表"租用"，因此release可以聯想到再一次租用或免費使用。&lt;br&gt;- unique: "uni"代表"獨一無二"，"que"是後綴表示"屬於某種品質"，因此unique表示獨具特色或獨一無二的。&lt;br&gt;- competitive: 由"compete"這個動詞轉來的形容詞，代表擁有一定競爭力或能力。&lt;br&gt;- favorite: "fav"是後綴，也就是"favor"的縮寫，表示"慣常的、喜愛的"，因此favorite可以聯想到自己特別喜歡的人或物。&lt;br&gt;- potent: "potent"和power和strength有相似的意思，常常表示某種能力或力量非常強大。&lt;br&gt;- harnesses: "harness"是指馬胸圈或虎尾莢，可以控制動物的運動，轉化他們的幹勁，因此"harnesses"還可以表示有效利用某物的潛能。&lt;br&gt;- tornadoes: "tornado"字面意思是龍捲風，在遊戲中也可以理解為一種比較強大的招式所代表的能力。&lt;br&gt;- claws: "claw"表示爪子，在遊戲中也可以理解為某個角色戰鬥時使用的武器。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;相似片語：harness one's potential [發揮某人的潛力]，massive claws [巨大的爪子]；&lt;br&gt;反義片語：weak moveset [弱招式組合]，losing character [輸球的鬥士]</content><link href="https://www.gamespot.com/articles/street-fighter-6-dlc-season-1-announced-akuma-returns-a-k-i-debuts/1100-6513457/" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>