<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><id>https://github.com/weg38asyy/GameRss.git</id><title>My Game Rss</title><updated>2023-04-06T13:11:21.274245+00:00</updated><author><name>Koala</name><email>weg38asyy@gmail.com</email></author><link href="https://github.com/weg38asyy" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Personal learning of English use</subtitle><entry><id>https://www.gamespot.com/articles/disney-dreamlight-valley-foraging-guide-all-crafting-items-and-flower-locations/1100-6507149/</id><title>Disney Dreamlight Valley Foraging Guide: All Crafting Items And Flower Locations</title><updated>2023-04-06T13:11:21.274494+00:00</updated><content type="html">Foraging in Disney Dreamlight Valley can be done throughout every biome in the game. Each biome has specific foragable items to discover, which means you won't immediately be able to find every all of them until you've unlocked every location with Dreamlight. Over time, you'll discover new items such as clay, crystal, and sand as you open up all of the biomes. Not to be confused with the game’s ingredients, these items will need to be picked up in-game in order to craft many outdoor objects, such as stone pathways and fences, as well as complete some character quests. Here's a full list of every foragable item in the game. &lt;br&gt; Foraging for most of these items does not expend energy and is a great way to quickly gather materials while attending to other activities. You can either sell the flowers for Star Coins or give them as gifts to increase friendship levels for your companions. &lt;br&gt; You need a javascript enabled browser to watch videos. &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;        Want us to remember this setting for all your devices?&lt;br&gt;       &lt;br&gt; Sign up or Sign in now!&lt;br&gt;       &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;        By clicking 'enter', you agree to GameSpot's&lt;br&gt;                        Terms of Use and&lt;br&gt;        Privacy Policy &lt;br&gt; enter &lt;br&gt; Now Playing: 20 Tips For Beginners In Disney Dreamlight Valley &lt;br&gt; Some of these items such as clay are rarer to forage, for example. Moana will need your help gathering three Pink Hydrangeas for the Fixing the Boat quest, so some of these items will need to be chased down early and often. The map itself does not display foragable items, so you will need to wander through each biome to pick up any certain items. &lt;br&gt; For more on Disney Dreamlight Valley, check out our 20 tips for beginners, learn the ratatouille recipe here, and learn how to use cross-saves so you can take your town across platforms. &lt;br&gt;  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;詳細句子文法解析：&lt;br&gt;1. Foraging in Disney Dreamlight Valley can be done throughout every biome in the game. （介系詞片語）&lt;br&gt;使用介系詞in來表達動作發生的地點，foraging與biome皆為名詞，若要表達活動的動作，需要使用-ing形式。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Each biome has specific foragable items to discover, which means you won't immediately be able to find every all of them until you've unlocked every location with Dreamlight. （關代詞）&lt;br&gt;使用which來引導從屬子句表示「這也代表著在你解鎖所有地點前，你不會立刻找到它們。」。這個關代詞連接了前文與後文，使文章更加連貫。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. Not to be confused with the game’s ingredients, these items will need to be picked up in-game in order to craft many outdoor objects, such as stone pathways and fences, as well as complete some character quests. （分詞片語）&lt;br&gt;以participle形式的Not to be confused作為主語，表示這些物品不應該與遊戲配方搞混。使用分詞片語能夠很好地表達附屬關係，避免使用過多連接詞和子句。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. You can either sell the flowers for Star Coins or give them as gifts to increase friendship levels for your companions. （或、並列連接詞）&lt;br&gt;使用or表示「或」的關係，讓讀者知道有兩種選項可以採取：出售或送禮物。「或」也是一種重要的並列連接詞，能夠讓句子的結構更加簡潔清晰。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. Some of these items such as clay are rarer to forage, for example. （副詞片語）&lt;br&gt;使用副詞such as來列舉「clay」作為一個例子，強調有些物品很難采集。副詞片語能夠清晰地銜接句子，有助於讓讀者更好地理解文章的內容。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;6. The map itself does not display foragable items, so you will need to wander through each biome to pick up any certain items. （復合句）&lt;br&gt;這是一個含有主句和從屬子句的復合句。使用所謂的從句表示「地圖本身不顯示可以獲取的物品，所以你需要進入每個生物群落以查找特定物品」。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;7. Moana will need your help gathering three Pink Hydrangeas for the Fixing the Boat quest, so some of these items will need to be chased down early and often. （情態動詞）&lt;br&gt;使用情態動詞「will」來表達Moana需要你幫助奪取Pink Hydrangeas，表示發生的積極事物。句中表達了需要盡早尋找這些物品的需求。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;8. For more on Disney Dreamlight Valley, check out our 20 tips for beginners, learn the ratatouille recipe here, and learn how to use cross-saves so you can take your town across platforms. （三個並列動詞）&lt;br&gt;文章以三個並列動詞「check out」、「learn」和。「learn」為中心，教讀者學習基本的道具探索技巧，食譜以及跨平臺使用的技巧。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;單字:&lt;br&gt;Foraging：搜尋食材&lt;br&gt;biome： 生物群落&lt;br&gt;discovery：發現&lt;br&gt;Unlock：解鎖&lt;br&gt;ingredients：材料&lt;br&gt;craft：製作&lt;br&gt;outdoor：戶外&lt;br&gt;paths：步道&lt;br&gt;fences：柵欄&lt;br&gt;items：物品&lt;br&gt;energy：能量&lt;br&gt;flowers：花朵&lt;br&gt;Star Coins：星星硬幣&lt;br&gt;Gifts：禮物&lt;br&gt;Companions：同伴&lt;br&gt;rare：罕見&lt;br&gt;certain：某些&lt;br&gt;map：地圖&lt;br&gt;display：顯示&lt;br&gt;wander：漫步&lt;br&gt;gather：收集&lt;br&gt;quest：任務&lt;br&gt;chase down：追踪&lt;br&gt;often：經常發生&lt;br&gt;cross-saves：儲存&lt;br&gt;platforms：平台&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;日文單字：&lt;br&gt;Foraging：採集（サジー）&lt;br&gt;biome：生息地（せいそくち）&lt;br&gt;discovery：発見（はっけん）&lt;br&gt;Unlock：解除（かいじょ）&lt;br&gt;ingredients：材料（ざいりょう）&lt;br&gt;craft：作成（さくせい）&lt;br&gt;outdoor：屋外（おくがい）&lt;br&gt;paths：小道（こみち）&lt;br&gt;fences：柵（さく）&lt;br&gt;items：アイテム&lt;br&gt;energy：エネルギー&lt;br&gt;flowers：花（はな）&lt;br&gt;Star Coins：スターコイン&lt;br&gt;Gifts：贈り物（おくりもの）&lt;br&gt;Companions：仲間（なかま）&lt;br&gt;rare：希少な（きしょうな）&lt;br&gt;certain：特定の（とくていの）&lt;br&gt;map：地図（ちず）&lt;br&gt;display：表示（ひょうじ）&lt;br&gt;wander：歩き回る（あるきまわる）&lt;br&gt;gather：収集（しゅうしゅう）&lt;br&gt;quest：クエスト&lt;br&gt;chase down：追跡（ついせき）&lt;br&gt;often：よく&lt;br&gt;cross-saves：クロスセーブ&lt;br&gt;platforms：プラットフォーム&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;片語：&lt;br&gt;1. Foraging in Disney Dreamlight Valley （在迪士尼仙境谷搜尋）&lt;br&gt;相似片語：Harvesting in the fields（在田野中收穫）&lt;br&gt;反義片語：Ignoring the flora (忽略植物）&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. not to be confused with（不要混淆）&lt;br&gt;相似片語：Distinguished from（不同）&lt;br&gt;反義片語：Mix up(混淆）&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. pick up  （撿起）&lt;br&gt;相似片語：collect gathering(收集，聚集)&lt;br&gt;反義片語：put down（拿下）&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. chase down （追踪）&lt;br&gt;相似片語：Track（追蹤）&lt;br&gt;反義片語：give up on （放棄尋找）&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;其它：&lt;br&gt;1. 從中文出發，單字提供台式腔調咒語記念法，例如：Foraging - 己辣金（ji lay kim）&lt;br&gt;2. 告訴學生單字的詞根、字首、字尾，例如craft - 取自字根create (創造)，意指製作或創作。&lt;br&gt;3. 片語如撿起、回友情等，請告訴學生實際上英文經常使用片語，並且多練習使用，避免靈活運用。</content><link href="https://www.gamespot.com/articles/disney-dreamlight-valley-foraging-guide-all-crafting-items-and-flower-locations/1100-6507149/" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>