<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><id>https://github.com/weg38asyy/GameRss.git</id><title>My Game Rss</title><updated>2023-05-24T16:52:11.413655+00:00</updated><author><name>Koala</name><email>weg38asyy@gmail.com</email></author><link href="https://github.com/weg38asyy" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Personal learning of English use</subtitle><entry><id>https://www.gamespot.com/articles/destiny-2-season-of-the-deep-seasonal-challenges-guide/1100-6514465/</id><title>Destiny 2: Season Of The Deep Seasonal Challenges Guide - Week 1</title><updated>2023-05-24T16:52:11.413781+00:00</updated><content type="html">The first week of Destiny 2's Season of the Deep has commenced, and like previous seasons, there are new Seasonal Challenges to tackle. These are optional but rewarding challenges that you can tackle which will earn you Bright Dust that can be spent on cosmetics and experience points that can help you level up the season pass more quickly. &lt;br&gt; One of the other changes this season is focused on how seasonal bonuses are earned. Previous seasons would give you a chance to earn a rare resource each week which could then be redeemed at a vendor for a specific seasonal bonus, but Season 21 is changing up that approach. Instead, you'll have a selection of Season of the Deep-specific challenges that you can complete. Once you've completed one of these challenges, you'll automatically unlock a perk for your Guardian. &lt;br&gt; These perks are familiar to the ones that were available in previous seasons, as you'll be able to earn high-stat armor pieces, extra Deep engrams, and increased vendor reputation. You won't be able to accomplish all of them in one go, but you will be able to work through them at your leisure during Season of the Deep. &lt;br&gt; In terms of the standard Week 1 challenges, the focus is on getting to grips with the new Salvage seasonal activity and completing the first chapter in the Into the Depths storyline. A few rounds in Salvage will help you complete the Front Line Salvager and Successful Salvager objectives quickly, and for extra experience points, don't forget to stock up on bounties from the command table in the HELM. &lt;br&gt; Once you're done with those activities, you can knock out more tasks in the EDZ. Head to that location, cycle through public events and lost sectors, equip close-range weapons, and you'll be able to quickly finish up the EDZ Activities, The Fallen Fall, and Close-Range Calibration objectives. You'll also need to catch some fish, so be sure to check out our Destiny 2 fishing guide. &lt;br&gt; Lastly, you can head to the Crucible to take part in the time-limited Rift multiplayer mode. This will only be available until next week's reset, so finish this quickly and move on to Gambit next. Make good use of a weapon in your primary slot--specifically auto rifles, hand cannons, and scout rifles--and take on as many enemies as you can. &lt;br&gt; For more on Destiny 2, you can check out the very long patch notes that came with the start of this new season. &lt;br&gt; Complete the Week 1 Into the Depths mission. &lt;br&gt; Complete Salvage or Deep Dive activities while using an Arc or Strand subclass. Additionally, defeat Fallen anywhere in the System. &lt;br&gt; Successfully complete jobs in Salvage activities. &lt;br&gt; Catch fish at any fish pond. Additionally, complete public events on any destination. &lt;br&gt; In the EDZ, earn progress by completing bounties, patrols, lost sectors, and public events. &lt;br&gt; Complete weekly playlist challenges. &lt;br&gt; Score points in Rift. Bonus progress is awarded for igniting the Rift. &lt;br&gt; Defeat targets in Gambit with primary ammo. Bonus progress is granted for using auto rifles, hand cannons, and scout rifles. Bonus progress is also granted for defeating Guardians. &lt;br&gt; Defeat Fallen combatants in Vanguard playlists or strikes. Earn bonus progress for defeating tougher combatants. &lt;br&gt; Calibrate close-range weapons--sidearms, submachine guns, shotguns, glaives, and swords. Bonus progress for defeating Guardians. &lt;br&gt; Complete Week 1 of Into the Depths. &lt;br&gt; Seasonal bonus: Completing a Season of the Deep weekly activity challenge grants a chance to earn an additional Deep engram. &lt;br&gt; Obtain a full set of Season of the Deep armor. &lt;br&gt; Seasonal bonus: Deep engrams can be focused into individual pieces of high-stat Season of the Deep armor. &lt;br&gt; Obtrain any six Season of the Deep or reprised Reckoning weapons. &lt;br&gt; Seasonal bonus: Deep engrams can be focused into individual Season of the Deep or Reckoning weapons. The weapon must be acquired previously in order to focus it. &lt;br&gt; Reach Rank 7 with the Sonar Station in the HELM. &lt;br&gt; Seasonal bonus: You and your fireteam gain bonus reputation when opening chests in Salvage or Deep Dive activities. The reputation granted increases for each fireteam member with this seasonal bonus active. &lt;br&gt; Reach Rank 13 with the Sonar Station in the HELM. &lt;br&gt; Seasonal bonus: Completing activities grants a chance to earn an additional Deep engram. &lt;br&gt; Catch fish while a fish pond is at maximum catch bonus. &lt;br&gt; Seasonal bonus: When fishing with bait, you have a chance to have your bait returned after catching a fish. &lt;br&gt; As a fireteam, complete three jobs within a single Salvage activity. &lt;br&gt; Seasonal bonus: When you redeem a key in Salvage or Deep Dive activities, you have a chance to earn an additional Deep engram. &lt;br&gt; Defeat each unique boss in Salvage activities. &lt;br&gt; Seasonal bonus: Your first craftable weapon individually focused at the Sonar Station in the HELM each week is guaranteed to have Deepsight Resonance. &lt;br&gt; Defeat each unique boss in Deep Dive activities. &lt;br&gt; Seasonal bonus: When you redeem a Salvage key, you have a chance to earn a Deep Dive key. &lt;br&gt; Successfully complete an encounter at the Abyss depth in a Deep Dive activity. &lt;br&gt; Seasonal Bonus: An ammo crate containing Special and Heavy ammo is hidden at each depth in Deep Dive activities. Opening the crate also grants additional objective time.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;句子文法解析：&lt;br&gt;1. "The first week of Destiny 2's Season of the Deep has commenced," - 過去式（Has commenced）表示過程已經開始且尚未結束，強調開始的狀態持續到現在。 &lt;br&gt;2. "there are new Seasonal Challenges to tackle." - "to tackle" 表示"解決" "面對"的意思，此處接名詞，表示要解決這個新的Seasonal Challenges。 &lt;br&gt;3. "which will earn you Bright Dust" - "which" 指的是前一個句子的"Seasonal Challenges"，這裡使用關係代名詞引出前一個句子的內容。 &lt;br&gt;4. "that can be spent on cosmetics" - "that" 指的是Bright Dust，使用關係代名詞引出作用。 &lt;br&gt;5. "that can help you level up the season pass more quickly" - "that" 同上，使用關係代名詞引出作用。 &lt;br&gt;6. "One of the other changes this season is focused on how seasonal bonuses are earned." - "is focused on" 表示"專注於"，強調今年這一季的改變。 &lt;br&gt;7. "Previous seasons would give you a chance to earn a rare resource each week" - "would" 表示以前的慣常作法，過去式表明這個常態已經不存在了。 &lt;br&gt;8. "Once you've completed one of these challenges, you'll automatically unlock a perk for your Guardian." - "once" 表示一旦，表示一個過程完成後就會有一個結果完成。 &lt;br&gt;9. "bonus progress is granted for using auto rifles, hand cannons, and scout rifles" - "progress is granted" 表示獲得獎勵進展，重點在於說明獲取進度的方式。 &lt;br&gt;10. "Seasonal bonus: When fishing with bait, you have a chance to have your bait returned after catching a fish." - "When" 引導副詞子句並表達條件；"have a chance to" 表達機率，表示捕魚的時候有機會回收你的魚餌。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;單字與記憶方法：&lt;br&gt;1. Commenced - 開始, 聯想「公司」在這個位置開始創辦。&lt;br&gt;2. Tackle - 解決, 聯想「拖拉機」將問題一一解決。&lt;br&gt;3. Rewarding - 值得的, 聯想「報答」，這個挑戰完全可以報答你。&lt;br&gt;4. Cosmetics - 化妝品, 聯想「cosplay妝容」，深怕你用完後和cosplay一樣美麗。&lt;br&gt;5. Perk - 好處, 聯想「pick 方便的」，這個挑戰完成後你可以輕鬆獲得好處。(日文：特典 tokuten)&lt;br&gt;6. Reputation - 声望, 聯想「reputation reputaion」，有聲望的人名字總是在名聲四溢地傳唱。&lt;br&gt;7. Salvage - 應變, 聯想「Salvatore」，在任何狀況下他都可以應付自如。&lt;br&gt;8. Encounter - 遭遇, 聯想「in counter 面對」，表示他居然順利地面對了。&lt;br&gt;9. Calibration - 校正, 聯想「Call Barry」，需要向後傾倒並且快速地叫「Barry」來跟他的調速器做標準校正。(日文：校正 kousei)&lt;br&gt;10. Reprised - 再次演出, 聯想「Replayed」，一個好的表演不演不休。(日文：再演 saien) &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;相似片語: &lt;br&gt;1. Complete one of these challenges &lt;br&gt;    -- Finish one of these challenges.&lt;br&gt;2. Once you've completed one of these challenges, you'll automatically unlock a perk for your Guardian.&lt;br&gt;    -- After you completed one of these perks, you'll unlock a perk for your Guardian.&lt;br&gt;3. Focus on --- To center or concentrate attention on.&lt;br&gt;    -- The new season is concentrated on how seasonal bonuses are earned.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;反義片語: &lt;br&gt;1. Optional but rewarding challenges &lt;br&gt;    -- Mandatory and unrewarding challenges. &lt;br&gt;2. Completing a Season of the Deep weekly activity challenge grants a chance to earn an additional Deep engram.&lt;br&gt;    -- Failing a Season of the Deep weekly activity challenge denies the chance to earn an additional Deep engram.</content><link href="https://www.gamespot.com/articles/destiny-2-season-of-the-deep-seasonal-challenges-guide/1100-6514465/" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>