<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><id>https://github.com/weg38asyy/GameRss.git</id><title>My Game Rss</title><updated>2023-04-05T13:10:50.623282+00:00</updated><author><name>Koala</name><email>weg38asyy@gmail.com</email></author><link href="https://github.com/weg38asyy" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Personal learning of English use</subtitle><entry><id>https://www.gamespot.com/articles/shigeru-miyamoto-dodges-whens-the-next-mario-game-question-in-style/1100-6512969/</id><title>Shigeru Miyamoto Dodges "When's The Next Mario Game?" Question In Style</title><updated>2023-04-05T13:10:50.623621+00:00</updated><content type="html">Shigeru Miyamoto inevitably gets asked when the next Mario game is during promotions for The Mario Super Bros. Movie, and he always has coy answers ready. &lt;br&gt; During a Variety interview, after the interviewer asks when we can expect the next Mario game, Miyamoto replies, "Please stay tuned for future Nintendo Directs." &lt;br&gt; You need a javascript enabled browser to watch videos. &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;        Want us to remember this setting for all your devices?&lt;br&gt;       &lt;br&gt; Sign up or Sign in now!&lt;br&gt;       &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;        By clicking 'enter', you agree to GameSpot's&lt;br&gt;                        Terms of Use and&lt;br&gt;        Privacy Policy &lt;br&gt; enter &lt;br&gt; Now Playing: The Super Mario Bros. Movie Official Teaser Trailer &lt;br&gt; Does that mean a Nintendo Direct in the near future, or a Nintendo Direct next year? Or perhaps the year after? No one knows. It's a perfect deflection. Miyamoto was asked a similar question during an IGN interview, and he replied, "Nintendo is always working on Mario." &lt;br&gt; Mario is Nintendo's biggest IPs, so players probably don't have to worry about the next Mario game not coming--it's only a matter of when, something Miyamoto doesn't have an answer to for players yet. &lt;br&gt; The Super Mario Bros. Movie comes out in theaters on April 5, and ahead of the release, reviews are trickling in. You can check out our sister site Metacritic for a comprehensive overview. &lt;br&gt; In GameSpot's own The Super Mario Bros. movie review, critic Phil Owen gave the movie an 8/10. "Folks have been having all sorts of emotional turmoil about this new Super Mario Bros. Movie since the moment it was announced that Guardians of the Galaxy and Lego Movie star Chris Pratt would provide the voice of Mario," Owen said. "All that gnashing of teeth was for nothing, though. The Super Mario Bros. Movie is both pretty funny and also just plain pretty--this movie is a feast for the eyes."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;詳細句子文法解析：&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. "he always has coy answers ready." - 這個句子使用現在簡單式，強調Miyamoto經常會有這樣的回答準備好。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. "Please stay tuned for future Nintendo Directs." - 這個句子使用祈使句，表示Miyamoto在呼籲玩家們持續關注Nintendo Direct資訊。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. "Does that mean a Nintendo Direct in the near future, or a Nintendo Direct next year? Or perhaps the year after?" - 這個句子使用疑問句，表示問題的可能性和不確定性。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. "No one knows." - 這個句子使用現在簡單式，表示目前還沒有人知道答案。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. "Mario is Nintendo's biggest IPs, so players probably don't have to worry about the next Mario game not coming--it's only a matter of when," - 這個複合句使用so...that...句型，表示Mario是任天堂最重要的IP之一，所以玩家不必擔心下一款Mario遊戲會不會推出，只是問題在於何時推出。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;6. "Miyamoto was asked a similar question during an IGN interview, and he replied, "Nintendo is always working on Mario."" - 這個句子使用過去式，表示Miyamoto在過去的IGN採訪中被問到類似的問題，並回答Nintendo一直在進行Mario相關的開發工作。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;7. "Folks have been having all sorts of emotional turmoil about this new Super Mario Bros. Movie since the moment it was announced" - 這個句子使用現在完成式，強調從公佈這部新的超級瑪利歐兄弟電影以來，人們一直在產生各種情緒困擾。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;8. "The Super Mario Bros. Movie is both pretty funny and also just plain pretty--this movie is a feast for the eyes." - 這個複合句使用and...also...句型，表示這部超級瑪利歐兄弟電影既有趣又很好看，是一場視覺盛宴。 &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;單字：&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. inevitable - 無可避免的。中文聯想：in-表示"不"，evitable表示"可避免"，所以inevitable就是無法避免的意思。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. coy - 謙虛的，含糊其詞的。中文聯想：coy和cow（奶牛）的發音類似，所以我們可以聯想到謙虛的態度，像是奶牛一樣溫和。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. comprehensive - 全面的。中文聯想：com-表示"完全"，pre-表示"預"，hensive表示"包括"，這個單字就是指涵蓋完全的意思。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. turmoil - 混亂，動盪。中文聯想：tur-和tornado（龍捲風）的發音類似，我們可以聯想到旋轉、混亂的風暴。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;日文單字：&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. Mario - マリオ (Ma-ri-o)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Miyamoto - 宮本茂 (Miyamoto Shigeru)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. Nintendo - 任天堂 (Nintendou)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. IP - 知的財産 (Chiteki Zaisan)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;片語：&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. stay tuned - 保持關注。相似片語為keep an eye on，反義片語為tune out。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. in the near future - 在不久的將來。相似片語為soon，反義片語為long term。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. in theaters - 上映。相似片語為on stage，反義片語為off screen。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;其它：&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;片語中的an eye也可以表示"a watchful attitude or alertness", 所以keep an eye on/ watch your steps同樣也可以翻譯成"步步為營" 。</content><link href="https://www.gamespot.com/articles/shigeru-miyamoto-dodges-whens-the-next-mario-game-question-in-style/1100-6512969/" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>