<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><id>https://github.com/weg38asyy/GameRss.git</id><title>My Game Rss</title><updated>2023-04-01T13:11:15.219082+00:00</updated><author><name>Koala</name><email>weg38asyy@gmail.com</email></author><link href="https://github.com/weg38asyy" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Personal learning of English use</subtitle><entry><id>https://www.gamespot.com/articles/god-of-wars-christopher-judge-calls-for-end-to-console-war-give-each-other-a-break/1100-6512891/</id><title>God Of War's Christopher Judge Calls For End To Console War: "Give Each Other A Break"</title><updated>2023-04-01T13:11:15.219590+00:00</updated><content type="html">God of War actor Christopher Judge, who plays Kratos, has called for the gaming community to be nice to one another, no matter what platform they play on. Appearing at the BAFTA Game Awards on Thursday night, where he won the award for Performer in a Leading Role for Kratos in God of War Ragnarok, Judge used his speech to call for gaming fans to come together. &lt;br&gt; "Thank you to the fans," he said, as reported by VGC. "Be easier on each other. You all have more in common than what separates you," Judge said. "No matter what platform you love, no matter what game you love, you're still part of the gaming community, and give each other a break." &lt;br&gt; The God of War development team faced abuse and negative comments from people in the gaming community before Ragnarok released in November 2022. Things got so bad that developer Santa Monica Studio put out a statement calling on fans to communicate their opinions with respect. Fans' enthusiasm for the god of War series "should not be toxic nor come at the expense of any human being's dignity." &lt;br&gt; Santa Monica Studio added, "Let's celebrate our community by treating each other, every gamer and developer alike, with respect." &lt;br&gt; Judge portrayed Kratos in 2018's God of War and 2022's God of War Ragnarok. The Norse God of War series is now over, and it remains to be seen if Judge may return for any future God of War games. &lt;br&gt; The actor personally lobbied to play Kratos in the God of War TV series at Amazon Studios. Officially casting announcements for the show have not been made yet, however. &lt;br&gt; This is Judge's second major award for playing Kratos in Ragnarok, following his Best Performance win at December's Game Awards. At that show, Oscar-winner Al Pacino handed Judge his award, and the two shared a very nice embrace.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;詳細句子文法解析： &lt;br&gt;1. "Appearing at the BAFTA Game Awards on Thursday night, where he won the award for Performer in a Leading Role for Kratos in God of War Ragnarok, Judge used his speech to call for gaming fans to come together." &lt;br&gt;此為一個复合句，舉行神殿電玩獎的場地被置於關係子句中，"For Kratos in God of War Ragnarok"為定語從句；Judga使用語氣為過去式的過去式形式，並在主句中介紹了他使用言論呼籲電玩愛好者團結的行為。&lt;br&gt;2. "The God of War development team faced abuse and negative comments from people in the gaming community before Ragnarok released in November 2022."  &lt;br&gt;此為一個复合句，God of War development team為主語，faced abuse and negative comments from people in the gaming community為謂語部分，精確地描述了团队被批評的情況。 &lt;br&gt;3. "Things got so bad that developer Santa Monica Studio put out a statement calling on fans to communicate their opinions with respect."  &lt;br&gt;此為一個复合句，Santa Monica Studio為定語從句中的主語部分，put out a statement則在主句中作後置句，calling on fans to communicate their opinions with respect為其賓語從句。&lt;br&gt;4. "Fans' enthusiasm for the God of War series "should not be toxic nor come at the expense of any human being's dignity." &lt;br&gt;此為一個复合句，Fans' enthusiasm為主語，should not be為情態動詞，而toxic nor come at the expense of any human being's dignity為實質性賓語從句。&lt;br&gt;5. "Let's celebrate our community by treating each other, every gamer and developer alike, with respect." &lt;br&gt;此為一個简单句，Let's celebrate為動詞；它告訴我們可以透过尊重平等的對待玩家和開發者来庆祝我们的社群。 &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;單字：&lt;br&gt;1. toxic - 有毒的，甚至可能莫名的危險和不快。&lt;br&gt;2. dignity - 尊嚴，表示驕傲和堅定不移，並且對自己保持著高水平的自我價值感。&lt;br&gt;3. enthusiasm - 熱情，指對某件事被激活的積極情感。&lt;br&gt;4. Performer - 演員，用于描述一個人的歌唱、舞蹈、音樂等的表現。&lt;br&gt;5. deliver - 傳送，表達，施加，再加上其他含義。 &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;片語：&lt;br&gt;1. come together - 意味著不同的社群组织在一起，尤其是因为共同的目的。&lt;br&gt;- 相似片語：unite&lt;br&gt;- 反義片語：break up, disconnect&lt;br&gt;2. with respect - 指對某人或某事表示尊重。 &lt;br&gt;- 相似片語：in a polite manner &lt;br&gt;- 反義片語：disrespectfully &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;其它：&lt;br&gt;1. toxic有毒的，令人聯想到毒藥，可以在腦中建立圖像並在商務課堂中存儲在大腦中。 &lt;br&gt;- 日文單字：有毒の、どく(ドク)&lt;br&gt;2. dignity與dia fan有關，dia fan代表藝人追求自己身份的高傲，在日常人之上，因此可以聯想到對自己保持高水平的自我價值感。&lt;br&gt;- 日文單字：尊厳、尊重、自尊心、尊大&lt;br&gt;3. enthusiasm中的"en"可能已被加強，使得熱情變得更加激烈。&lt;br&gt;- 日文單字：熱情を感じること、熱狂、熱心、情熱。&lt;br&gt;4. Performer與"form"，"insert-er"有關，表達了某人將自己的技能和才能融入整個作品的能力。&lt;br&gt;- 日文單字：劇団員、パフォーマー、演者、執行者&lt;br&gt;5. deliver指向某個地方傳遞消息，與“deliver”形象相匹配的圖像可以是交付某物，所以可以在記憶過程中形成圖像聯想。&lt;br&gt;- 日文單字：デリバーする、提供する、手渡す、伝達。</content><link href="https://www.gamespot.com/articles/god-of-wars-christopher-judge-calls-for-end-to-console-war-give-each-other-a-break/1100-6512891/" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>