<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><id>https://github.com/weg38asyy/GameRss.git</id><title>My Game Rss</title><updated>2023-03-29T13:11:11.192024+00:00</updated><author><name>Koala</name><email>weg38asyy@gmail.com</email></author><link href="https://github.com/weg38asyy" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Personal learning of English use</subtitle><entry><id>https://www.gamespot.com/articles/resident-evil-4-rocket-launcher-guide/1100-6512560/</id><title>Resident Evil 4 Rocket Launcher Guide: Location And How To Unlock</title><updated>2023-03-29T13:11:11.192295+00:00</updated><content type="html">The Rocket Launcher is one of the most iconic weapons not just in Resident Evil 4, but the entirety of the survival horror franchise. This armament has a single shot, so make it count. Here's our guide to help you get the Rocket Launcher in Resident Evil 4. Likewise, you can learn more from our weapons hub. &lt;br&gt; The Rocket Launcher in Resident Evil 4 can be found after you've cleared the Lake area. Basically, you'll need to take out the Del Lago boss, then make your way past the Mural Cave Puzzle. Eventually, you should find a boat, one that you can sail back to the docks where the Merchant resides. By the time you get there, your old vendor pal should have the Rocket Launcher as one of his wares, and it costs a whopping 80,000 pesetas. &lt;br&gt; This amount might seem daunting at first, though the weapon doesn't really have further upgrades (it won't need any). Generally speaking, there's no reason for you to pick up the Resident Evil 4 Rocket Launcher so early in the game. Still, if you do want to grab it, that's entirely up to you. &lt;br&gt; Likewise, if you want to lower this amount slightly, you'll have to acquire the Leon with Rocket Launcher Charm from the Shooting Gallery. This lowers the purchase cost by 20%. However, it's the fourth in order among the 3x Gold Token combination rewards. &lt;br&gt; As mentioned earlier, the weapon only has a single projectile, one that causes a massive explosion that will likely kill every regular enemy in a radius. It can even deal tremendous damage to bosses, ending an encounter if need be, though there are some caveats. For instance, during the Verdugo boss fight, if you merely shoot it instantly, it will just run away and reappear later in the tunnel. However, if you freeze it using one of the liquid nitrogen pipes, firing your rocket will cause its body to shatter, leading to an instant-kill. &lt;br&gt; Moreover, be forewarned that the explosion's AoE radius can damage both Leon and Ashley. If Ashley is already incapacitated, then taking even a smidgen of damage from the blast would kill her and lead to a game over. Last but not least, there's also another variant known as the Infinite Rocket Launcher. As the name implies, it's got an unlimited number of projectiles that it can fire. We discuss this in our unlockables guide. &lt;br&gt; Resident Evil 4 has more mechanics and secrets for you to discover. You can learn more in our guides hub.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;詳細句子文法解析：&lt;br&gt;1. The Rocket Launcher is one of the most iconic weapons not just in Resident Evil 4, but the entirety of the survival horror franchise.&lt;br&gt;重點：本句使用the most + 形容詞最高級，用以表達此武器在生存恐怖遊戲領域的代表性以及重要性。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. This armament has a single shot, so make it count.&lt;br&gt;重點：本句使用一般現在式動詞"has"表示"具有"，使句子簡潔明瞭；另外，使用片語"make it count"表示"好好把握"。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. Here's our guide to help you get the Rocket Launcher in Resident Evil 4.&lt;br&gt;重點：本句使用's + 名詞表示"這裡"，來引言即將提到的主題為本文所提供之指南。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. Likewise, you can learn more from our weapons hub.&lt;br&gt;重點：本句使用"likewise"表示"同樣地"，用以提醒讀者還可以從該網站的"武器中心"中學習更多資訊。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. The Rocket Launcher in Resident Evil 4 can be found after you've cleared the Lake area.&lt;br&gt;重點：本句使用"can be ~"表示"可以被發現"，暗示此武器並非一定可得。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;6. Basically, you'll need to take out the Del Lago boss, then make your way past the Mural Cave Puzzle.&lt;br&gt;重點：本句使用"basically"表示"基本上"，標示整段指南的核心關鍵點，並使用"take out"表示"擊敗"，以及"make your way past"表示"越過"。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;7. Eventually, you should find a boat, one that you can sail back to the docks where the Merchant resides.&lt;br&gt;重點：本句使用"eventually"表示"最後"，照時間軸描述取得該武器的進程；並在句中使用形容詞子句"one that you can sail back to the docks where the Merchant resides"來形容"一艘船"，使句子更具描述性。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;8. By the time you get there, your old vendor pal should have the Rocket Launcher as one of his wares, and it costs a whopping 80,000 pesetas.&lt;br&gt;重點：本句使用"by the time"表示"到了那個時候"；同時，使用"should have"表示應該只會發現，而非固定目標；另外，使用副詞"whopping"，表示數字"80,000"十分高居然會讓人感到震驚。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;9. This amount might seem daunting at first, though the weapon doesn't really have further upgrades (it won't need any).&lt;br&gt;重點：本句使用"at first"表示"起初"，暗示後面文句中態度會有所改變；其中使用片語"seem daunting"來新增形容詞意涵，意為"看似困難"。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;10. Generally speaking, there's no reason for you to pick up the Resident Evil 4 Rocket Launcher so early in the game.&lt;br&gt;重點：本句使用"generally speaking"表示"一般而言"，及"so early in the game"表示"在遊戲中這麼早"，來暗示此種情況不常見。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;單字：&lt;br&gt;1. iconic：代表性強的&lt;br&gt;記憶方法：icon(偶像)+ic→具有代表性的偶像&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. armament：武器&lt;br&gt;記憶方法：arm(手臂)+ament→手中的武器&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. projectile：發射物&lt;br&gt;記憶方法：project(射出)+ile→能夠發射的物品&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. daunting：令人膽怯的&lt;br&gt;記憶方法：daunt(威嚇)+ing→使人威嚇的事物&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. wares：貨物&lt;br&gt;記憶方法：war(戰爭)+es→貨物，即指可以貿易品&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;6. whopping：高的令人震驚的&lt;br&gt;記憶方法：whop(猛擊)+ing→打擊人心的數字&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;片語：&lt;br&gt;1. make it count：好好把握&lt;br&gt;相似片語：make the most of it：充分利用&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. eventually：最後&lt;br&gt;相似片語：in the end：最終&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. at first：起初&lt;br&gt;相似片語：initially：起初;第一次&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. generally speaking：一般而言&lt;br&gt;相似片語：all in all：總而言之&lt;br&gt;反義片語：exceptionally：特殊的/破例的&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;其它：&lt;br&gt;1. Resident Evil 4：生化危機4&lt;br&gt;2. peseta：除了萊拉以外的另一種西班牙貨幣&lt;br&gt;日文單字：ペセタ (pese ta)&lt;br&gt;3. Infinite Rocket Launcher：無限火箭筒&lt;br&gt;日文單字：無限ロケットランチャー (mugen roketto ranchaa)</content><link href="https://www.gamespot.com/articles/resident-evil-4-rocket-launcher-guide/1100-6512560/" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>