<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><id>https://github.com/weg38asyy/GameRss.git</id><title>My Game Rss</title><updated>2023-06-01T13:13:44.862972+00:00</updated><author><name>Koala</name><email>weg38asyy@gmail.com</email></author><link href="https://github.com/weg38asyy" rel="alternate"/><generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator><subtitle>Personal learning of English use</subtitle><entry><id>https://www.gamespot.com/articles/etrian-odyssey-origins-collection-is-discounted-ahead-of-tomorrows-launch/1100-6511380/</id><title>Etrian Odyssey Origins Collection Is Discounted Ahead Of Tomorrow's Launch</title><updated>2023-06-01T13:13:44.863223+00:00</updated><content type="html">The Etrian Odyssey series returns on PC and Nintendo Switch on June 1. The first three games in the dungeon crawler franchise are receiving HD remakes. All three games are being sold separately, but you'll get far more bang for your buck by purchasing the Etrian Odyssey Origins Collection, which comes with all three. If you're interested in revisiting the world of Etrian Odyssey (or jumping in for the first time), you can save on Steam keys at Fanatical. The full Etrian Odyssey Origins Collection is available for just $72.15 (normally $80), or you can grab standalone copies of  Etrian Odyssey HD,   Etrian Odyssey 2 HD,  and  Etrian Odyssey 3 HD  for just $35.19 each (normally $40 apiece). &lt;br&gt; All preorders include DLC packs of additional character portraits of various Shin Megami Tensei and Persona characters you can use in-game as a bonus, plus a 5% off coupon to use on future Fanatical purchases. &lt;br&gt; Etrian Odyssey is a series of dungeon RPGs on the Nintendo DS and 3DS where players explore daunting labyrinths in first person with a party of customizable characters. The games are inspired by classic dungeon crawlers like Wizardry and Might &amp; Magic, featuring tough turn-based combat and deep party management reminiscent of those old-school titles, but with modernized presentation and gameplay. The series’ trademark gameplay hook is the map drawing system, where players hand-draw the in-game maps for each dungeon floor using the DS and 3DS touch screens. &lt;br&gt; The Etrian Odyssey Origins Collection brings the first three games, originally released on the DS, to PC and the Nintendo Switch with enhanced HD graphics, remastered soundtracks by series composer Yuzo Koshiro, new difficulty settings, and retooled mapping controls with a single-screen gameplay presentation. You can preorder the Nintendo Switch version on the eShop. &lt;br&gt; Disclaimer: GameSpot and Fanatical are both owned by Fandom. &lt;br&gt; Best Gaming &amp; Tech Deals This Week&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;詳細句子文法解析：&lt;br&gt;1. The Etrian Odyssey series returns on PC and Nintendo Switch on June 1.&lt;br&gt;Subject + verb (+ object) 的基本句型， "returns" 為原型動詞，單純式現在，表示 '系列回來了'。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. The first three games in the dungeon crawler franchise are receiving HD remakes.&lt;br&gt;Subject + verb (+ object) 的基本句型，"are receiving" 為進行式現在，表示 '現在（由現在開始及未來）正在接收重製版搭配'.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. All three games are being sold separately, but you'll get far more bang for your buck by purchasing the Etrian Odyssey Origins Collection, which comes with all three.&lt;br&gt;複文句型，'all three games are being sold separately' 和 'you'll get far more bang for your buck by purchasing the Etrian Odyssey Origins Collection', 'but' 是轉折詞，表示後者是一個建議來降低費用.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. If you're interested in revisiting the world of Etrian Odyssey (or jumping in for the first time), you can save on Steam keys at Fanatical.&lt;br&gt;複文句型，If 用來表條件，you can save 用來表結果「如果你有興趣回到Etrian Odyssey 的世界，或者是第一次嘗試進入」，舉許此判斷，主詞必須為人.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. The full Etrian Odyssey Origins Collection is available for just $72.15 (normally $80), or you can grab standalone copies of Etrian Odyssey HD, Etrian Odyssey 2 HD, and Etrian Odyssey 3 HD for just $35.19 each (normally $40 apiece).&lt;br&gt;複文，'The full Etrian Odyssey Origins Collection is available for just $72.15', 'or you can grab standalone copies of ~ for just $35.19 each'， ',' 用來分別連接兩個句子和兩個詞語.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;6. All preorders include DLC packs of additional character portraits of various Shin Megami Tensei and Persona characters you can use in-game as a bonus, plus a 5% off coupon to use on future Fanatical purchases.&lt;br&gt;複合單子，盡量避免疊詞，確保語意清晰，'bonus'-&gt; 'thank you for your support', 'coupon'='discount.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;7. Etrian Odyssey is a series of dungeon RPGs on the Nintendo DS and 3DS where players explore daunting labyrinths in first person with a party of customizable characters.&lt;br&gt;Simple sentence structure, 主詞はSubject+verb(+object)，where 為副詞 (類似於in which),“where players explore”的部分为一个形容詞从句，該從句修飾先前的“labyrinths".&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;8. The games are inspired by classic dungeon crawlers like Wizardry and Might &amp; Magic, featuring tough turn-based combat and deep party management reminiscent of those old-school titles, but with modernized presentation and gameplay.&lt;br&gt;複文，兩個獨立的句子，用 ‘but’ 連接，表示相對或者附帶的條件.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;9. The series’ trademark gameplay hook is the map drawing system, where players hand-draw the in-game maps for each dungeon floor using the DS and 3DS touch screens.&lt;br&gt;複文，'The series’ trademark gameplay hook is the map drawing system' -&gt; 這是一個介紹習慣， 'where' -&gt; 副詞從句/遠程形容詞的含義表示，該從句修饰先前的 map drawing system.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;10. The Etrian Odyssey Origins Collection brings the first three games, originally released on the DS, to PC and the Nintendo Switch with enhanced HD graphics, remastered soundtracks by series composer Yuzo Koshiro, new difficulty settings, and retooled mapping controls with a single-screen gameplay presentation.&lt;br&gt;複文句型，說明 Brig back the first 3 games,到 Steam 和 Switch。由“with enhanced HD graphics to...”，“remastered soundtracks by...”等等話所引领. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;單字：&lt;br&gt;1. labyrinths [n.] 迷宮，maze。&lt;br&gt;2. dungeon [n.] 地下城邦，underground prison。&lt;br&gt;3. franchise [n.] 版權經營權，股權，範圍經營權。&lt;br&gt;4. customizable [adj.] 自定義的，可定制的，靈活的。&lt;br&gt;5. preorders [n.] 預訂，預售。&lt;br&gt;6. playable [adj.] 可玩的，可操作的。&lt;br&gt;7. soundtrack [n.] 音樂集，原聲帶，改編配樂。&lt;br&gt;8. HD [adj.] 高清晰度的，高質量的。&lt;br&gt;9. presentation [n.] 贈送，展覽，介紹，小禮物。&lt;br&gt;10. hook [n.] 扣子，鉤子，勾引。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;單詞記憶提示：&lt;br&gt;1. labyrinths[日] 迷宮: 迷路在lab族(收拾整理)的房間裡&lt;br&gt;2. dungeon[日] 地下城: 種花在 d u n 上&lt;br&gt;3. franchise[日] 版權經營: 就是 我麻煩了franchise伙伴兄弟&lt;br&gt;4. customizable[日] 自訂: 小村在同族mandarin樹下活下來，要訂在操作面板仔細流程&lt;br&gt;5. preorders[日] 預購: 食姓名即是好耶！預購名額再快旅行。&lt;br&gt;6. playable[日] 可玩: 妹妹很及格~she is playable today~&lt;br&gt;7. soundtrack[日] 原聲帶: 對攝影師裡最美31M二女&lt;br&gt;8. HD[日] 高清晰度: 悔學中文HY的我是HD，好的，簡單。&lt;br&gt;9. presentation[日] 展示: 今天宣傳的我想要得獎：參加maple show，請大家支持我吧。&lt;br&gt;10. hook[日] 挂鉤: 老師說來採溪之前要帶串BEST FISｈHIDING钓餌回家我只想睡覺。 &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;片語：&lt;br&gt;1. receiving HD remakes 的相似片語: accepting new opportunities, welcoming changes, embracing new challenges&lt;br&gt;2. standalone copies 的相似片語: complete set, whole package, all-in-one device&lt;br&gt;3. by purchasing 的反義片語: by renting, by borrowing, by sharing&lt;br&gt;4. inspired by 的相似片語: influenced by, derived from, patterned after.&lt;br&gt;5. in-game 的相似片語: live gameplay, real-time scenario, immersive animation &lt;br&gt;6. trademark gameplay hook 的相似片語: defining feature, recognisable gameplay aspect, key signature element &lt;br&gt;7. hand-draw 的反義片語: computer-generated, auto-map, procedurally generated.&lt;br&gt;8. enhanced HD graphics 的相似片語: improved visual effects, upgraded display resolution, polished graphical output.&lt;br&gt;9. remastered soundtracks 的相似片語: revamped background music, renovated musical scores, remixed sound effects.&lt;br&gt;10. retooled mapping controls 的相似片語: refined cartographical interface, optimised mapmaking mechanics, streamlined map editing.</content><link href="https://www.gamespot.com/articles/etrian-odyssey-origins-collection-is-discounted-ahead-of-tomorrows-launch/1100-6511380/" rel="alternate"/></entry></feed>